Hi, I don't know. Why do I do it? It's just because
Hey, Goddy see cuz I know that it's like God didn't see my other panels up
So I need to post a new one so God you could come hang out
Hi chibi chibi, yeah, I mean it's just like why
I mean, I didn't ask I stepped in it because I was asking for it, right?
Welcome. Oh, welcome. Thank you. I wasn't I wasn't gone for a while
I was just going for like a little a little time. Maybe my my bosom, but
Sorry, sorry. It's okay
I know I refer you would say 23 or something or I don't know what it's a 23 is w and then
Numbers P whatever
23 I don't know. I don't know whatever
numerological code
No, no, not you not you as much. I know but I probably couldn't have brought it up, but you know you had to know
Yeah, how are we doing guys? Yeah, people were I wasn't I was here yesterday. I'm here today
I've been here every day, but you know I didn't see you at all last night or all today. Were you okay?
Yeah
I like I worked on like basically for like several hours yesterday. My friends came over and like
Help me vacuum. They've like they clean my my clean my my my bath with my bath is so sparkling white now
Friends that that you were able to actually
Have real-life conversations with versus us not that I don't love talking to us, but it's important
Well, I had you have it but it's like, you know, it's like, you know, it's how dangerous that everybody is in either place
You know, it's like I got my busy stick close to my family, you know
We're so sad about your bike and then you left. Yeah. Well, I was sad about my bike
But I bet my bike will be fine because it's like
I think it's here. I probably it's probably in the mailbox. I just have to like go down and get it
But if not, I got it already like a message back from bike shop
They're like hey if your bike is not turning on or all these things. It's like, you know, they
They, you know, they, they can, they can fix it and stuff.
I think it's just might be a fuse or something.
So we'll see.
I think it, it's gonna be good.
What happened?
Yeah. And Spunky, you're not mad at Spunky.
He wasn't mad at God either.
I think someone said it was Spunky was mad at God
or something.
I don't think they've ever been mad at each other.
But yeah, she did fart in her bed and wake up Justin.
Okay.
She said she didn't do it.
Yeah.
We all fart.
Well, yeah.
I've already seen you're human beings, you know, it's like
really
People there are people that just hate hate being a human being, you know, it's like did everybody hit the like button, please
I don't know it. Did everybody hit it like it's 26 people. Let me see. Okay. I did have to private do the stream
But you know, I did but Christina even though even though I did I did
You know, you know, I do
Lead a significant amount of my streams probably about almost half my streams. I have to leave
Um, still I have, uh, 10,000 watch hours the last, uh, 30 days I have like almost like a million.
It's like, it's like so many, um, impressions, like 650,000 impressions they gave and I got like,
like a hundred thousand people to join me.
It's like, so it's like really cool.
Um, seeing the statistics also have like 79 members or something like that.
So it's getting back to that.
You know what else you didn't buy any of them.
Well, I did well some of the men some of the memberships I did I did but I did buy some of the memberships, you know people people buy
Oh, yeah subscribers. Yeah
Well, I have 25 55
I have two thousand five hundred few five subscribers now
I think I think around 2,500 25 point six or something 2.56 or something like that
Bozzi used to fart all the time till I changed his food now. He doesn't fart hardly at all
Yeah, I remember those horses those horses, but you know, we would do other I worked when it's on a working ranch
as that, you know, I was
You know preteen kind of years. It was like a Christian ranch and we wouldn't think right right
They just had to ride horses and stuff in the horses. Yeah, they would
You know, I'm just like, you know, I was a good mom and bought my son a horse my my
mistake was I bought two Arabians
well
I have a friend that was going to train him because she said those Arabians had no business around my kids and
I'll be damned. She had him a week one of them bucked her and broke both kneecaps
So she wouldn't give them back because she didn't want that my children to have them
Which thank her, you know, I I appreciate that she looked out for my children
Sweet peeps is telling cute little story. Let's see. Thankfully there because yeah, everyone in chat
I already everyone's even getting their protein and the bino. I don't know everyone everyone's talking about digestion
It's been a fun day. Yeah, it's just one of those days guys. What day is it? It's June 30. It's actually at Lisa's birthday
That's the day the least of the Giordano's birthday having birthday at least I love you sweetheart. I might read a
Might try to call it to you later before I can't my Lisa, but
We shall see. You know, I know you're probably very busy and a lot of people are wishing you love today
Yeah, it's been a fun day. Yeah, it's been a good day. You know, I say, you know
Myself or it's like, you know what it's like you're gonna matter matter what you like, you know, you're a good person
You know, you love people. You know, you would never hurt anybody. You know, you're
Harmless person would not hurt a fly
I will tell you, I just came from a horrendous meeting where everybody was yelling and screaming
and I thought the police were going to be called.
So I'm kind of a little hyped up, I might as well share that now, so I'm processing
it.
I apologize.
Well, what's happening is you had a meeting about
No, it's been a hot meeting and we got the FBI involved we got
We got the state's attorney involved and the IRS because
People are doing bad things
So we have been trying to stop it and they don't like it
No, I mean it's like, you know, it's like trying to get in like the Joker and Joker and Catwoman's plans
It's like they're gonna
And they're trying to hide it and we won't let them know
No guys, I'm sorry. I said we're the new we're the new the agent Aquarius say everything's coming to light in this new
New era and also we'll find out there's certain things that will come to light that we don't like
There's also gonna be the reasons for those things that we don't like that
We're not we're gonna like even worse than the reason we don't like remember remember all those readings that you told me that
you know, I was concentrating on something working on something big and it'll all come to like, well,
tonight it kind of did, just saying, and it involves like 5000 people. So we had to stop it. We had to stop it.
Right, I mean it's like in it guys think about how like these these five thousand people are gonna have like a better day
They're not gonna have some kind of weird. They're not gonna get money still in from them anymore
I had some horrible horrible circumstance happen hundreds of thousands of dollars have been stolen that we're stopping
Thank you. So we did good. We did good. We did good damn it
Sorry. Good jobs. Good jobs, Christine and everybody, you know, fighting to get a fight. You know, also we got the we got the wreckage here RICO. We had this Rico working for us too.
Then the first but now I had to put more cameras on my house.
Retaliation is true to happen.
Well, yeah, that's why I mean I say I don't I don't ever fire the first shots
You know I'd say I will sometimes respond with like a snarky way, but it's I wouldn't really even attack back
I just will like let the person
Wear themselves out wear out their own resources with like trying to like get me and then it's like then I always look up
And everything's always fine, you know, there might be like a little bit of a one of the hedges is burned away or you know
But it's like most of everything and everything is looking fine. And so
Well, you know something I'm always we we tried to get them to fix things without involving
people
And without involving the government and they chose not to
Yeah, but the problem is it's like these people most these people are informants for these agencies in a way that might be double agent
I mean it gets it's everyone wants to be James Bond or like some kind of sweet games or I don't know
I get to I get the Christie, but Angela Lansbury. I don't know everyone wants to be some kind of like, you know
Nancy drew Inspector Gadget
Bucking Batman Catwoman everyone. I wait we keep living out these these same story lines over and over again
So good like we got the people trying to steal the people to try to protect protect everybody and then the middle like what the fuck is going on
You know, so, you know, it's a guy, you know, just wait a lot of what the fuck's going on and now we're setting light on it
Yep, that's yeah
So how many yeah, I don't know how Patrick found me. Who's who's Patrick by the way Patrick? Why should I come up?
Is there a reason you think I need to come up
Yeah, well it's like the midnight you're talking to say I was built for war
It's like if you look into my astrology my Mars so Mars is a planet of war like Mars is a like the red planet
It's a planet of like, you know, so it's like the wands. It's all it's like all this fury and anger and
War like stuff, but it's in my first house. Like, you know, the first house is a house of identity
It's also an Aquarius. So it's a very detached kind of planner. It's kind of like not too good too much of my
too much of my my my strategy in my way it's just like I'm a very I'm very detached from
from emotions you know in certain way. Aquarius are kind of like aliens you know
they're artists or our emotions are like there'd be too much to take all our one
sweets we'd rather not have them at all but the cap my Capricorn is very sweet though it
has a big heart that's why I have heart on one side of my chest not the other one
one side of my Aquarius
Hi, I got it. Yeah, I'm drinking a beer right now a voodoo ranger
How does everyone do in the chat where is everybody is it my is my link pinned I don't look I pinned it again
Pin it again. Come on up
It's Sunday night it might be a little slow night this week, but actually it's 28 people
We're doing okay. We're doing okay. We're doing okay. You're good
And and what do you mean or else Patrick?
What do you mean are else?
You don't want to mess with me trust to me
Patrick you're making threats
He said cam up or else who the hell does he think he is?
You talk to Christine like that you little
You monster. How are you? It's many oh, it's Monday. Oh my god. I just said it was Sunday. Oh my god. It's Monday. Good Lord
You didn't you didn't you didn't go live last night. Yep
There we go guy that pin that link is
I'm sorry we can enemies enemies list Christine. Oh, no
I remember tomorrow is Canada Day. Happy Canada Day page. Oh
Midnight is already a long one service is blocked service is not blocked. Come on. Goddy. Come on up
What are you doing? We need we need some meetings. We need some games more games
There's a little panel for a Christmas night start the list of enemies for me. I told them that's a long list
Oh
There you go, St. Pete. I'm no problem with that. I live in Florida.
Patrick is a menace to Chrissy and just usually pee-pee.
Yeah, happy birthday. Or happy Canada's day. Canada dry.
You know, happy Canada day tomorrow. Canada dry. Canada dry. I can't say I'm a big fan of you.
Canada dry. I did not like your your lost appearance where you made weird faces and
Introduce other some other woman. He introduced some woman. I was there and he just wanted to show you
He had a woman and I got a look that she was a lie
I mean a weird face and then you wore a shirt about it said
Something about the size of his rod or something. I don't know. He's not my fishing. I don't know. Oh, yeah
Remember that guy who is there? I remember that he's a fake fake
Yeah, it's a big phony baloney
I've known him for a while. He doesn't like me.
Never any wines. He's such a cry, baby. He never said me updated. He never said me updated graphics
My graphic says it says Ikea Ikea Wakin does my I'm always Ikea Wakin, but I know appreciate him making me grow the graph
He thinks if she would have made you go graphics that
He gets leeway on what he wants and and that's not the way that's the way it's supposed to work. If you give somebody it's a gift and you keep it moving
Yeah, let me say but and it's like somebody like donates for a particular reason like you know if they were for reading or for
You know, you know for the kicking someone out the panel or or to say specifies a donation
But it shouldn't be like, you know, I have Arthur like still hey
I'm a donator and I'm being disrespected in your chat and I'm like, okay
Well, I think you might have donated maybe like a couple times the first month I was out
So that was a few months ago. I appreciate
those donations, it's like, I mean, it's like, you know, you're not a member now. He's not a member now. You know, I say so.
You know, I will tell you psych, I'm not a member, but you know a couple of times a week, I throw
membership gifts out there. Yes, yes, because I think it's more important to get the people who really don't come an
incentive to come to your panel or your channel versus me who come.
Does it make sense? Yeah, and I think there's really interesting people who have gotten the memberships to like, you know
Time time when a membership, you know
Oh, also, I think there's like someone named the shit show and they have a really cool show there
Yeah, he does have a cool show. He's been on here. I think once yeah
He has a membership and then and then who else? Oh, yeah, this person named name blame it on Katie or something
Yeah
But you know, I do a couple times a week. I donate a
Yes, membership because yes, that's how you get people to come into your stream
Sure, I can do it on myself. But what's the point? I'm here anyway. You know what I mean?
Yes
well, you know the cool thing about the memberships to is that
You know, it's like people can decide whether they want to renew them renew or not
And uh, you know, it's also, you know, there's really, there's also really cool things
I don't know guys
Have you seen the things where there's like some kind of gifting option? I don't know if they had I turned on this thing
This option in my chat called gifting. I don't know what it does or how it works
But I don't have you heard of it. It should be like I don't know if there's an extra extra setting in there
Let me know about it. Let me look
Let me see. I'll tell you what it said. I don't maybe it takes a little while to
kind of start working like the points, but let me see.
Oh, on those points, you can like buy
a Super Chat less expensive if you get so much,
and I think, and I've never seen anybody,
but if you get so many, you get a free Super Chat,
but I've never seen anybody get that yet.
But I will I will share with you there is a change coming and hasn't hit you yet
But you know how we all use these names
Um, yeah, it's going to be changing that it's going to be YouTube is going to show it
It by the at sign and what your channel name is so like its sweepy has a different name that
He used to create this it'll say at whatever it is
I've seen it on a few channels already and they're they're saying that it is a new thing that
is going to be rolled out by YouTube so instead of all so that's going to help you for example
all these um people that come in like the katie one we were just talking about that's going to
Yeah, so it's gonna help differentiate like see mine is you're not gonna like mine mine is at
Christine six six six six
Ironic isn't it? I know it's me. I know it's me. I'm just kidding
Grande, uh, Grendel's sack. Oh, what's that? What is it for? I don't know what a Grendel's sack is. I don't know.
All I know is I'm locking my door on 4th of July. That sounds kind of scary. I got, I got a sedate.
I got a sedate for Fawze. Hey, look at mobile, mobile, mole, 90, or one, or one, five, nine,
Molly mo mo mo. Yes. Yeah, you gotta get she got a gift at me for shit
Any guys if you want them, let me know if you want to read anyone to do with sacks on this channel
It's probably better not to ask any questions. I love those sacks
Is there somebody named sacks on the channel or sasks? Oh, you're having a sasque. Okay. Dingle such a good boy. Hey, Dingle
Oh, excuse me guys
Yeah, don't talk about sasks sacks sex or any of the bug not even the number six
Yeah
So you pee
Bozies like that and I just feel so bad because I give them the smallest dose possible
And he and he walks around like a zombie for two days
I feel so bad for him, but I don't know what else to do
I've even cut the dose in half what the doctor said to give are the vet
But I can't I can't let him get so stressed because his heart races and he starts drooling and that's not fair
Christine I do not I'm not true. Oh, you have my father. I'm sorry. No, no, not father. Oh, it's not who is it was
Which dog Christine? Oh, it's it is foxy. Okay. Yeah, I was thinking I was true
It wasn't fun, but Christine my sister does have her she has these two dogs and they're really cute like foxy
I think they're like, you know on the same kind of
general family as a fuzzy and
She has his problems. She has to give her dog a steroid the steroid gets the dog heavy and
He's walking harder. So they get this whole balance of giving the medication trying to extend the life
You can make him the dog as comfortable as possible. And you know, I think it's gonna kind of steroids
You know, I know these can get the crease the appetite a lot the dogs we eat a lot more
Right. No, it's just sad. We love our dogs and you know, we try to keep our dogs here as long as we can, you know, you know
I I had a dog that had a stroke and it couldn't walk on its hind legs
It had nothing and I tried so hard and I kept it
For a week later and then I had to put it down
I just didn't have an option because she was 70 pounds and I can't lift 70 pounds to take her outside and all that I can't do it
I mean my gosh, I only weigh like less than a hundred and twenty. How am I supposed to live this seventy eighty pound dog?
It was sad
What are you guys talking about ding who's soul is yours got it?
You're not let us steal keep the my my chat souls gaudy you have to behave yourself. No stealing souls
God ain't give those souls back. No, you cannot soul take her
Yeah, Gotti. It's like I want to I want to see a contract. I want to see a signed contract
With Ursula, you know notarized by the the the king of the sea, okay?
I want to see I want to see that contract before you come taking so the souls from anybody in my chat
Okay, Christine. Do you have any diet tips? I rather wish I weighed 120 pounds. Okay, it's very important know what you eat
I promise you
Eat your proteins first. I eat the size of the palm of my hand for a meal
And I don't do white. I don't do white rice white bread white pasta white milk
nothing
Nothing white. I and and this is not me. I'm not being racist. So in my in my world
When we talk about food, white's not right.
That's how it is.
No, no, no.
Got it.
So, but this is called, okay, I'm not gonna go over the whole little mermaid, the legal
verse again, okay?
So,
Just me accepting you on the panel does not infer or imply or guarantee anything. All it guarantees is that I have
No, it's not it's not some deal for you can have all my souls. This is like the kind of legal argument that
AMC ghosts makes, you know, the AMC person. Yeah, it's just it's like
The legal premises of a loon. Okay. You're basically talking like a lunatic right now
Don't be a loon. Don't be a lunatic. I don't know. It takes guy. Gotty. Come on
It's the law of the seas. Maritime law. Okay. Okay. I know. Yes. Nothing
process. Try to make and I know and I I can't tell you how I don't ever go out
ever and my serving size fits in the palm of my hand.
It's very important and proteins are very, very important.
That's what build your muscle plus play pickleball with me. I play pickleball all the time. I
Love pickleball
Okay, that's weird right and I swim
Guys, you're supposed to guys you're not supposed to you're supposed to read it read look
She's looking away. She's like no no no
No, no, I do not agree to these terms the conditions plus she's 16 years old. I mean it's like
Yeah
Or Ariel's a minor. Okay. Leave leave leave Ariel alone. Okay. Oh, no
Now Ariel for the little mermaid now is now he's talking about now. He's talking about Cthulhu. Okay
And now he's now he's bringing in the the briley. You know, love traffic
You know where my granddaughter went yesterday with her daddy and her uncle and her cousin
They went to they went to unicorn worlds
They get to ride unicorns and everything
I'm afraid I'm afraid if I went to a place called Unicorn World, I ended up in one of the cages, but
There were no cages. Okay. There's no cages. Okay. Well, thank God. There were no cages
I probably be locked up in the backstage, but it was really it was really nice, but
They have like my little ponies come out or was it like, you know, you know, yeah, they were unicorns
There were actually unicorns there were I swear to God
There were unicorns that had only one horn in the center of their head.
Christine, Christine, those are either rhinoceroses or they glued,
they glued a fake horn on them. No, no, no, no, no.
They weren't, my son, look, they were growing out of their head.
Okay, well, Christine, I think that's just what they tell the kids.
They tell the kids. No, my son was there.
Okay. Okay. I believe you. I believe you. I believe you. I'm yes
Somehow or another they have greeted these horses
Yeah, 90 horses to have one horn come out of their head. Well, that's that's that's that's that's that's an unfortunate
Like growth, I mean, that's like it's that's not a that's not a real that's not like a unicorn horn
The unicorn horns are magical and they can make they like you know like a spear
Well, it was magic because Riley asked for something in the unicorn
wished it with its nose and gave it to my granddaughter and it was what she
wanted. Well was it like a unicorn? Was it for a unicorn?
It was she wanted a baby unicorn and a little unicorn with a baby, and that's what they gave her
I guess it guys guys. I told you
Last I
Was in my other granddaughter was 12 and she didn't really want to go but she came home so excited telling me all about it
Yes, they had a blast
Hey, Chris. Are you my little pony unicorns Chris? Oh, no
No, I'm with a kid with a kid with it Chris
Watches like cartoons or that shit back in there when I was younger. Oh
My little pony
Yeah, my little pony full of balloon. We have all got all kinds of my little pony stuff here. Oh my gosh
No, I'm just uh, I'm thinking about uh, what's his name the lead singer of a sound garden, Chris Cornell. Yeah, he passed away, unfortunately
Yeah, why are you thinking about these people that I know why are you thinking about these people that are very controversial that I don't
Live themselves right at this very moment. I'd like to understand that
Why are you thinking about them?
Oh, come on, Christian.
I want to hear what is the theme of Mr. Bennington
and Chris Cornell right now.
Right now.
Why?
Wash away the rain.
Wash away Chris from my chat because he sucks.
Bye.
Mr. Sike, did you ever get that nail brush I told you to get?
Yeah, I did.
It's on his way.
It's coming.
OK, thank you.
This is coming. I got I got a whole I got a whole set of 60
64 tools 64 male tools all you need is an albrush. I promise you
Yeah, it has several it has several things you can dig out all the stuff out of them. Well
Be careful though because you don't want to dig out too far where you end up bleeding underneath there causing an infection
Yeah, oh, yeah, they're not guys. There's no infection. There's me. There's me no infection. Okay. No if you start using those tools
Won't they come not today God and not today not looking at the the clouds
It's looking rainy with that without a chance to come. Okay, so hold on angle if you're dreaming about psych
We need to have a conversation, please
Dingo says I wonder why psych was a dentist in my dream. I recognized him. I trusted him with my teeth
If he's dreaming don't know offense, but if he's dreaming about you, we have a problem. Oh
My god, guys, I'm not Freddie. I only have so many I only have so many
I only so many, you know rain cells. I'm sorry guys. Well, my battery is almost almost gone guys. I'm at 1%
Maybe 2%
I don't know if my bike will ever exist again guys. We'll see. I'm gonna get my battery fixed
I'm gonna get that battery fix guys your new charger will work all you gotta do
I'm gonna let it let it go for 24 hours and
Then see don't freak out about it yet
Okay, I'm gonna probably a little bit
Come back Chris Chris you're gonna make fun of me all night
You're just gonna make fun of me like I'm like I'm a joke and then just keep wanting to come back
Well, no, I'm trying to find you you had to restart your stream. What happened? Yeah, because you said you said you said I
23 ABC the EFG H.I.J.K. Oh, and I know he said twenty three twenty three fifteen
Which is like some kind of you know code you have to say that if it's a code you're supposed to say
Yes, you said WP, but you spelled it out. It's okay. He's all right
Hey, baby. All right. Hi. Hi, Christine. Hi, Chris. Hi, too
I
Today's Monday is crazy. So I just did like a bunch of stuff and then I went to the pool
Okay, hey come up come up
No, no, she doesn't want to she's no
People don't have to cam up I
Can't love sometimes whenever I like it we'd probably be better off if you did not come
Those three people that aren't came up. I really
Despise when people like you came up. I have I have
No, that's not it. That's like Chris's signature word. He always says, hey, busters, come on.
You just got to know Chris.
Well, that's just Chris's personality. That's just the way it is.
Chris is just Chris, yeah.
You're the thing like like when you're like they look but every good you see
He's very expressive which I like when you do
Basically every time you come up be there's like you don't look you know you think like oh
You say some shit before you can't do it, but like you end up doing it
Chris how is that Albert?
No, come on. Don't pick on him. Prince Albert. Albert, what are you talking about? Oh, look, Psyche's interested.
No, in my cat. He's in my cat. He's out of my couch probably.
Okay.
Katie Gangster, come here.
I thought you meant Prince Albert.
No, he's a cute one.
He's a cat.
This is my body. I suggest you behave.
Hey, God, he's got a missy heavy. God is missy heavy again. God. He is
behaving
Man, God, yeah, I don't know if they're the same
That you got he got he's being fine. Jamie. Jamie's Cowboys. Tell me what's going on. Where are the dogs?
But your kid either
Oh
That's over an hour ago
She did she left over an hour ago she did had a thing. Here's KZ
You tell me calm down
No, no, she said gaudi and then like gaudi's not even doing anything
I didn't say gotty
God he has bodyguards in in the
Man God he there's a name in chat
Well, you don't have to yell whenever well pay attention
Whenever you scream you don't have to yell
Crystal I mean not crystal Christine is a unicorn. Okay, don't ever mess with her. Oh, well, you always watch your mouth
You just a rooster
Yes, God. He was. And by the way, with Bita, she she always takes up her females. So don't mind her. Why not? Don't be sorry, Captain. We, we, we straighten women's crowns. Why not?
You guys don't you need to straighten each other's mohawks if you want to be men.
What's up? What are you telling me? We can't wake it. We have you.
Oh, look at the chicken.
You're my chicken.
You're my thing.
I
Just in 1979
No, my birthday. Well, no, no, no, I'm not kidding my birthday. What?
Yeah, I'm like the smashy pumpkin song guys
It doesn't matter what you think about me. It's like, I just knew that, you know, Goddy. That's not
Yeah
There's someone named mom's Mably
She was the first of stand-up comics. She was actually a black woman in 1940s 1930s and 40s. You look at her
Excuse me, please
Say excuse me
Feel like we're an arm. What do you call it like a library like school library? It was like everybody be quiet
I would be a mood that does we did that but it's funny
You got a rumble
Well, okay, I'm sorry Chris Chris you need to like stream on other plat like rumble and YouTube and stuff like get back on YouTube too
You may not like rumble if you decide rumble. I cannot stand rumble. Yeah
It does stop
Well, I mean you'd like to fucking bite your tongue over here on YouTube where you can't fucking say you have freedom of speech
He has no freedom of speech
No, you know something
The monthly check I get from YouTube makes it better
Yeah, the terms of service prevents freedom of speech. Okay. There is no such thing as freedom of speech
Do you not realize that? Yeah. Well, you know, when you have a business are you allowed to say, oh, you're like
Let's have my business, you know, just like, you know, crucifying a segment of a population of the country
Are you allowed to do that? No
There are consequences to freedom of speech
Have bill money
Yeah, or you know
like I okay so if I have freedom of speech why can I not get in a fight at the local convenience store
and we both go to jail that's stupid that's not you know you will if you like if you like hit him
first you will go to jail you're there he's freedom of speech like you know you can have freedom of
Yeah
Me to the left bottom and then KZ to the right bottom we look like we're both there
I don't want to deeming king up there
Okay, okay, I'll move you guys both
Yeah, let's put the demon king
I'll put next to Casey help me
Turn around your chair
Up with us
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Unique there. No, now I'm on the bottom. Oh
Put me we're ziggies at there we go. No, we're happy
Like a visual thing for you
What I'm talking about is that like when I was a kid
I am saying when I was I know I'm I'm saying how things have changed
Spit it out. Yeah, we meet it
Everything changes
What you're gonna be
It's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it's when it
Now
Like lesbians we're not lesbians. What do you want to put up with me? Oh the cat fix it. I thought he said he don't like
Oh, that's what I hate about the left if I bring in my fist
DT we're talking about the cat right now
Is that another one?
That's too scary.
What is this? What is that? What is that picture?
I thought it was a man with a beard.
That's Fawzi.
She's so cute.
Fawzi, look at her.
She's laying like you can't
This is really okay
So you're pretty pretty
What? What did you just say? Oh, Ziggy, what did you just say?
I just, I don't put animals above people is what I'm trying to say.
What? What?
I have a question. I have a question for you. You wouldn't, you, you wouldn't, would you rather
Can I have a cold spring for a moment, please?
I can't even have it.
I'm sorry.
Yes, you can.
Oh, look.
What is that?
Is that a Chucky doll?
Oh, my God.
No.
what is that oh my god it's a black doll is that like the new the same you got black
dolls you wouldn't you really wouldn't punch punch they're haunted those are haunted dolls christine
do you see those dolls do you see those dolls these are haunted dolls i can i recognize a haunted
doll anyway i see them i see them their eyes are moving with my i know i'm an expert in haunted
Oh, she's a beauty, she's a beauty.
Does everybody have her?
If Albus looks like Rudy, I'm so cute.
Oh
Wait, what's what's your problem, Ziggy? You're gonna be a problem robbing fun
Everyone's laughing having the best time and you're like
Look at the dolls haunted
Oh, it's a it's a it's a male doll, but it's a
It goes squeezes on like a
My grandma made my grandma made a doll than Michael and looks just like that
So I can't I had to hide this doll from my granddaughter. You know why?
It's anatomically correct and it has a squirrel sack and a penis
What's it all? Is it something with an E in it? Yeah, my OI. Chris is doing some channeling. I think that might be an Emily in the goal.
Emily's the one that that was the Chuckie doll. Oh yeah. Hey, yeah. You know the Chuckie doll?
Yeah
Granddaughters bedroom it sits on my couch
You're making a scary doll face.
I'm a horror movie buff, man.
I love fucking horror movies.
Hey, have you seen the puppet master?
Or have you seen the puppet master?
Who's the guy that made the puppets?
The puppeteer or something?
There was a guy that made the puppets.
I don't know.
It was the puppet master.
He made a scary little demon puppet.
I love The Shining.
Shining is a great movie, too.
Stanley Kubrick
I'm sorry
I know it's scary but I have it right
my second personality is like
when he goes crazy and shining
that's my second personality
do you know her other doll
the one I just showed you
we had to hide
exactly what the fuck you were supposed to do
I'm writing something right now
we had to hide the other doll
because it has a throttle sack and a penis
and we're not ready to explain it
but listen
Her other doll has a JJ well doesn't this name her flirty dolly and get it over with
We we bought dolls the teacher anatomically
It's like he's in a comical mode today
That was funny each each one of you like even psyche like what's your favorite scary movie
There's one movie there's a doll
That's that's how it was three three dolly, and it actually lactated and it was
It was it was a talking it was a stocking scary y'all, but
My favorite
And I'm gonna ask Chris K Chris K. What's your fucking favorite scary movie?
Why am I on bottom again in the corner? Oh, I'm sorry. Don't put baby in the corner. I'm sorry
I
Rosemary's I like Rosemary's baby. I like whatever happened to baby Jane
Has so much truth in it. It's a very interesting scary movie here
Okay, it's my turn isn't my turn. Yeah, you can't go some demons talking to him though, didn't he and he went crazy almost
I don't know I don't
know I don't know I don't know
I don't know I don't know I don't know
Uh, uh fuck what's that movie called dude just answer the question
It's the shining that's what he said
So my name really isn't christine and my favorite movie is christine
You can keep Stephen King book, based on the Stephen King books.
Yes.
Like, Christina is a car, right?
Christina is a car that starts to, like, it's kind of like a female night writer.
That will unalive you.
Yeah, yeah, like a female night writer where she was homicidal to begin with, you know,
like a night writer might have.
That's what I'm saying.
My name really is not Christine.
That is why I got that name. I came up with that name. Yeah. Well, here's the thing like you're not
You don't know what I'm doing
Oh my drop
The Lord Vader is a sexy woman and I know I think Doug D and Lord Vader are like really like hot chicks
I just think there's like a lot of hot chicks in the tap for some reason like I know I don't know why
Always beautiful living around here. I know they are but they're all sitting around here
Smoking their cigarettes like it's like a psyche. Who does it think he is? Fuck him. And then hi psyche
They fucking they destroyed his car and the car came back to life and we're like, that's right
That's why my name is Christine. I will I will unalive you
And I come back to life
I'm so glad I don't have beef with Christine. I'm good
I'm not starting shit with her either
This is a better way than the car guys. If you see a car speeding towards you. It's a good idea
Mr. Ronald is
The car is not going to come on the sidewalk with her dolls under name Christine and all that
Christine your next step is to like put all put all your dolls into like one room and then oh, I did
Have that your guest bedroom for the grandkids or whatever
She used to keep all her dolls. She's got this little table, this little kids table.
She used to have all our dolls there and all the tea things so she would have a tea party with her doll.
One night I came in and one of her dolls started talking.
Scared the daylight out of me. I woke my husband up and said, go get those dolls out of the living room.
I was so scared.
No, we're talking.
I've heard I've heard these I mean I've I seriously I've heard these story like I've seen it on YouTube
I've seen videos of dolls their eyes moving them and I started to talk and like yeah, and they tickle me Elmo
He picked up his fur. He's like a strange robotic skeleton, and he's always glitching. Yeah, it's it was pretty crazy
Well, I was scared to death and told my husband
I woke his ass up and said go get those dolls out of that living room get them out
What do you think?
We put him in the closet. Yeah, we have to burn. You ever see the twilight zone there's a twilight zone in the like there's like this family
The husband the wife is remarried. She's a daughter and so
She gets her a talking tina doll. So she has a doll called talking tina
And it's a hi i'm talking tina and i love you and then when the daughter and the mother leave the room
She's like, I don't like you. You're an evil man
Oh my god, we used to have an elsa doll that talked tonight threw it away
I threw the Elsa away. I don't know. It was closer in the middle of the night when nobody was touching it. I threw that SOB in the garbage.
Alright, so clearly you're a Stephen King lover.
I love Stephen King.
Yes. Alright, so there was...
That one that you were talking about but there was also another one, and I can't remember it
Everybody no, it's no I love a cemetery
You know what I have I have a pet cemetery in my yard. Oh
Fuck yeah, but what I'm talking about is the cars
There was another car thing to where everyone was strapped up in the gas station
Where all the trucks are coming in gassing themselves up. You remember that? Okay?
I don't know about that movie. I don't know. Is that a horror movie? Is that a cemetery?
But there's a movie called bird what guys?
Oh my god
Birds yes, we're talking birds. It's called it's called it's called it's called burn
But let's talk about birds right now. So birds. That's another Steve. I said, I think it's an Alfred Hitchcock
Alfred Hitchcock
Yeah, but what I was trying to say is is that Stephen King Stephen King did two
car movies he did one with the
you know
Like are you thinking of like Harry or something? He's talking about one that was like all like some way trucks
They're all trapped in a fucking like a convenience or something
And my mom showed me that, like I, that's where I, I got, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I got that, I
Yeah, it's the guy from like, you know, tell him Bob and
Like on the stupid movie children of the porn scares me still
Okay, that might be the other car movie that mr. Mercedes is called
It's mr. Mercedes
miss
That doesn't sound like a scary movie at all. It sounds like a comedy
Hmm. No, it's scary. It's scary
Yeah, it's pretty when you're here. Yeah, it's pretty guys hero misery hero it right misery. Yeah. Oh, I love it
Like finders keepers
Beedah would be like that with me
Jonathan here. I don't wish
I'm gonna try to the bed and like nail your feet
No, no, no, no, I won't do that. Just get like I'll just tickle you
You weirdo, I'm I have a
I
Protecting be cages ankles. I think we can pee on the bed and then wall and I don't cuz they've been tickled in peace
Fun on the streets and
Yeah, I remember that it was it was like an international scout vehicle. I remember the mist now
Sweet pea am I right?
Because I remember when I was little my parents had an international scout and I was afraid of it
The mist
Yeah
And then we're okay. Why is why is midnight saying they need some more fucking Eve vagina?
Diamonds
I was talking about the other doll. I have
Lord Bader's here
About
See I bought my granddaughter dolls that are anatomically correct, and if you carry them they're like a six pound out
They're like the real babies and they're like they're like a dead babies
They know what I I had made I had made a doll with my granddaughters face on it
You send a picture in and they make a real baby with their face
Yeah, let's let's kind of horrifying
Then you get this like dead object
Has like this similar face and then they're always gonna say that that doll's weird
It looks like me like my my dead twin sister or something like that
It was kind of weird
I collect death mask
like is that terrible but you get it and you can send their picture and tell them what their hair looks like
and they make that doll and I swear it looked just like her it was just the weirdest thing
hey panthro hey spoto this woman already you seem cool no I'm married
Oh, you guys go by you and Jen go back together. Hey, J one
Can I meet I can I have another tempted drawing beat it in that?
Yeah
Christina have you hold on
No
Okay, I did I did pause, okay
My baby I won't want to be please I mean
Okay, you're gonna like you're like so ready. Hey, you're like so
Like smart asses. That's what I like
I'm gonna make this perfect for be like that. I love you so much. Both women are smart
FYI
And not really anymore
Well, I'm a big smart ass. So is Vita. So we got you covered
Fucking be good to go right Vita
We're older we're older we're smart asses
So what are you doing? Why am I on the solo screening yet?
And I would like one next please and I put my picture up
I don't know if you're gonna want one after you see this, okay, I'm gonna put it, I'm gonna put it, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm
No, I don't have an idea of what she looks like and I don't want to, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I don't get that label BKJ wonder why not I
Barely get it, but I have a tattoo to myself. So good
I can't draw like a to tuxedo cats next to it too. It's like a whole
Yeah, they really listen to anybody and I'm telling him like JT and Gaudi's
Don't even care about that kind of stuff, you know say you just whatever I do care a bit is like
Yes, taste the biscuit Oliver. I don't care. I don't care that much. Okay. I'm gonna put Lenore in there too. Hold on. Oh
Yes, yes, Lenora's
There you go. Have you ever seen that? Have you ever heard that song taste the biscuit?
You gotta put
Yeah, you know, mom is there mom is there and okay, you got that and I'm gonna put a
A pentagram and I'm gonna put the crescent moon, okay?
You're not gonna do it
Okay, guys you want to hear but it's not okay. Don't be please don't be insulted be I'm trying to like
I mean you really pissed
Guys you ready to see it ready for the reveal guys
Thank you.
Look at those lips, Vita.
I love it.
Vita, I'm sorry.
You need to make all the noses a little softer.
I love my lips.
You have my heart.
I think the chin.
It's better.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I would like one now.
I love it. Thank you.
Can you save it for me forever?
Yeah.
Um, the kiddies too. I love it. It's adorable.
Yeah, I would like one.
Christine wants one. You got to put Christine's picture on it.
I want to see you actually.
There you go. Oh, Christine, you're pretty.
Oh, Christine. Christine, have you ever seen?
Have you ever seen? Have you ever seen? Have you ever seen? Have you ever seen?
You're seeing it. Have you ever seen the Grinch? I cleaned up pretty good. Who's gonna be the Grinch?
Everyone has this woman named Chris. Her name is Christine something Christine. I can't show you me though
That's her name. Guys, you know from talking about it from the Grinch and she played like the mayor
Guys, her name is a Christine something. She's like I mean a lot in a long order. Her, I think her name is Christine. Hold on
What's her name? Who's that lady's name? You guys, you know, she's on like
The girl with the tattoos, you're talking about.
Christine, Christine, the one that has the little put-off.
Like Lottie?
Lottie?
Are Christine?
Oh, yeah.
Well, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just miss Christine.
I'm talking about there's a famous actress that's in like the Grinch, but...
Say, I'm an old woman, but I take care of myself in my...
I have a 40-year-old son.
Everybody thinks I'm his mom, that I'm his girlfriend.
Oh, well, you're you're very pretty. You look like a Barbie
She plays the mother in the movie. Yeah. Yeah, exactly. Okay, Christina. I almost got you. Hold on. I need to make
I had to make her joke
Her smile to make a little bit a little bit
And those are my real teeth, everybody.
I have all my teeth.
Oh, you're not like Crystal Marie.
OK, thank God.
Yeah, I have those are mine.
I have my own teeth.
And you have two halos because you have those glasses and those are your little halos
I got
Oh, my my son wears a shirt that says I'm with my mom. I keep telling him him and I should switch. He is like this old soul and I feel like I'm young at heart.
Okay, Christine, are you ready? Are you ready to see your your drawing?
I'm ready.
Ready? Okay, hold on. I need your name real quick. Christine C.A.
I love his art. He really makes great art.
My god, you know, it's from the heart. That's what matters
Art his art. I know but his art is from his heart. Oh
All you're trying to rhyme. Okay. He puts
At least you didn't rhyme with four because we're doing we're doing good. Okay. Well, no, because you put love in it
I did I did
Oh shit, huh? Hey, Christine. I'm gonna put you should get like a little stand by the beach and like, you know
Just drop people like that and do their third car. You think you know, like
I think you need to sign them all to encase someday. You know what I mean
Here's your picture, they paint for it, and at the end they get that, it's like...
Yeah, everyone's gonna make money except for me, that's gonna be my fate, okay.
So, Christine, okay, so you're ready, Christine, and I'm sorry...
Alright, tada!
I hope you softened my nose.
Yeah, I did, okay, so there's...
You do have a soft note, so there's Fawzi first.
So there's Fawzi.
That's looking good.
There's Fawzi.
Bob Fawzi or Fawzi, I don't know.
Okay, so let me see.
Why did Christine look like she had a sharp nose?
Where did Christine?
I don't know.
Oh, wait.
There she is.
Oh, look.
You've got my glasses perfect.
Yeah.
I mean, I do have a softer nose though.
I know.
It's cute.
It's very nice.
Thank you.
That was great.
So I keep reminding you of, like, you know, the five-year-old that just told you right
now.
It's like, wow, that's such a good job.
We love that.
Yeah.
I really like my job.
Maybe there's a reason to charm to them.
There was the eyes.
Yeah, those eyes.
can you draw a pentagram to it? I can draw a pentagram, hold on, let me see. No, no, don't put no
No, I'm not. I just want you to step around and open a portal. Oh
See that we're all going to hell Ziggy. Thanks
We're all done now
You all guys at the end of the world that was the final but the fight is that was I just
That run is free guys enjoy your enjoy your time on earth left, you know, it's gonna be
I don't know what she looks like, but
I just showed you what I looked like. That is me.
No, I know. Yeah. Okay. Well, I know he showed us what you looked like.
Oh, I'm going to say that is me when I clean up.
That was pretty funny.
No, because you changed your picture to Fawzi, so I think you might miss that.
Oh, yeah. I changed it to Fawzi.
Yeah.
You're quite an artist. We really appreciate that yeah, you know, it's it's from the heart
It is
And it's like, you know
Yeah, I'm gonna get a better I'm gonna go I didn't like
I'm improving my art you guys
You know when you do your book you can use this as like the illustrator
You just need to learn the soft and noses. That's the only thing
Everybody looks like they have a witch nose
Yeah, but yeah, I need to fix because I have a because I have a witch nose and so I like project it on to everybody but
This was the original beat as kiddies you can see the design is improved
Just like hello that one
Little witch house for the cats
What did you write on the side? Did you write fuck beta fuck beta? What does that say fuck? Did you curse me?
What is this the note?
He put it with that on you
Like whenever you were making whenever you were making the pentagram. Did you not I mean use a roller dude? It's okay
I'm gonna have to fly give me a break. I'm trying to host a buck
Mr. Magic
There's page 35 degree angles man
33 degrees okay, there's and there's Mr.
It might be and look and look there's a there's jokers stroking it
The Joker never changed. That's like that's gonna be the same Joker like that's just the same Joker
He has his arms and his big smile going towards me
So and then I see what I was like. Oh, so then here's Sam and see that's a pretty good salmon. I say it's like
You're here is
Apple Big Apple is a beer his expression. What is being it? What's stuck into his eye?
It's his hand. Oh, it's in a peace sign. Okay. Yeah, it's a little bit of a lobster club. He's just he's
Riding on top of them
On pages that already had writing on them that had a little space
So I'm going to read this poem that I wrote down in the whole poem, so I must have really
liked this poem. And this is by Robert Burns, and then I put Alex's picture after this poem.
So it says, there was a Bonnie lass, and there was a Bonnie lass, and a Bonnie lass,
and she loved her Bonnie laddie deer.
Till war's loud alarms, tore her laddie from her arms,
With money aside and his tear.
Oversee and over shore, where the cannons loudly roar,
He was still a stranger to fear, and not could him quail,
Or his bosom assail, but the Bonnie, his last, he loves so dear.
That's all he cared about. We're not
It didn't have picture picture of Alex I don't know I drew
If you ever saw like boogie woogie from a yeah, boogie woogie from a what the nightmare before yeah
Yeah, I get yelled at for being on your panel at 4 a.m.
Oh, yeah, that's you my son. He's like mom. What are you doing up at 4 a.m?
My friends are on mom you don't have friends
That's when I would have looked at him as a parent been like, what are you doing up at 4 a.m?
Turn that shit around on his ass. I woke him up, apparently. I probably did. I was probably screaming
He's like, yeah, likely story
He has an old soul he's probably sleeping by now even I swear to you we should swap ages
Okay, so before I ever ever did like one one illegal drug what I did was I got it
I got this there's this thing from Javalia coffee company
They said it's hey
We have the coffee with the month club or it's what's in you like, you know a lot of coffee every month
I don't know coffee maker, too. Yeah, I did it when I was like 12 years old and they sent me the coffee
So I was I was 12 brewing coffee with a TV in my room
Eventually meth was involved, but you know, this is my teenage years. It was it was very it was very wild, you know
I have I have only smoked pot once in my life and that was as a teenager and
I hardly ever drink
It's pretty cool
It's pretty cool. I'm an asshole without drugs. You got natural dopamine. That's what it is. That's why you always lay back, relax, cool and chill.
No, that was training. That was pure training for my job. Do you know what it's like to have people in a trauma room and people are dying, running around with their chickens?
No, there is some number of fucks can be assholes my homeboy junior when his dad was dying of lung cancer when we was younger
And dad was a straight fucking dick. Yeah, see I am very calm
I get everybody into place
They've listened to my voice and they follow my directions and we save lives
It probably didn't help to me and Junior used to steal some of his weed though. Yeah, I probably didn't help any
But that was your training. I promise you guys here's a secret about like if you steal people's drugs or you feel like you know
Like they're gunner or like a table legal gun
You can't they can't ever prosecute you because
Consider unclean hands and so they can never prosecute for it because we're doing something illegal in the first place
So I don't have weed is maybe we is not maybe
Finding when they caught a police officer life are still under drugs and they go to jail. I've seen all right
It happens all the time
I am very good self-control
California in California in California now that is legal. I wonder if the rules are changed
We are right
No, because it's still federal
Down the block I gave him $20, you know to give me some myth and he stole my $20 you can't do that shit
Because that's because it because judge Judy has actually had my math is where someone said they
So the person's weed and judges like well, you know, you have to have something in law called unclean or clean hands
We have to come if you're putting them you have to have not doing anything wrong in the first place
So that's why Alex can get away with stealing
15k kilograms of
Cocaine and trafficking and some becoming a cop because you know, it's like you know
They had unclean hands and so they couldn't we can never charge them for it
You think that's why Alex is always angry because somebody steals Alex weed
You know Alex has pure math. There's no weed involved
Alice Alice needs another like you blowy for
Alice Alice once I'll give you another you know if Alex takes a line of coke
He calms for a while, and then he needs to take another line
Constra why I mean it's like I mean he basically turned into you know, I'll tell you
we instead you after hours with Alex and
he would actually
In verse in a calm tone and talk about his life as we talked about that's why I have a special place for Alex because I know things about him
I would never ever disclose whether they were true or not
I don't know. I like Alex, but I still think he should play in traffic catch brain damage just to slow it down a little bit
You know what movie night with him he has watched movie night with us and he has been such a gentleman during movie night
I swear to you. Yeah, I know he is he can behave himself if you want that's why it's frustrating when I'm like Alex
You not say this in that
Get in again again. Okay, I'm gonna draw Vader right now. I'm gonna do a really quicky Vader Vader. Just a quicky, okay?
So the quicky okay Vader I got I got I know I have I've an idea of what I'm gonna do
You should charge like a cash off five dollars for each drawing again anymore after this guys
Anymore after this good. These are the free more. Yeah, if you want to if you want and I'll put it
I'll put it in the book too. It means like, you know, you want like a more advanced one yet
Yeah, and so there's that honey you said what what you said a pissing out some theater
There's nothing else you need to put on later when you put the wet on draw rick and morning
Oh, no, someone said something I need to draw something. Oh, it's t-rex arms. Okay, hold on
Drought the t-rex arms. Oh
I thought you said two right thumbs
T-rex arm or two rectums. Yeah, I'll just you wreck them still there's two buttholes
Nipples, okay Lord easy. What's that discord that you posted in the back, huh?
Okay, do you want to see it home? Oh, that's just mine. It's like a little private one. Just visit it, you know
Now with people, yeah
Okay, little Vader hold on. I'm gonna put the Sun in the moon next to you
I don't think it's a banana. It's banana. Don't it like God if you also look like a female
You're like a really cute like a wolf woman Vader. I don't know if you're a woman or not either turn like that
I don't know a little bit t-rex arms
I'll make a little hell's all those lines. Well, I'm getting a flag in the arms
See this there's a flag see that's flag right there. Those are her arms. They're t-rex arms
So she's that's Vader. That's it's Vader. Yeah, I don't know. He's a guy though
Hair in front of their face
Then there's a kind of like kind of like JT's
That is Vader. Are you are you rain? I don't know. I don't know. I mean there is a guy
Rain is a guy
Are you a guy Vader or you a guy Vader please tell us cuz I think you know
Says Lord Vader on it. I drew a donut. There's only one person. I will mispronounce one person
Elijah
No, and he's me and he's the he I don't care what he says
Oh, no RuPaul. Yeah, RuPaul RuPaul's free obviously
Lordy diamond
Oh, oh
That is a key this in I can't I don't want to get no, I think I'm like
The same
My clothes want my clothes Peter my clothes
I'm sorry. I thought it was JT. I'm sorry Bader. Is that you? I thought I was JT's like girl
I don't know. Look, I kind of drew the kind of really cute ears
Kind of I'm trying to draw the Darth Vader's helmet and it turned out to be the wolf man
I don't know guys. It's a cute wolf girl, but I don't think that's me.
It's cute. It looks cute. I don't know. I thought that's a cute picture, but I don't think yeah
Well, Bader didn't donate. So
Whatever. Think of what they get. Think of what they get. You got a free drawing
Beggars can be choosers. Yeah, I mean it's a come on guys. I have one more real life
Then I have to go
Oh, you're sexy a beta like that. They just said they just they're sick
I was trying to be I was trying to do the dark dark Darth Vader mask
But then it turned into like cute like furry like the perfectly like the hair is all perfect
There here. This is me. Oh, look at there's there's beta. Oh, that's a beta because I won't I won't add a draw
Oh, that would be too complicated draw. You look is that a gorilla state? Oh my gosh. What's going on? Oh, that's our Darth Vader
Draw you with huge tits. Okay. I'll draw Vicky Vicky. Are you gonna you want to send in the cash that Vicky?
I'm gonna draw you a big
Vicky I'm just gonna imagine. Let me see. Okay, Vicky. Okay. You're it's like you're like one of those mysterious people. Okay, Vicky
Vicky wants huge tits. Just make it all tits. Okay. Your wish make sure you put the nipples no milk
Oh my god. Yeah, it's definitely diamonds. I don't have room. I don't have room enough on the
Sorry a page for that. I am in a mood tonight in case you can't tell
Yeah, I don't know if I oh my gosh, I made you cross eyes. Oh my gosh
I don't think you've ever heard me speak like this. Have you?
You're doing fine. You're not doing anything wrong. You're just
The case is draw with huge oh my god, I just I just made your nipples hairy and I also don't have room for your
But
Enjoy your drawing. I'll put your name on your stomach
Let's see K why okay Vicky kind of look it kind of looks like this
I'll give you like a little cross on your neck so you're like you know make sure you put nipples, okay?
Nipples are important
Wow, oh, there you go nipples with eyeballs. Okay, we're good
Please
I don't know. I didn't have room for many much more besides
Why is it? Why is it here? All right, Mars. Well, the nipple hair is because I need an eyelash
eyelashes look great on
Did you like it?
Yes
You can put some nair on the hair or put a lady, a Venus ladies chick across it and it'll be gone before you know it, okay?
We don't like, we don't like hair on nipples. Oh, look I got it right guys! Lord Vader's a female. How did I guys, how did I know this?
How did I know this? How did I keep you?
I'll be back guys, sorry.
Lord Vader, Lord Vader's a female.
Never mind, I have no clue. Oh, I'll be right back. Okay.
Yeah, like I said, I can read energy. That's why I can you draw yourself. Obviously, I draw a
Drew was a female because they're gonna do a self-portrait
I mean, it's like, I mean, I'm sorry. You see 40 diamonds picture you like
Good. Yeah, that's good. Where's the piano? Well, I see I need to go like this one here. This will complete at home
Like that oh
Yeah, that's good. Yeah, perfect. Yeah a good job site and I love your perfectionist. Yeah, where are the balls?
I don't know. And I drew, oh I drew Nick tonight. There's Nick.
Oh, he brought up, he brought up Penis next time.
He drew, he brought up, he was going on more.
He had a big fake Penis.
I mean he was trying to, he's a draw me and then he put on a big, big Penis.
Just change the D, into the D run and just make it dick.
Yeah. And I drew him like, I drew him like that and I said, Nick.
Nice. Nice. Good job.
Master pieces. I can't wait till you open up your own gallery
Our gallery. This is Vicky again guys. This is Vicky. I'm jealous of Vicky's boobs
Yeah, me too
Me too
Um, Dougie, can I draw you can I draw Dougie? I'm gonna draw Dougie. Dougie. You have to send me like a hundred dollars to draw
I'm just kidding guys. I'm just kidding guys
Sweet pea wants one we sweet pea sweet pea said be no you won't do mine. Come on. Sweet pea is like
What's wrong with with a Doug's eyes right there?
This Dougie
Let me get the, okay, there's the top teeth.
And where's the bottom teeth?
I don't see a big, big oval gap in them.
Oh my God, what's going on?
Okay, let me, okay.
Okay, I mean, make that bigger.
Hold on, make that bigger.
Oh, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Guys, I got it, okay, I got it.
Okay, Doug, are you ready?
Ready dog. I didn't see there is our hair. Oh, I don't know. I think it's like a little ear
I'll give you like I'll give you like a little bit of character. Okay. I don't know
I'll give you a couple hairs in your chin too. I'm gonna have a little hair in your head. Okay. Ready for it
Yay
Versus glasses
Well, look at his his eyes
Your face looks so unsure and disturbed at your own drawing
I don't know it's I don't much he's like a blowfish. I don't know it's like I don't know where I don't know where it begins and ends
Dingo. Oh, you got the wrong drawing. I guess I'm going blind guys. I'm going blind. Okay. Dingo got a bonus draw
I said it as I was drawing Dougie
No, I drew Dougie. I was trying to I'd have to draw the situation or something and I did draw Dougie though
I did draw the other day. Dingo likes it
You like to dingle there you go. There's another day
Oh, yeah
He sounds like yeah, that's really good. Yeah, it's perfect. I see the essence. Yeah, did you see pause me?
This Christine's dog. I love that one. It's so cute. Oh
That's really cute
There's LD and his dog
Oh god
Dolphin that kind of captures the essence a little bit of D. Yeah, I heard a really bad service
My dog you see the picture of my dog. Can you draw him? That's savage
Hold on a second. Oh
Oh
No
Sweet peace sweet peace that please please. Can you draw a sweet pea?
Yes, we feel you see sweet peace that you hate her
No, I love sweet, but it's we I can't really see sweet. Can you come on panel just for a minute so I can see I
Eyes I can I mean I hear I can draw like this, but it's not gonna make you like happy, but
It's like it's like you know you like you want a sweet pea. Oh my gosh. I can draw like
It's the thought that counts, you know.
And it kind of looks like this.
And you have to like put it in like garlic sauce and like I'll put a little garlic sauce over there for you for you.
And you can dip it in there.
Dip it in there.
There's a whole bag full of them, okay.
Okay, is this sweet peas?
Okay, I don't know.
There's a sweet pea. I think it's good. Yeah. Yeah. And it says sweet peas and there's a whole box of that. Perfect.
I can't. And then you can have like a little dish chew right there. But you didn't put any boops for her.
Hold on. I'll put boops in there too. Hold on. Okay. There. They're not as big though. There's boops there.
Yeah
Octopussy I mean it's like all the octopus parts. There's all these like arms. I mean, what's what is that sauce on you put?
That was that looks exactly like her. Good job. Good job
You're adorable thank you
Hello, can you hear me now?
Yes
Thank you
Anybody else guys, I'm kind of tuckered out on on the art for a second, but if you want to draw if you want to draw into that guys
We send a nice donation, but I might even I might even autograph
Incentive to you or it will be in my book one of the two pretty good stuff
If she wanted you she could have you hold on I want to be in the middle PSA in the pod
What's going on you like the honey sauce, okay? Oh, yeah, okay. I was really just these sweet peas, okay guys
Oh
Sweet he was the name of Popeye and olive oils
Done they named him sweet pea. Oh, really? Yeah, but he was anything but sweet
And you know
Popeye was pop I did live up to his name and
She was skinny as a twig. She was always like, you know going to like meet Bluto for beers and stuff like that
Yeah, Papa was that Papa's not trying to like, you know save the day and like, you know look out for their son and then
Olive oil is out
Blue dough they're at the hamburger place and then wimpy's they're asking for like a loan and the burger like every day
It's every I don't know guys. Are we living are we living an episode of Popeye?
It's asking them lies new character on lock guys. You got my new character. I don't know finally it finally happens
Spanky's crying. I remember it's spunky not spanky. I used to have a cat named spanky actually
I had a cat named spanky when he ran away. Why does the wimpy guy didn't always have a
What didn't he always eat burgers? I know but he always he never had money for the burger
He's always asking for a loan and he'll pay back Monday
Then when Monday comes he's nowhere to be seen and then he repeats the cycle over hoping you'll forget
Go as you remember you have this wimpy this little wimpy receipt log
Some day you're gonna cash that in. Okay. Some day you're gonna cash it
Popeye's fake news psyche didn't give me muscles spinach in it. No, it did it
You know, I mean iron's fine
It didn't have actual like iron like people thought it would give them powers of metal. Oh, I'm sorry guys. Here we go
No. Oh, here we go. Wimpy's a dead bean out paying back his loans. I know you know
We obviously but aren't we all like a little bit of a wimpy sometimes there's like some kind of deal
We put off paying sometimes. Well, we'll get around to it eventually. I'm sure but it's like, you know
Today's not today
I haven't even opened the can without the strengths without he just would pop them open without any
Either like yeah, he was pretty muscular and then when you have them you just can't even yeah
I was weed for sure
He didn't wait too much work
He overworked his biceps. I mean he was skinny as olive oil the rest of him was just the skinny as olive oil
But then he like would work his biceps and they were they were big
Then he had this really weird look at it. He like had that look on his face
Or is that he and you're actually and he just had to eat this can spin it can spin is like the worst thing ever
Disgusting guys, you know, he has these frozen spinach or fresh there. I mean it can spin it. Oh
Talking about this guest. Oh my god. Come on. Do I hear enough? Hello?
No, I didn't everyone's good
LD look at my
Look at her drawing. Yeah, Vicky. They want to see the drawings again. We can show the drawing. They're Casey be there here
How are you guys doing? Yeah, guys?
It's good. So I have my rest of my I have one more beer left. I think yeah
I want more beer guys need in my house is clean out the clean my bathroom and my kitchen like spotless
Yeah, did you did you clean it or did you pay?
They said this thing they're like just don't let us do it because they're like and then it's like
This and then they're just like this did it and they
Say fairy is a what'd you do? Just silly catch up on some
Yeah, yeah, it was a it was a it was like mumples stills and came and like you know clean my floor and you know
I do know their name, but I'm not going to misuse
Rumpel Room. Get the razor out of the closet.
You've been, hold on.
Get your ass out of the closet.
My ass out of the closet.
Oh, Bader's in the closet.
Bader, are you gay? It's okay.
It's okay to be gay.
We're all at least a little bit bisexual
in these parts.
I lost to you for myself. Oh JT is here. Oh my god JT. Oh my god the mastermind is JT
Do you see your girlfriend like it? Do you know JT? I think you're perfect for I know it is Vader. I hope hopefully Vader is
Gosh, what's his girlfriend's name? I'm so sorry
Okay, I forgot but you know what JT anyway, I
Love her though. Okay, JT this this is this though JT is
Lord Vader
Raid it's her name is rain her name is rain. Okay, that's that right there is Lord Vader
And she has Tyrannosaurus Rex arms
Some might say they're a little bit cockroach like some might say it looks like a veil some might say it looks like a face
Well, look where we're like just slice of avocado on the side like what is that?
Well, I was trying to draw
The sun the moon as usual
They come out looking like an avocado and banana, but yeah
It's the same it's the same effect
Basic idea same basic idea, right?
Okay, there you are too far see yes, I like that yes
The guy I used to I actually won an art contest when I was like, I think I'm like third or fourth
I think it was fourth grade and
We had a yard duty and her name was MC. You're your sexy. You're beautiful werewolf. You were yarding and MC
And MC was like this like she was kind of like, I don't know if you guys know Tracy X, you know that
She was like, hey, what's up?
She was like, they're kind of like personality where,
and the kids were kind of like scaring her,
but she was doing a good job of a home.
Oh, here we have Dougie Doug.
What's up, Dougie?
I better turn my volume up, right?
Hi.
What are you doing?
You sound perfect.
How do you make something?
So you know, you know, Bita, right, Dougie?
You know, do you know Bita and you know, Casey, do you?
I've seen Bita kitties, yeah.
Um, I don't want to beg you from, um, Todd Glofinger's troll.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah, Proud. I've seen him around.
I don't know that we ever had much of a conversation,
but I'm sure we've said hello in classic, you know what I mean?
Yeah, and it's incidentally it is it is Melissa's birthday today. And so if you guys do when I go over there
You can say oh, it's a birthday tree. Yeah, June 30
Who KZ is
KZ KZ is a friend of the chat to he's I think he's been Rhode Island or something Massachusetts or something like that
He's like East. Can you tell me why KZ's dog's eye is like staring like is that just I know KZ KZ
It kind of is like
I was going to draw a picture, but it's like, it scared me too much.
It was like, it was like a full screen.
You're drawing goggles.
I think it's a doctor.
No, what do you mean?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't easy.
Well, what's wrong with your dog's eyes?
Are they swollen?
They're completely swollen.
You're a pattern.
I'm like, all healthy.
I don't like it. I don't like it.
Yeah
Amy's been with me since the beginning we know it's weird, but the guy who the guy like speed of the guy with his name
his name is
What's the guy know the guy his name is Carl or something he was here the other night and he was like
Like oh, he's like everybody. I'm starting a live right now come right away to my
And he's like oh, but I'm not trying to take away like he and anything. Oh, who's this oh he near and Jamie's Cowboys
Oh, I want you to demand these special friends
But I'm not trying to take them away from you say I was like, okay
Don't worry. Don't worry. He has
some guy that I used to talk to
over the years. He's trying to
he's trying to make me like uh
Jamie was like she was mad and
she was always saying hi to
everybody. Like Jamie was the
best. It is. Thank you. Spunky
has now been called Spanky.
I didn't get to the west coast
and so I just don't get that
The wild wild west. Hello person. How are we doing guys?
Person is a real person actually person is my nightbot programmer
That's the reason my nightbot when you type exclamation point above plug and but hole it will say something personalized back at you
It's like either different. Who's there? Hey, what's up?
All the different people
Are you telling me what to do?
Ilzia
He said you pronounce it.
Is that how you say it?
They came out and they I like he'll join we are his they came on without that underwear
pronounces the J himself. I think where is the comment?
Join it
I know I can't help but I think it's I think you what I want to hear
Ilya
Didn't sink the oh, there's a little bit of Jane. Yeah, no one might be on there and no one does not like to be stunkin
I mean, it's like, you know, he's having a bad idea. It's the first time I've been off the end with them
Lager has been better for them
Lager has been better hair than say better hair than me. Oh my god my hair
Whoever whatever, I don't care if it's
Human skin mask that has Korean and foreskins all of you know absorbed on it. That's why he looks so good
Okay, I'm just all natural. You have to put up with me. Okay. No, it's because he's so short
Well, I would rather have my penis three inches longer and maybe a foot taller than be as good looking as him and be shorter than him.
You're actually, you guys are a couple.
I heard a person, Ellen said that.
That's a compliment. Remember in the beginning everybody was like, psyche looks like blogger, remember?
Everybody was like, who's that guy blogger?
They look like brothers.
And be it was actually said oh, so psyche's the good-looking version of I liked I like when she said that but yeah
I know he's like a little cute and like you know
It's like if I get kicked off of anywhere, they're like, oh
You are a blogger come oh give them another shit
Oh, they're so sweet. They're so cute. Oh, they have curls. Look at their eyes. There's a beautiful eyes. Oh, he has Korean foreskins, you know, radiating from his skin.
You know, I know it. I know. It's better than mine, but I still, I still, I have my...
beauty cream. What do you think?
Look at yourself. Korean. Does it make a difference?
Psyche, thanks for having me back up, man. Who's the uh the chick
like right below you? I think so, Samantha. Who are you talking about? The
chick? That's that's Dougie Doug. That's not a chick. That's a
I said, I'm trying to be just like, hey, hey, hey, Ziggy, Ziggy, are you ready?
Ziggy, are you ready?
It's that here. You got a nice
Yeah
It throws people off your you know because you have this beautiful hair
You know me too people always say oh psyche, you know, you're a beautiful woman. I'm like, hey guys guys
I'm actually I'm actually a biological male. I know guys. I know it's a shock, but I know I
Know I have great hair my great skin
I just like you know, I don't wear a lot of makeup and I look I always look like that has but yeah
I'm a biological male. I'm thinking of transitioning back to my original sex. You know as soon as I
And I always had a great head of he had until I was 28 and I shaved my head never grow back the same
You were 28 you shaved your head and you had never grew back
Yeah, that's an awful story man
My god, I just supposed to go back even better if you shave your hair
It all disappeared in there
I'll do what I mean to shave off my eyebrows for a hundred dollars. I was like, well, what if they don't grow back and I look like
Anything I can put it my name is a cray and I can it can use a Crayola and just like draw them on and I was like well
That would look ridiculous
Yeah
Okay, I have you ever seen like those videos of the women who will get like the tattooed eyebrows and they're like gone wrong
Well, I see people with tattooed eyebrows
Yeah, well, I mean I had roses with them and stuff. They're actually really good
I mean they they just are a supplement to their regular makeup. They'll put makeup over on stuff
People the tattoo the tear drops to their cheek
Well, that means that they're Mexican and they've they've lost a homie and they're poor and yeah when I grew up
I always had the understanding that the that the the tear drop kill somebody was significant to a death
Yeah
They caused it sometimes there was like knock off. I mean it depends on
If you had it for no reason that was like it was a
It was
He me I tattooed
Initial tattooed on my arm. I didn't put it on my face. You know what I mean? It's like
yeah, I
Don't get why people like to tattoo like their face. Yeah
This generation of kids they they're gone crazy with the face tattoos and then I'm telling you when they grow up
They're gonna regret it
Yeah, they think the marriage like like like native New Zealanders
It's kind of like okay, so my one of my friends she has her above like she already has her eyeliner tattooed
You know like so she doesn't have to wake up and put on eyeliner like you know like her cat eyeliner
She has her lip like tattooed so I know a few women who have that too. Yeah
Yeah, it makes it more convenient I guess and just putting on makeup every day
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like that, you know, it's like it just cuts down on the time a little bit.
It also gives a good sense for the eyebrow to put it on.
That's the thing, like, I think, um, and, you know, every species, like the animal species,
nature, the men are always better looking. Like, if you look at the lion, like male lion versus the female lion.
like men just wake up. You don't really have to get ready to have lunch with them.
Well, I don't, especially in the birds, especially in the birds and these male birds like the peacock and then the birds of the Amazon and some of the ducks.
Yeah.
They will, the males actually, you know, versus part of the female birds are shit.
Yeah, the females are great.
to comply. To plant the seed. Almost every species is like that. The animals will take
it through sometimes, but there's always a courtship that goes on between a male and
a female, no matter what species. And the female always decides no matter what species.
Well, yeah, and it's like but also thinking about that had the power the female
Human to human female has in the race and like as to who gets food who gets fed or not
There's a lot of there's a lot of homeless people out there that if there are certain women that we're like saying
Make sure that they have food. I mean, it's like, you know, there could be like everything
Everything a man does is pretty much for a woman
No women women women you control they mean they feed you when you're when you're a baby they can feed you when you're an adult
You know as they give you know, it's a if a woman's not helping you get food if you're not getting your own food
You're pretty much raised by
More women. Yeah in our game
This is a
Tupac be careful. I'm gonna get you accomplished. I'm just kidding. Yeah, no copyright. Yeah
Female buttholes can look tasty. Oh, yeah. Why are you being so disgusted a male?
Like compare
Show you two buttholes. Are you gonna know who the difference? How are you gonna know guys?
If anybody you know the difference in two buttholes
Yeah
Who's the zoo or bloggers on the other one is blown out like a balloon one is
Happily blazed and we can it's kind of like at the fair and you like do that like little like you spray with the water
With a gun and you fill the balloon. I kind of want to do that with their buttholes and see who wins
Oh my god
Bye, I got it. Bye. Yeah
So hey, hey, there's monkeys hairless. No, that's great
I mean it doesn't be great to be hairless, but it's like I don't know. I'm afraid of like a little
Five o'clock shadow or something like that when it comes in you have to get there. It's the oh, I have a few
There's a few hairs you didn't get in my
asshole
Okay
Yeah, they're not really care
Imagine these people they bleach ass. Hey when I was in my 20s. I always kept that area kept
The clean
But how do you even see it? I mean, it's like the
Electric raise us strictly for downstairs and I would end down spread them and
Anybody help you or do you just do it yourself?
You're a guy a guy in the locker room you never said hey, hey, but bro, can you come get my give me in the back?
No, okay, never mind
Hey, a lot of fragile man like, okay, hold on.
Butthole, yeah, the butthole.
Butthole, butthole.
Casey's squatting over a mirror to shave his gaper.
Oh my God, that's a little bit extreme.
Spunky.
Listen, I have been, most people have squarroves.
They don't lie, dude.
Don't splint.
Most people have just walked over a mirror
at one point in their life.
I know.
Well, it's better to put a mirror down there yourself and have somebody following you around with mirrors in their shoes. That's for sure, right?
Some dingle Barry
Watch
Come on, we're we're talking about
Take a shower with a washcloth and a bar of soap
Yeah, clean it just clean yourself. It ain't that and guys you're not fully clean unless you're just fully clean
Okay, you use a washcloth
Advertisement
It's such a dark psyche
I'm like, I'm like, I'm like,
I gotta imagine you're like a new person. I found your channel and they walk in they're like, what are they talking about?
Is it the channel they talk about?
You know hygiene right now, we'll be talking about there's something in a few minutes
Yeah, it's anal high guys. I think June 30th is anal hygiene awareness day guys. Make sure you
Know you keep it nice and clean down there
I have two booties
You got a big day that young lucky mother fucker
If you don't I've used it
My life, but I've never owned one and I wish I had though
Yeah, nowadays it's you can buy the attachment and just attach it to the toilet now. Yeah, that's what I have
That's what makes you my water right up right up to your intestines
Yeah, you don't need to go for your bidet anymore. Oh, yeah, you can just buy that. Yeah, look it up yourself
Yeah, you could like a blood washer or something very handy. It's very handy. It works perfectly
I don't care one works pretty well, too
I call it my I call my I call my buddy not my b-day call my buddy. Yeah
The the the the showers the shower head always get attached for me too. I need to be able to take the shower head off
Attachable, yeah
Detachable
Detachable bobo penis anybody
I remember that
Dennis Dennis
Oh, Hannah adores me. Okay. I don't know about that. They at home. It's a baby person. Hey, hey Trix. Hi
God, he's gone. Where'd Goddy go? Where'd Goddy go?
Yeah, hey dog
doesn't so much but
I'm comfortable with all this talk about hygiene or something. Yeah, I'm sorry. I always just talking about like, you know
Make your help make make that little
Nisht is next to God. He's so nice. You're right
But you know Doug has the Doug has a show but Doug is like better at like
Moderating his his panel better than me because you know what he already has Goddy and JT already banned from his panel
They can be
What channel
No, no, no, I said you I said your panel not your channel. I said they're in your chat, but they're not on your panel
I've had to so got it off my panel. Absolutely. Okay. I don't know the JT's ever come on my
But um, no God he gets thrown off because he don't obey the rules
Come on like when you were a mod when you were a mod for Todd Goldfinger you banned me for no reason
I'm a good friends with Todd. I'm a vision on what's up. I was like you're a mod
But he's like, okay come back and then you modded me
Nothing I just said hey Todd. What's up like a little joke like
That gets strict about that he's strict. I mean, you know, he's an Ecuador, right?
Uh, he actually joined my panel like a month and a half ago. He was like, um
He was like two different he joined two different times
He once I mean joined with like a female. He's like i'm getting married with her this and that and then
And then next thing, you know, I think he's getting married though. But no, no, no, what on the french girl?
It was like a mexican like
I mean, uh, he's in ecuador. Todd. Yeah, I drove him to the airport in january
Oh, that's cool. I like Todd. It's really good record. I don't think I ever banned anybody from Todd's channel
You did it was a long time ago. That was like
People out right, but I don't think I banned anybody
Todd in every no, he's gonna try and stay there. He's got his visa extended
And he's trying to work, he's trying to produce a program, an online, like a YouTube show or something shit. I don't know.
Yeah, cool.
Yeah, Tom comes up with a lot of ideas, and yeah.
The French girl went by the wayside months and months ago.
Oh yeah, she was extremely, extremely good-looking, but you could tell she was crazy. It just set the crazy eyes.
Yeah, she was pretty though
I'm really good looking woman
He would pull like really really good when he was on the Alisa show
Some Russian girl came up and she was like I think you're so hot and sexy and Alisa got really mad
She's like you think he's hot you think he's sexy
She was like putting them down. He's like what do you mean? And she's like are you serious like you really think he's hot
It was the funniest issue. No, I think you're hot
Most women think Todd's a very good-looking guy
That's what I hear from all the women. I mean, I look at him like a brother, but yeah, yeah
Extremely good-looking guy for some reason
Hello again page. Hello. How are you?
Hi page. I'm well. I was thinking about
I was just taking a hoot to you when you talked to me and I couldn't answer you
Look what we got guys. Well, look it up tonight
How are you doing? I have a question for Dingle since he's been only been around for a while
Don't I know you by another name already Dingle, right?
You're like somebody else with it now with a different name. I
I'm just wondering, because that's not good.
Busted. Dingles busted. I think Dingles busted.
Dingles says no, but we'll see.
No, there's like a lot of people with Dingle names.
There's a Dingle Berry Fresh name too.
No? Okay. He said no.
Yeah, Tennessee is kind of taking people's words for it,
but we do know that, you know, people can buy it also.
So, you know, we're going to...
How are you the page man lick her? Oh, yeah, what what does that mean? I'm all right, Bita. How are you?
I'm good. I'm good. You sound tired. Did you work today?
No, I thought I had to work, but then I realized I work next Monday, not this Monday. So I would have went in for no reason. Oh
Okay, well, that's you
Like when it's cool and it said like classes dismissed. That's cool. It was like he went there, but then at least the other day. Oh
Yeah
Yeah, I saw you live for a little bit. I had to go do some stuff, but I came in there
I was like, oh, there's a pretty page doing her thing
I just was happy everybody liked the message Nick. What are you doing Nick Nick Nick?
Nick said he wanted to have me draw him today. He said oh draw me and then he put up an enormous
inflatable penis balls and pubic hair. I had to end the stream because it was too it was too
realistic for the for the algorithm. I was afraid my I was gonna lose my show because he was putting
Yeah, they don't like that. They don't they don't and it's like what?
Johnson didn't wear long sleeve shirts, but this is a different Nick Johnson
Well, he's he's the guy he looks like a Jamie Kennedy. They could Jamie Kennedy experience their mouth was
Yeah, you know Rizzler. Yeah, Rizzler's here. Yeah, Rizzler. I know
Several different chats like a lot of person you love trivia
Guys we have golden girls trivia coming up tonight. By the way
I don't know shit about golden girls like that
My team you don't know
Comment knock on my door is that one? That's not golden girls, man. That's okay. Never mind. Um
Thank you for being a friend, and thank you for traveling the world and back again, your heart is yours, and your friends have a comfort on us, and if you feel a party, invite everyone, you will see the biggest.
If you see from me and I think you let me up. I'll come back again sometime. Okay. I love you. I love you always welcome here
Thank you so much before I just have a question. Yeah, and of course, you know, I'm straight
I'm married and whatnot, but I think the most gay man that I know actually like golden girls
Is that that seemed like a fair thing to say because I never thought I never thought that show was great
They were a little bit funny
It was
It was it was written by gay men all you know golden girls
also
I do have like my grandmother also didn't watch it. She's like they bought like Betty White and
And so your gay men also know that their grandmothers and stuff they really have a connection to me that it's camp
Whatever yeah, can't be yeah, but yeah water keep flamingos. Yeah, yeah game in love Madonna and
Now I was a Gaga
She's a lady. God has a big one. Yeah, guys. What's your story?
It was an all right show and fairly funny and I would get a laugh, but I never I never thought it was great
You know
There's other one that she mentioned. She's married with children. The best one ever
Good night
Like we have we have both that we have both terror destroyer and the daughter of truth in the chat
And so guys excited. What is terror search that I always want to look at my boyfriend's test
For crime recently should I marry him when he wakes up from his crime or his coma or marry?
He's identical twin brother whose testicles are pretty good shape
I don't know, go for the better set of balls, I don't know, but go for the better heart actually.
You know, if you're missing a ball, you know, I think your heart can compensate for a ball.
Yeah, and then you can go on, but one night.
Yeah, Tom Green has won penis, or has won testicles since, you know, he was 30 years old, so, you know, he's...
I know, I watched the Golden Globe movie.
He's filmed that whole process, too, I remember.
I watched the Golden Girls. I know it's funny. I like the episode, but I don't know that that well, like for, you know, I just like, okay, so they're like five of them living in Florida and then four or five.
They're like plants, you know, she's like this light, right? And then Rose is like the dingbat. And then the other one was like the kind of like controlling nag, you know, the tallest one.
and then the little mom the mom yeah Dorothy mom she was like all spicy and wasn't putting on
this shit she had toured a certain generation she was like Sicilian she was like you know from
like Italy she like all these mafia connections and talks you know you know she still would look
up with guys and shit she still had like yeah yeah yeah because you know they were all of them
were because all their husbands died yeah they were all kind of like bloody for their age
I put it out there for emotionally and innocently, but yeah.
Hey, at least Terror Destroyers coming with some unique material tonight.
Usually they come in with like just repeating stuff that people said in the chat.
Now they're actually coming with jokes. I like it better. It's an improvement.
They're a good job, Terror Destroyers. Maws don't ban Terror Destroyers.
They're not trying to ruin Terror. They're not going to ruin it.
There was some fire. There was a fork.
Yeah, but you know...
Didn't they range from like age 50 to like age 80?
Yeah, and Betty White was actually the oldest one, and then Sophia or Estelle Gatti was actually the youngest one out of all of them, but they played the oldest and the youngest, I think, you know, pretty interesting.
And then that Dorothy one would always get annoyed at Blanche because she would try to steal and flirt with her boyfriends
She was just like oh god not again, you know
Yeah, and then and then Dorothy would all I or
Rose would always have a stir about St. Olaf. She's like she's for sure
They come this Dutch community from from St. Olaf, Minnesota, and I always have the stupidest stories
Yeah, oh urban banner flutin, you know lost the country fair and I didn't know the
Balloon flew away with the pig inside of it and everyone
And I said oh my gosh roses are done. Yeah
Doors who give me I haven't slept for days because that would
Be too long miss head bird. Okay. Good terrorist or maybe somebody else's quote, but you're so good
How's everyone doing? I left my nice background going tonight. It's 8 33
I'm trying to quit smoking cigarettes, but I think I might have to get one more crack
I'll just try to like have it last the week
It's so expensive. And it's like I don't even like smoking and
I need to fix my bike too. I need to get my bike fixed
Unfortunately, it's not doing well right
Mod it's it's mod
The other was on Modge, the show from the 70s.
It's big women's lib character.
And then that's what she was famous from other shows.
Betty White was of course a Mary Tyler Moore
and she also had the Betty White show.
Rue McClanahan, I don't know, she was kind of new.
I don't know, or at least not a big actress,
a well-known actress, now it was a still getty,
but a perfect casting.
For some of my bike the bike is not charging right now, so I need to have it service to get it charging
It's not I gotta do charger to I'm gonna try to put that in but it's just not charging on the one I have
It's so it's not gonna charge when it dies. It's kind of scary
So also I did take off with the chain still though the lock on it and then it got kind of tangled in my
Keep it's tangled my stuff. It's fine, but it's like
I need to get it cut off.
Betty White and Ruth Kenan were both in Mama's Family too.
Yeah, Mama's Family, they had Vicki Lawrence
as Carol Burnett was involved.
Goodbye, knee pain.
Hello, penis shortening surgery.
Oh no, oh no.
One ciggy tastes 20 minutes of your life.
So they say, yes, yes, they do say that, right?
I bought some of the cow brain with a cow brain or cow testicles. I don't remember. I bought one of the two. I bought like these like these like supplements from the liver king.
Have you followed what's going on with that guy? Like he challenged O'Rogan, went live stream into his Austin when he lived, he lived, got arrested, got out on bail.
Streamers went to go see him. He started a lot of treatment and talked to shit again
And you know he might get arrested again
Well, he needs to go back to his own. I mean he's making guys making millions of dollars
Why go bother Joe Brogan like they just leave Joe Rogan alone at this point, you know guys
I can't be really concerned about
uh too many other streamers right now because I have my own stream and so it's like that's a whole different universe like yeah so
they have some pretty shit going on like he's making money the alpha male universe is crazy right now
he's making money and it's like they both are in kind of a space I mean it's like yeah trans cows
Ginger that's that's the alpha male universe like it. There's some wild shit happening over there right now
Well, I mean it's like Joe Rogan is like Joe Rogan himself might be an AI at this point
I mean, it's like, you know, it's just like his voice is just everywhere. You know, you can uh
You know, it's just like he's the he and he might be a trans transgender seal
We don't really know if he's not like a female to male. I don't know. Has anyone proven this
Um, let me know in the chat if you've heard that they can go 33 the final until I love that movie. So I like
My sex the way I
Play baseball one-on-one with as little dribbling as possible. Well, there we go Frank Drablin
His name is dribble to three pieces. No, but I'm guys
Don't let flirty
Make you ice cream. I
mean nothing personal, but it's like
Unless you like that kind of like Greek flavor. There we go. KZ. Are you here?
Yeah, yeah, sorry. Yeah, I think yeah. Yeah
Drops sorry to you. Oh, sorry to you. Yep. We're back. Hey Joe Rogan is a real male male man
I don't know if you're hurt is he's a he's a routine and Joe Rogan goes way back
He's even from the state that I'm from so he's a real person
Well, have you ever noticed some of the most prolific feminists were men and some of the most
prolific masculinus unlike you say our women you know it's like it's kind of
like we got both right did he just tell me next to let 30 diamonds make you
ice cream yes I did say that but you know it's not a mean way it's just like
you know I just like you know I don't know if that will be safe to just so this
yeah just like you know
Goodbye some mint chocolate chip and just have have that instead in the spirit of spirit of eating ice cream, but
For God's sake don't get what's your favorite kind? You know what? I've been on I've been eating the cherry Garcia like this
This is the best. I
Like the I like my bed and Jerry's. I mean I like the I like the
Brownie I like the graham cracker. I like that with the all around the world or something keep your coffee black
Page are you awake?
I'm awake. I'm right here listening.
Okay, okay. Cookies and cream is always a good go-to too. That's always a fun thing.
I do like it. You can't go wrong with that.
Yep, I'm all about the chocolate on chocolate on chocolate on chocolate. You know what I mean? Oh, I can't do
And chocolate whipped cream. Yeah, you can have you have plenty of chocolate
I don't think you guys like white chocolate though. Yeah, some people like like love chocolate, but then like white chocolate
White chocolate great. My grandmother loves white chocolate
I think it's good on there. The only thing I like white chocolate in is the Hershey's
They're called hugs. They're they're like white chocolate and chocolate mix together. Those are good
But otherwise, I don't care for white chocolate. It's a little bit strong
It's not like paid paid fellow for chair. Oh, I know I so I get worried sometimes and I say are you okay?
It's just he's like, I'm seeing right here. I'm fine. I'm like, okay
I've been on a kit-cat kit. Yeah, yeah, yeah, well, she had kick-ass you like kick-ass
Give me a break
Give me a break break me off piece that KZ bar. Hey, Marcy likes strawberry cheesecake ice cream
Oh, I like that too. I'd love strawberry. She's the ice cream. I have the teeth. She's actually right here, too. I
Used I usually love desserts. I'm a very big dessert person
Yeah, guys, are we having fun? I have this other beer. What do I keep like like for the fifth time?
I thought I got up and got my beer
And I think you're drinking bears or you drinking that the hard liquor drinks like the hard boot of Ram
Booty ranger is nine percent alcohol. So it's like it's a hard beer. Yeah
Drinking bears and trackable. Oh
I'm always drinking beer. I don't know what you're talking about. I
Drink like
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Yeah
If you call the fury, uh, it's like, uh,
You're just not gonna ask me because I'm a girl or what?
Wait, okay, Paige, tell me your opinion.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh, see, I didn't even see it.
When you're drinking, Paige, you don't drink beer, do you?
I do.
That's right, you do.
I mostly drink beer. It's all I drink, really, and water.
I'm sorry, Paige, Paige, I'm sorry.
I don't, I mean, it's really like,
And I like, and I like PBR and or...
Yeah, the PR PR stands for what peanut butter raspberry? Pags blue ribbon. Oh, okay
Well, I was close. I was close. I was just a little bit kind of
Incorrectable, what do you mean? You're why are you embarrassed for me? I'm sorry. No, why are you laughing?
Why are you laughing? I like I like to smile in your eyes, so damn sweet pea whoops. I mean if someone's waffle
Stops in the shower. Yeah, I don't know what that means
Person and right we have school behind the bike shit. Oh, yeah
Guys, we have an interesting chat going on for people in the chat, too
Samantha the attractiveness that I'd laugh. I have one more beer left. Can I make walk to the store you?
Some more cigarettes
I'll try to make the rest of the week waffle stops. I don't know
Don't even don't even you guys are just like don't even it's not nice
It's not a nice thing for people to do especially adults. I don't know anyone who's ever done that
People saying people to think that don't say that it's gross stop it stop it. No
Yeah
Don't make me go in there
Let me think of like you said about all the people. It's like yeah, we're all beautiful people
And we all have to you know
Be ourselves always otherwise if you're faking it, you know, that's when people get called out, you know what I mean?
Yeah waffle comes from the shape of the plug hole. I don't know what you guys talking about what kind of waffle window
I did I did have to get my guy
The guy that came over really yesterday. He'd like clean my whole bath of my bath. So but like now that I see it white
I thought it would just had just turned
Yellowing different color, you know, I said I'd change this color. I thought the white porcelain and chain
It's completely white again. It's like it got I don't know. It was so bad before and but then I'm taking a spiritual bath
And so I had all these leaves and like berries and herbs and everything and he's like what the fuck is he
Do they thought I had like the brothers of nature from out there? No, it was just my spiritual bath stuff
And then he he clogged in my dream, but I unplugged it haven't yell a lot. Yeah
What happens in jail? What's happened? You any paces waffle? Oh, yeah, please
I'm sorry. I don't mean to read the comments before
People don't really don't write things that I don't want I wouldn't want to say a lot, please
Lot of evil things in jail. I don't a lot of good things, too
I thought people make some really good
Ilja come up and pronounce your name first
Beedah's calling him Elijah
Eliza, I know I heard that the other lies Eliza what?
Eliza
Blow them off blow them off like blow them off like this. Oh blow them off
You let you lie. Oh blow them off. I don't know people do better themselves in jail. Yeah, better ourselves better ourselves
On skin well, I don't know that's no supper horse
Hey, so sweepies a waffle guys. What do you have my waffle stamps? All I know is like I met I
Someone like let me borrow a pair of shoes for the shower. I take a shower with a couple other guys
It was very erotic
Now I worked in the kitchen. He let me use his phone card. I
Was gone. I was out in three days
This is in 2018 guys. I've changed my I've changed my ways
I've changed my wicked ways, but I don't know where you where you like one of the tier runners
Yes, I was I was a trustee, so I was I worked in the kitchen. I don't know
Yeah, trustee right. Yeah, it's different same thing different. Yeah, I like the movie blood and blood
Obviously when everyone's locked up you would be let out so you could do clean up and do other shit, right?
Yeah, I'm the first I'm the first and you have to sleep with in order to get the
Because I'll see you get through the ventilators and have a ride a ride a race to pick you up if you
Make love to me. Okay, the chocolate warm waffle. Oh, yeah, I had a I had a Robin sandwich
It wasn't quite the chocolate waffle, but I didn't see people make these really intricate cakes and stuff. I
Heard that someone was talking about it and I didn't
Know what it meant and I figured like you would know cuz he went to jail
I think it's like the little drains are shaped like a waffle and then people step on them and then it's like and then it's like
That's the worst thing because it wasn't yeah, yeah
Did like everyone knows when you don't even play you don't play in the showers. Oh, yeah
But you don't play in the shower
You can't you can't do because I kind of did but here's what they have to take you to the toilet
They're like you have to like go to the toilet and you have to like use it like backwards
You just sit on like if it's in the toilet backwards
and then like keep flushing it. So it's like apparently that's how they were originally made.
You're supposed to sit facing so you can put your book in your coffee and everything.
Well, yeah, that's that's that's the butters that South Park butters like oh yeah, we'll
do this. Yeah, South Park episode. I'm really surprised nobody has done like a remix of rum ranch
Ram Ranch. Yeah. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't want to get like you and like all the all of your
Stumps around here. Like it would be really cool to do like a real like a real
No, no, that's right. There's a real place a
Ram Ranch is that where like, you know, you get Ram
Showering club is a gay club the gay club. No, it was a it was a
It's the ranch
Casey do you want to come to the Ram Ranch with me and have some fun?
I don't know. That's what I always got when I heard that word Ram Ranch. Isn't it like a gay club or something?
I thought I was like a porno company
Of like gay people
In the shower
Pink pony club pink pony club guy. You look at this all called pink. I'm on Google it because I swear in
Massachusetts in the Boston area. There was a gay club
What's that what's that island in Providence or something with what's in Provincetown or what's that?
What's the gay thing in Rhode Island or there's there's some like Provincetown or there's some famous Massachusetts
Martha's Vineyard as big for gaze. Okay. Yeah like Leo
Yeah, that's where like the Kennedys lived and shit, you know rich out there like Taylor Swift got her house out there
No, well mansion
I've seen island. Yeah guys. I've seen it. I actually call it little saint James and it was his nicknames
I've seen island also as a Phoenician temple there
I think I heard that they're gonna they're gonna destroy that place. No, they're not what they're selling it
No, no, no, they're selling it. They're doing something. Yeah
Like this they're gonna like demolish
It's already government-based they're not gonna sell it or anything no one's gonna ever go there
It's like it's like hard to get into them fucking
Look in Antarctica. It is. Did you see that video? There's a you
Yeah, yeah, YouTube channel. He made a video of trying to get on to Epstein Island
Like he took a boat out there. He snuck onto the island and he got caught stuff, but um, you know
He videoed the whole thing and how you short edits of how it used to look and now it's now
Yeah, I mean, it's an island and it's like, you know, it's all these billionaires
Yeah, it's like there's not really that great stuff on there
It's like it's like they come on the helicopters safe for like in a day with the food they brought and then take off
That's just the one they found out about trust me they they they move shop through another island
Rich billion is out there. They get that own islands and shit like that. It's like
When you got big money
Casey are you coming out of the closet Casey someone says you're this you're coming out party tonight. Oh, I'm not game
Yeah, I'm straight. Oh, he said he's straight guys. I have to take his words for I think he I think he's a father
I don't know. Hey, hey, and he said no, no, oh, that's in your chat
So someone's saying the end of word in your chef. Let's see
That's okay
Well, you gotta remember to like especially now since Trump became president, you know, like it's all the young Democrats
They they all went to Massachusetts, California, you know to fight Trump's deportation, you know
Well, yeah, they didn't all go anywhere. I mean the most numbers sitting like complaining about it
I mean a policy isn't supposed to lead me
I really that's why I don't want to talk about on the show because it's like I don't even care about it
No, it's not what he brings it to you.
Yeah, time said you came out of closet tonight. Oh, yeah. So time said it
Casey, it's okay
Attractable do you want to hold hands and support KZ coming out?
KZ's also
Attractable is married. I know I know I don't say he's getting thank you. I could use
Support him. It's in the support
To be a home record is that way you're trying to do home record? No home record
It's a home record what he's not being honest with his wife or his drunk friend
That's not adultery if he's not not if you do to me because I
Hands I can do that if somebody
I mean, I forbid him to date you, you know case you only date me or
That's when I approve, okay
Casey that doesn't apply when you when you join the when you join the join the Psyche's Angels membership
Okay, I'm just kidding. Who is who's the does Jimmy me? Oh, I was just thinking I was just about this year's story
But then earlier somebody said that I she had too much sometimes so it's okay
I overshare to all my classic overshare all share so much that you don't even know what's true or what's not
Okay, okay as we can had to be proud he June might be
But you can still let the rainbow flag fly. Yes, you can't keep
Like this is your last day
Gay prize over if I don't make it through this year. This is my last gay pride month guys, you know
I'll make it I'll try to make it to next year. I don't know
45 you know when I was a younger man and running around getting high
You know, I ran into a few people who were, you know, homosexuals, gay men, and we get
high there.
And there was a couple men who tried to convert me, wanted me to convert, but I'm a straight
man.
But no the convert you so what do they do they said okay, they're like
They get super aggressive and you know
Do drugs with me and off me all kinds of
They put their hand in your lap
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
The series
Get a blowjob, I mean come on join the world. I mean
2025 what do you think I mean all the cool people are gay now
Well, I'm just too sure to hide things KZ. Just come out. It's okay
I don't even have a blow job like I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job, but I'm not even a blow job
I am you wake up and you see all you see is a blonde wig in your lap. You think it's Paris Hilton
um
I say that that's hot
And then you then you fall back asleep. So are you even mad at me the next day?
When you found out it was a personal it was just me
No, I said you're you're woozy you're getting you're like
You're okay. No, no, no, no, no, you thought you you saw I was there
You were like, oh, we thought I was parachuted to that. Oh, you got me high enough to be complete. Yeah
Yeah, but it was such a cheap way that nobody would be fooled by that way they get really I got a party city
It was like $1.99 a party city in the bag about this week. It doesn't it actually come on fire after I left
Party city first of July is coming up. Are you gonna wear the speedo for like
Making a reappearance guys
I'm just kidding guys. I'm just kidding. I'm sorry. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I'm not trying to be like too
I'm trying to be for comedians for entertainment purposes only if you don't you don't like anything else
As long as you can laugh and have fun
That's all I care about. It's not about
changing the world. Okay, so
How's everyone doing? Hey, Shorty. Sweet P time. Hey, Shorty. It's your birthday. Hey, Shorty. Hi, Shorty. Listen, Psyche, I got a drop down. Thank you for loving me up. I was fun. You're welcome. I love you.
Hey, guys. Later, Paige. I adore you. I hope you have a good day and a nice tomorrow or everything. Love you. Love you. I will see you guys soon. Bye, Casey. Be good. Bye.
Love you. Bye. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cagey. Be cage
Happy birthday shorty. Hey, oh
His baniel if you are you banning it must be rich had Casey what's going on?
Yeah, the stupid hateful comments from the retard. Yeah, what's his name?
That's in my chest. Yeah
Happy birthday shorty
So yeah, I'm gonna try to quit smoking cigarettes, but you know, maybe not today
Maybe they ought to try to try later this week. I think I'm gonna get one more pack tonight. Just one more pack and a lighter
Katrina. Oh my gosh. Okay gosh
Casey you can't ban your old Chad come on Casey you gotta let yeah
That's just one person that right there is March. He hangs around with that schoon. He can't even come on YouTube anymore
He's banned of Aiden. He's one of those low-powers like Syrax who just immediately gets banned from YouTube
Yeah, skin walkers are scary. Yeah
They're scary. Oh my god. I
just
Yeah, they said
Mr. Big Pipe that is my revenge you forever. I have a better invitation of you than you even sound this funnier
people like it better there I also told mr. I don't say no mr. Big Pies and he
was they own he's their own mr. Big Pies he just rolled his eyes they okay he's
like yeah yeah he's gonna cast spells on us and people to be like us right
mr. Big Pies sweet sweet on a on a rowboat in the Pacific Ocean
And singing a song it should not be on some dry land on my show you support kids
Then you should oh my gosh
You know walkers are scary. Yeah. Yep. I know I did a skin Walker Marcy
I was in your skin Walker or hey, okay. She called herself different things
She could shape shifts. She knew how to turn into like a
200-pound lighter person 20 years younger. I saw it a few times
Pretty interesting. Yeah, let's first my date is
Yeah, is that one good is that I'm talking about you having fun, so
Wait, I completely defeated Mars like I made him run away. He talks my kid like I exposed him for who he is
Like he don't even come around anymore. He hangs around that kinky trim the true and kinky cartoons over there
They don't even talk to me anymore
And you know what they don't even want me in there chat because they know all the shit
I know about them big dogs kid. They literally
Exposed my children. Why are you bringing my family into the
And that's why he ain't even allowed on YouTube he's a low car like that
I don't know these people I don't know these people. I don't I don't I don't think I want it. I don't know if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you if you
But everyone I don't have enough enemies I don't need like a thousand more enemies, but please please case me
Please I have enough enemies. Please don't call it people on the show and in a bad way
I just I don't know it has nothing to do with you
But then they come at me saying they're gonna strike my channel there
I'm in trouble and I say I don't have anything to do with it
So I'm saying it's like just be careful with what you say cuz
You're getting people mad at me that I have nothing to do with and it's a for your beef and it's like and I don't know anything about it
so
Okay, so hey
Our and you know, you know one person you don't ban from your chat is use spamming the n word I can't see
You need a lot. You need a modding
And I didn't see one objectionable comment. What are they? Okay, there you go. But what are they where they stay? Oh, they're
Okay, yeah, they got a spam lot. Oh, it's okay. I understand
Get a spam lot for you
Oh, yeah, it gets exhausting all guys, but you talk about I think he has okay. Yeah
Yeah
Why are you bringing up other people are like it's like oh, hey, you know this person blah blah blah like I
Would be like oh, I don't know them or do you know them?
Oh, here's some names and like they'll go fuck them. I mean, or they're back and I was like, oh, I
I don't know
Also, I'm getting all this like and why is the n word repeating over f a gg ot. Oh my gosh
KZ control your chat, please. I mean, this is hurting my feelings now
Thank you. Thank you. It's okay. It's okay. I'm not really feeling good about it. Just ignore it
Now it's going to keep happening like
Just you should have just
Casey I got 40 people in my chat. I got 40 people in my chat and no one's bothering me. Okay. I know how to deal with these people
I don't do it. Okay. Okay. Hey gays. Hey, oh, yeah
Hey, Samantha. He also joined a two-show community as okay. It's okay. Why I'm not gonna read
I'm not gonna read those rude comments about Casey or anybody else because you know what?
He's my friend and these people are my friends and I'm gonna
protect my friends and it's like unless you have some kind of like proof to show me something and you want to send me something
And my discord maybe the hope I hope to change my mind. I probably wouldn't change my mind
I'll say hey, I like them anyway. I don't care. They have something some weird thing in the past
You know, I think they're different people now. I think we all y'all kids change, right?
It is oh, what?
Can a mom post my discord yet to go to the discord I can I can do it
I just a minute I might be going to the store in a few minutes
Uh, I mean, I don't know if the new discord think it's on the
Can't you show your butthole? Yeah, well, yeah, but you make Ilya you have to show it in the chat
You can't show your butthole on the panel and also Ilya I
Think I think maybe times it by a membership Ilya
I'm just saying because it's like, you know, you were good in the last time you didn't pull mom me twice
I think it's like, you know, I want you to like hey flirty
Oh flirty. Oh flirty. No, I don't I don't know if it I don't think so. I don't think he does
No, no, no, let's let's not get into this. Let's not get it. We've discussed it on the show before. Yeah, I
Don't think he wants to respond to this in the moment and
No, I wouldn't want to anything. Yeah, right. I know I think you want to have one
I have your own panel where you can respond to it because it's just like this is people sit talking shit
They don't know anything about it. Yeah, I know I come here just to chill. Have a good time
This is just yeah, I know I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't you bother. I'm just saying I think you know
It's like once they saw that it brought attention to them, you know, you're gonna keep wanting that
No, it's like I mean that was that was the last attention that I would but we're getting there in our lives
Okay, that's so they'll be just like grasping and straws. Okay, so I'm back. That was a fresh discord. I'll pose. I'll be right back
Where's everybody?
Okay, yeah, I I don't know how it keys me back
I was just I went backstage to get the link for the for the discourse. There's case the whole there's a link to the
Discord guy
Don't give them my link. Don't give them my link. I'll fucking cancel it
So you don't know the retards. It's a private. No, no, no, no, it's not it's not you know, it's not your link
This is my link. I posted my my disposal
So they can people can join mine if they want because people are asking for my link
But I think you're presenting your link KZL not sure. Oh, okay, my fault. I apologize. No, I did that in back chat earlier
But it's not even there. Okay. Okay
Yeah, are we okay guys cave you just let me go. Oh, I don't know. I don't want to read your comment. Oh, okay
Yeah, it's okay if you're poor. I mean as I'm yeah, please
Yeah, I literally have negative 50 cents on my bank account. I can I know I can survive
Samantha Avery your Irby. Yeah
Hey, baby. Hey, Marcy. Hey Marcy. How are we doing guys? Okay? I think I'll finish this beer
I mean, I think I was walked down to the store. I don't feel like looking at the bike today
It's like too depressing. This doesn't work right now. I'm gonna get it fixed seems they can
You notice how much will cost hopefully it'll be reasonable you think probably probably for them is probably just like oh
The place that's used and that's it. No big nothing
By charge at least 100 bucks, right?
There you go. Thank you so much. Thank you person
Persons updated the discord link, but yeah, that's expired a few days kind of inconvenient. Lisa does change hers though
Because he's terrified of asking me to his price like you have thought about the baby
Yeah, but they don't really have babes in California
They all of babes are you know I can smoke the weed babes
But then all like the these are kind of flavors, but they're not really flavors are all weed flavor
But then it's like that the I used like menthol babes and stuff
They don't have anywhere they don't they have like these jewels. They should like these kind of
Not very good. So wrong shit
Now we get
No true matter Gus under his all it's not his and K. You're the one I use you
Oh, I don't know. It's been on Casey. Are we meeting psyche? It might take you to the discord they
a lot of he produces family. Yeah. I'm I can probably Casey. I probably won't I'm like not really joining this. No, you don't don't. I don't know. I know. I
want a drama. I don't come here for drama. They want it. Psych. If you want to give it to them, use it. Yeah. That's what I do. I don't. I don't. All my drama is on my show liquid, like, you know, like I I had stuff going on on my discord and
Uh, you know, it's it would just show your butthole. I can't show it on my show. I have to send me private private message
I'll show you a private message
Purge. Yeah, thank you time
uh
Kind of
I don't know if some of these people there you go your body your choice Steven was that from Steven. I know my first
Hey, you know who they were just picking on to remember blame Katie
Somebody was up here and told me about her not too long ago on your panel, and that's when I first picked her out and she was
Popular in that Cyrax universe, and that's the guy who got really jealous because they couldn't be
And that's, you know, in this weird extension.
So they, they, they just blame Katie. Yeah.
So she, she's back finally.
Blame Katie right now, man.
What, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, kick rocks man. This isn't the place.
Juan says he's not.
Marc, he's Juan.
Casey don't shift the focus onto Katie.
Hey, let's think of how many alts have been.
Where's Art Vandalay been?
Oh yeah, that's right.
Justin Bentley, Ted Smokha, is dead.
I don't know if it's you, I don't, I just don't know like I don't know if he's talking shit or whatever. I just want you to let's let's not talk. Hey, Floody, come on panel. I want to talk to KZ and Page and me.
Hey, he said are you made these alts because you kept banning your tower?
Well, yeah, that's because you're saying the n-word and f-a-g-g-o-c
What am I not supposed to be? Yeah, you're retarded dude. Like you are literally a retard like that comment says everything
I said like come on dude. What are we working with? Yeah, who is this guy psyche? I'm sorry
He's one of them who sub to my channel just to see what I'm doing that do this
You know, but he's not a lot around me anymore. He knows he's he got what he the pit the link is pinned
Yeah marks marks
The battery home
Long time. I've been here. I think I did your favorite song
I see. Oh, my phone is dead, so of course I can't play it right now. Oh, hold on. What's it got? I'm looking diamond. Hold on
Let's go along
Hold on one are you there? Who's one? Who are you? Oh, I'm one
One
How are we doing?
Yeah, how are you? Hello? Oh, I'm doing amazing. I see you support a pregnant woman beaters or woman beaters who beat women
You're wrong
Oh, I know what and he's
Not you for it was that you
He's even worse than who I thought do it like it so we have nothing to worry about it
Young young
He's one of those who's still hanging around thinking they own Marty's old discord. His mind is not there anymore
So he's one of those young kids. They like usually tools and stuff
I like when the discord I saw that I've seen that police report
There's no name on the police report if it is his name. There's no information about what really
I don't know it's like yeah, cuz it's like guys
I know I'm not choosing to ignore it diamond. I've seen that before I've read that. It's is a it's is a
MEDF or D man
What has been charged with this charge?
And that's it. That's all it says. It doesn't say oh here's exactly the details what happened doesn't say even his name
So it's not supporting it. It's not supporting anybody's having you know, and it's even if somebody does a horrible thing
I I can I can know so many that has murdered or unlawed people, right? I can know them and I can still say hey
I don't, I don't hate that person. I don't, there's a person, that person is saying very
bad.
That person, for example, was a big follower of Music Bismarie. Now we all know Music Bismarie
sold the women's drugs and that she dies from those drugs.
Marty ended up taking drugs and dying from drugs himself, you know
He thinks it's cool to follow Marty who gave a woman drugs and she died she lost her life that woman's gone
She's been gone for years. So that's cool to follow Marty, right?
But show the proof of where I did this
So
Hi, sweetheart. Hey, what if it's literally say if everyone is saying he did that and he's no good like everyone can't be wrong
So no, it's like, but you know what everyone can be wrong
Everyone can be because there was anybody there that night. Is anybody no detail. Does anybody
They know exactly what happened
Anybody know
I don't know if it's something new like come on just because everyone believes something doesn't mean it's true
That's why people you know are sometimes railroaded in this world sometimes people are just like ostracized hated
And they didn't even do anything imagine how bad how hard that would be if you didn't really even do anything
And then everyone hates you right?
I don't know again. I can't be having a difference of opinion. I just don't know the details of it
I know some other people can get uncomfortable, but this is the drama you say you like
Yeah, and I don't know keys these are saying you're talking about someone that passed away, you know case the you know
You're not you're not a channel. You're not you're not sick. You should have not be
Talking for the dead when they're not here. Okay, it's like because
You know, you don't have
Dead people
The Marty Marty's the reason I was able to scream I went
Ask him to help me he got me
Yeah, he knew Marty guys I do Marty's too Marty's done he's leaving out of it, but no, he's not here. He's not here. He's not here
Defend herself, but you know he would say about me. I knew I knew he'd say I'm I'm still underdog
I'm still underdog and I'm still
I'm still calling the best like I see him, right? I'm so I'm still winning
I know I know he's saying that his baby mama had to go to a shelter. Oh, I don't want to
Hey guys guys, we're not
You're not slandering the chat. I don't I don't know. Why are you talking in a family in the chat? Like what's wrong with these people?
Be in the meeting. That's
It's getting too it's getting too hairy guys
Yeah, okay. Yeah guys, um, jimmy kebler if there's something talking about
Okay, so all the shit you want about me
Leave my family on I don't say anything about anybody only time I come in people's when they come me
I'm always I treat people how I expect to be
Okay, well
Okay, so it's all it's all kind of deep breath. Okay, we're all doing good. It's what is it Monday night guys Monday night guys
Guys, it's a new day. It's a new week. It's it's it's tomorrow's Tuesday, you know Tuesday is Tuesday
Tuesday is the day of Mars
They try to make me look bad in front of the pretty way I know don't worry about it. Don't worry about it
I was really
Let it just a cool
Not a sex you say because people will say anything. They call me the worst names. They call me the worst names in the world
Yes, the panel loves women
Well, no, no, no, no, no, it's horrible. It's horrible. We love women. We don't love the rest of the thing you said
No, we don't know but we you know what even like even like a woman would be interested to know like what make what?
Even if that was true in some way, what makes that what it what makes a man sick?
They would like I've been around here for a long time
By Marcy guys like you'll get a life
And I kind of brought this one too because I
Just they're just you know, they're just trolling right now. They're just trolling easy. Don't don't take it too hard
There's trolling. Okay, there's trolling. You're saying they know one thing that bothers you
It's the one thing that bothers you but the same that right, you know, so that's the one thing they're gonna say that
This is this block block them ignore. I'm not gonna read any of it. Okay, and I'm sorry if I
This isn't someone calling names actually read your information if that okay. Well, but what's the fact?
I didn't see any fact besides I start heard a criminal charge. It's like at least it got charged with you know
You know
Beating her boyfriend, right? So it's like I would have just read the charge
I'd say oh this woman she beat her boyfriend
You wouldn't have seen where he was hitting her back and that she wasn't even hitting him like you know really
Harmful way really there's like three suits is kind of to me. He had he was he pulled her hair. He was worse than her
I'm an idiot very very that's why you're not some fucking mod here
That's why that's why you're you're you're just you know, you just you're grinding grinding Kate and
It's simply for flirty diamond and you don't even know what the fuck you can do here. You're just like oh, I'm just an idiot, right?
I'm an idiot, right cuz I want
Casey's dick. Oh, I really want Casey's dick. What dude? Okay, Casey has a dick of a cockatiel to me
It's like it's like it literally I think of it as like a little cockatiel dick. Okay. I don't even I don't know
You know
It was good, but it was not I mean his it was like this guy is really famous guys in the music
Marcus something like that. He's a black porn star. He's really famous. Yeah, it was his it was his dick
Very, you know, why did you go for the best black male porn star? You know, you could have like said, oh, you know
We'll go for like someone with like, you know, there's an old piano
No, you have to go for that guy with the best penis in the industry
I came to run for as a monster a little longer and so you started talking shit about me Barry Barry. I don't like it
Barry yeah, I like the dickpicks. I
Like the dickpick though. I still have it. Well, yeah, I mean yeah, it's fucking with it. What are the guys name is?
Not you who's to whose butt was that Barry Barry? Who's who's to whose butt was it? I can't find them
I can't track down the but I can't
And that's where my old phone broke cuz I like drooled so much on it. It's
Sparks sparks electrical over heating. Okay guys. I
Don't know guys. I'm drill
Or in 10 minutes to go. I'm gonna walk to the store
Same guy. It's the same guy
Not you not you
You give like you look like fat Albert's grandfather
BV bad boy Barry also big but Barry. Yeah, we all stuff guys. Yeah, we're having fun. We're having fun
Hey
Are you good? I'm gonna see smile page. Yo, hey, wait, wait, you ever smile around me anymore. You don't like me
Okay, I'm just listening. No, no. I'm just in my head a lot. Lily. I don't know
You always look you always look disapproving. Oh, they're oh, hi, sweetheart. You're just approving. I'm
Laughing sometimes you look at me like this
I look at everybody like that because I'm squinting because I have glasses and they're always sliding down my face.
I'm squinting too. See my eye color or not?
It's green.
It's like green.
Green. I got green.
I got green.
Big chip kick.
You're feeling this whole channel. Oh you do Shane. I have a feeling you're gonna you're gonna have like these hemorrhoids in your butthole
They're gonna be really painful swollen irritating. You're gonna have to get the expensive preparation H
They're gonna go down. They're gonna go away
But this is gonna be blood on your toilet paper for a while. So there you go Shane enjoy that reading
Sorry, that was just an impromptu
It's hemorrhoids. It's hemorrhoids. Oh, he's taking my tail is going down
His bus bus going down
Okay
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry guys
Hi, Jimmy Jimmy's in the chat, you know Jim Nick sees the actual real panda emoji the picture of Jim Nick as
What's the other Jimmy picture?
Okay, you're shuffling
Hello, hello. Yeah
I hear shuffling. What do you mean? Like cards? I just yeah
I was gonna shuffle some for like a live later for like a reading later. Okay, okay
If one pops out you can just look all the time. I'll pull out a card here. I have a card for the chat
Guys doing a card just for me. I mean me to you. Oh for me to you
I'm gonna get this part is like this chariot card
Characters moving forward
Moving forward it's a Allison little bottle or it's like this
You know, I don't know she's in like a opera box or the baseball game or something like that
Even if you're sitting still you're going someplace, right?
It's like your it's like the mind that goes places. You're just moving forward. You got some cats right there, too
You like that little car for you guys
little mini
Tent or tree frog is here. It keeps me better. Oh
Tenting is here. What is what does tenting mean?
Tenting play dance in the mixture. I know I can't play it. I can just sing it
There's a big John's and her can't stop can still this moment
Lots of certain dance we chase for love's hope and potents dance to the Missy series
I don't know that's all I have to remember
Why does it still show up for us when you
When we do the I don't know you know she's up for me because it comes through my stream yard
So it's like so I get it before anybody else
It comes through the the text goes through my stream yard now
Hey page page. Oh, oh, let's everyone live in the page. Oh, look at this. Oh, yeah. Oh, uh-oh
Let's let's sit in river. I'm gonna sit inside. Hi, babe
You go girl
If someone says I adore page
Okay, okay, we're here like you know the chats really looking forward to it looks like it says
Lord Vader says I adore page
You know Lord Vader never said anything nice to me, but he's yours. You're reading. Yes. I
Actually like I like that I like that you're a little intense significance other. Oh, oh
I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna read the comments.
Guys, anyone want to donate or reading tonight? Page is shuffling and reading. Oh pages shuffling. I'm gonna put up the banner real quick.
I think she wants to shuffle real quick. She's shuffling the cards. Hey guys, if you want to join the membership
Guys we have like 79 78 76 77. I don't know. It's like someone between 76 and 80
Memberships it's a hundred guys
There's a page page it back
My cats are fighting. You guys quit it. They're like growling and running. Oh my god. Get away from my feet.
So, old people, what are you saying? I hope you are done living at your...what?
What?
Okay, I think I think one one is ready one is ready to say adios to one
Guys, are we ready to say adios to one?
Is there a mod in the house?
Jamie
Jamie are you here? Jamie can you hear me kick off one?
Kick off one, please
You don't think he's talking me home. What do you say? Oh people I don't know what he's talking about support the work
Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah, he's is guys can someone delete what? Oh, I'll do it. I
Will I'm ready to kick you off. You're very annoying one and you're just using my name just to annoy me
Your name is not Juan. I'm Mexican your white fat Jewish man. I know who you are
Oh
You're very should play death. Yeah, I would choose over you the dog in the hat. We get a petition to get time
Unmotted on water. Oh time late
Yeah
time
Time I think Jay dogs. It's just a time
Jay dog you have a picture with dog. I think it's perfect. I think it's kids met
Dance to the mystery page your your microphone your mic
You could open up I
Know I kept it up for a reason so that wasn't loud. It's just so loud on the table. Oh, thank you. Make sure you know
Okay
What did you pull?
I pulled the chariot. I pulled the chariot car. So they keep moving really forward and like you know coming out of whatever
Whatever's stuck in right now. We're just coming out of it. I see like this big like kind of like pull like
Kind of like my electric bike. It's off. It's pulling me
It's thundering here enlightening
Oh
You're singing
Chargers jump jumping out of the deck it's a response. Well, this deck is just kind of like spastic. I don't know how to explain it
That's too many
Okay
We have a night of swords in the upright so this is you know, this is worrying
Which changes nothing so it's silly for us to do that to ourselves. It's overthinking. It's just it's constant. We're a sleepless nights
This is heirs of Gemini its strength and selflessness and deeper meaning so
You know sometimes those thoughts that drive us crazy that constantly cycle and we lose sleep over we do sometimes find clarity in them
Just being optimistic
But anxiety and hopelessness and captivity and imprisonment feeling like a victim victim mentality for sure
and we have the six of wands so it says you weren't this was in the it was in
the reverse so it's you in the upright it would be you have earned every one of
your successes you know progress and confidence but it's in the reverse so
it's pride of riches delay fear apprehension doubt and feeling ignored
you know but finding solutions healing and empathy also fires so this is Leo
And then we have then we have the five of cups. This is Scorpio
This is water and leaf and like sadness and like but no knowing that things will get better. So it's almost like
like knowing what's to come
Next like that there can be better to come because there's only
Like look at all those built cups
Yeah, but there's still some that are full behind. Do you know what I mean?
So he's not worried about the two that still have you know
Have something
It's crying over spilled milk basically pretty much
It's like feeling your grief, but knowing that'll get better so that lost self pity despair disappointment, you know
Disillusionment morning. Okay, that's pretty sad
Yeah, we know another car to car we know the car to cleanse the pallet like that
Advice advice like word advice. How do we how do we move forward from this? How do we forward?
She's hopeless there he goes it popped out
Beautiful it's the Sun. Oh
You know, the success lies ahead. So this thing that too is just clarifying that you know
Just because these cups have spilled milk doesn't mean that you don't have milk later or that either isn't going to be replenishment of it
There's always something to look forward to
You know and coming out of that conflict just finding it within yourself to do that
I think you know and not worrying so much like this
You know other people think and other people's pressure and other people's opinions and other influences in general or like you know
Addictions or or I don't know habits just things like that
They keep you locked in your head and like constantly cycle and cycle and cycle thought but you learn from it
Right eventually you do learn from it because this is this card right here, but coming out with the Sun. That's great
I think yeah
That's all the advice the sun is like I'm very yeah, we got the fast fast moving energy coming with that the wands, right?
Moving positive energy your news fast moving success out of this area of despair
Interesting hey, and that's also like you know guys because it's like also
It was especially with that five of cups like the five of cups is like really the dark night of the soul
And so they have that followed by the Sun card as like the advice
it's like you know it's like we can like kind of like
Shine our own light to get us out of any problem guys. You know how amazing it's like
We think we're so hopeless. We're stuck in this dumb
Allison wonderland all these laws and and we're supposed to do this we're supposed to do that morality and stuff like that
Which is not and then it's all different standards for everybody, right? It's like so, you know
We're just in this like we're kind of world. You know love yourself guys love yourself and like a
And then have that joyous like that child's heart like just like you're pretending like you're right. You're naked. You're riding a horse
You're you're letting go dive. You're right. They're horsing with for feel the sunflowers
You know, you're you're reborn that kind of thing. It's a really positive energy. Okay
So I hope you guys like that page page is awesome reading for everybody
I don't even know the cat's name. Obviously. Who are cats?
I don't know the cat's name is church. I know a cat's named
cat's named
This is Christine's his name Romeo pages. His name's Raven mine is named Lenore tricks
Marvel I haven't seen Marvel in a few days. Oh my god. It's 9 30. Yeah, that's a
I'm gonna walk to the story. Oh, I hear me out. Did you hear me out? I heard me out
Burry it's gonna storm out there
You're not gonna want to go outside, buddy
If it's storming that that's when the cat's gonna want to go out. You're probably gonna want to go out hunt
Yeah, he wanted to go outside
That's birdie
Burr burry burry bur like be you are our burr. Oh, burry burry
Yeah, burr in your fur
very for
Well today I came across another
black Raven Raven or
Crows feather you have more crows right here than Ravens I can
If I was to pick up all the feathers I saw again, I just see feathers all the time
It's like is there kind of rare you find feathers
Blue jays everywhere. I've been seeing DJ's everywhere. I go
Yeah, then yeah, well, maybe the blue jays are either with the world series this year. I'm not sure I'm not sure
Uh, they're they're they're baseball. Oh, no, let's hope not red socks red socks. I read the red socks. Okay
Hey, so 10 Doug you aren't oh my gosh
Who's who's it?
Who's 10th dog? Oh, hold on that 10th dog. Okay. J-dog time my credentials speak for themselves. Okay, so J-dog is a
military
Former military police officer. He's he's worked for the FBI
He's giving tips
He's the he rents air B&B's
One after the other there's there's no explanation for them
He has a secret job probably some kind of you know informants or some kind of government
government informant, but you know we like him any way like him a cool guy
He didn't he didn't talk to the FBI about me, but
That's okay. I forgive you J-Dog. No
I forgive you. Oh
Page oh page left page from the FBI. He's out of here
page
So in a few words, he's a pretty big
He's a pretty big deal. No, he just needs to try to tell someone to take you all the old man. Oh
J-Dog
Hey dog, what do you what are you talking about J-Doc? What do you think you're talking about?
J-Doc
Play on J-Doc
You told you guys we need can someone get the audio of that. I mean I need to remind you of what J-Doc said to me
He did on camera, I know
J-Doc
I mean, I would buy JDogg. I would literally buy him a hotdog and probably a beer. I
Mean I would
Someone get that. Oh, yeah, can someone find that it was you know
Okay, sweetheart, okay age. Thank you. I know I think you have to go to the store
I really wish I had my bike to go
Has a little bit of power left too. I don't want to get stuck in
That's gonna fix it. That's gonna fix it. Okay
Time your words speak British Columbia. You eat the hot dog without biting it. What?
You just swallow it hold a dog you swallow it
Sit out a hole and digest this hot dog. What's going on guy guys?
Okay, it's the back. Okay
You'll sit back here for you. So KZ is getting it. He's you don't want to be on it. I don't know
Are you you want to just you sit back you sit back? Okay, we'll talk. I'll talk I mean I'll talk to myself. I can talk to myself
Okay
What's going on, you know
You've been gone you were gone for a little bit would you take a bet on a couple days you didn't show
I was gone for a little bit little now back again. I didn't I slept I cleaned my house guys
My floor is like clean like there's no fleas. There's like
No, there's no crap on my floor. It's just all clean fleas
They bring in occasional fleas, but you can brush them, you know, brush them, brush them,
we'll get that peel out with those good brushes.
She brought me some flea medicine, so there's no fleas, and then the bathtub, which was
like disgust, it was like all this color, it was like disgusting color, it was like,
oh my god, looks like it.
Like it's just someone covered in mud that
My bath that now it's completely white the kitchen the floor is all clean that everything's everything's looking good
I keep I keep CRL for that. You know that fear. Oh, yeah
Yeah, why is calcium line restore something that calcium line rust calcium line rust?
That's what it stands for right calcium line rust simply call it. Yeah
everything
the um the bathtub you know and that because that's the worst that to get clean sometimes
well full stampy i don't know it's how well full stampy it was just like you know i do like you
know i i was doing like a lot of like uh like colored spiritual baths i had they all this like
you know these like things and they just colored my bath kind of and then i say i i should have just
like dumped a bunch of like fucking you know bleach on it just shrub shrub shrub but it's like
I kind of gotten so lazy and I kind of got hopeless and I was like, oh, you know
It's not even worth it. Like, you know, but it is worth it guys
You know fighting fighting for your life, you know, it's like that'll keep you like alive
It's like even if you don't win, right? It's like how about like you like you actually like figure out a way to win
Everybody has won just by being alive. What are the odds?
I'm just being born, like, think about it.
We're born to this life, to experience it.
And as a temporary experience, it's a very temporary experience.
We have a certain amount of life to live, and then we're going to be gone.
And only our soul knows that answer, really.
We have the ability while we're here to like you know to have free will to decide what we want to do and do our best
And we'll see how it goes. I remember one side to the bathtub stream or pay to the bathroom's red shit
It looks like she was bathing a blood opaque paid to that. Oh my god
Well, you know, I think a spiritual bath and had some leaves in it. Yeah, kind of like
It was really nice. My bath looks so good right now. It looks so good baths with colors
Yeah, I mean it's like you know because there's like I had these my sister
I mean these shower steamers and you would like steam water on them and then they would
Like releasing a sense or something hey space transmission TV
Okay
So that sounds like this is a
Bathory, you know count his bathroom in the chat, you know bathroom. Hey guys, so there's a few things you can do to help the show
Okay, if you would like to help the show
You can become a member. That's probably the most important thing
I have like 79 almost 80 members
I'm gonna make the membership even better, but I will it can be asked me for reading
I'll give you a reading and I'll give you more cards and I normally give somebody that's for
How much are your memberships now?
499 for 99 a month and it's like and then it's uh, you know
You get the readings you get the extra content because I private most of my shows and still go back to the shows
So if you're a fan, that's probably gonna be worth it and then I have the you know
Your name goes in green with the moment you prefer like people get memberships people super chat
People
I mean because I get you know, you should pays out once a month, right? And so if you're gonna like, I mean
I love you. I love super chats, you know
But so the super chat and the
Memory they take 30 they take they take the same amount out. And so it also like sometimes I have to unfortunately like, you know
Like you know in my stream. So I'd say, you know, it's probably the best way to do it would be the cash app or to
To become or to donate memberships or become a member that kind of thing because
Now now we'll guarantee you'll know you'll be connected to the channel. It's probably the best way
But I don't I think I donated probably like 15 memberships this week
And then people have donated like 20 30 memberships and stuff. Wow guys, and so it's you know, it's pretty cool
I also started this thing. I don't know there's these gifts and that's like if people buy good gifts
I get some kind of rubies the rubies can be traded. I'm not sure how it works
I was looking into that and that's like the to show it's like a new thing
It's kind of like the twitch thing this way shows the top chatter and stuff and like you can turn that on and off in your settings
You know and you probably want that on
I turned it on because I want to see it work because I just started getting the top three
in chat.
Now it ranks the chat for participating which is kind of like a cool thing.
I see a bunch of people using it at the end of their shows, so now it's like the top three.
Top five
Yeah, I'm gonna start doing that I'm gonna start mentioning all the top people in the chat like you know the people that participate in the most in the chat
Yeah, that's a good way to reward people mod sweepy. She's being harassed. Okay, sweepy. No sweepy
Unfortunately, I you know this ideas would happen that
You know people will just start start to harass when I didn't have any mods
So let me
Go to my chat. Hold on. I will go. Oh mon sweet pea
Just remember guys, it's like some people at some people I have to because they're so
Kind and good people and then they're being kind of mistreated in my chat
Hold on. Oh, that's not going out live. There we go. This one so
It's okay. I just read the dog said the dog pounds coming from
There's a mod for me. You know, I have I have actually a feature says permanently on mod
And that's what I type next to JT
But yeah, sweet pea you're getting her you're getting harassed and check sweetie
I don't know because you are sweetheart, and you're hey guys, you know sweet people like first member
I remember things like oh this person my first member the first person to say hey, I'm gonna join this
Yes, it is it's a real sweet pea yep it is she text message me so I know her that she's the real one
Is that in English English?
Hey, sweetie, you got it. You got it. I know you. She never she never misused her. Come on
Hey, and sweet pea, can you get can you can you look out for JT in the chat? He or JT and the and
What's his name Vicky they're very insecure people. They're afraid that they're gonna get this ban from the chat and
JT just click the link
No, it's easy. Well, he's not gonna get banned from the from the panel, but he might get banned from the chat
I can always unban him because you always tell me just tell me, you know the channel owner
JT you know like you're like I'm this like lower tier the channel where you're like, oh
Who's this person? Who's the channel thing? I'm I talk to you daily like a lot
So it's like, you know and a lot of you it's like you think that we're like so far apart and you know
I'm like, I'm not right. I'm right here
Keep your eye on them. Yeah
Well, I think I did yeah, but I think they're good. I'm gonna mod a Memphis shade you I mean it's like you know
guys some people were just here for so
you just prove themselves as
Supporters, okay, I don't know how I can describe. I just get a feeling. I
Said you're coming up there. Okay. Hey, JC. You can come up here. I'm but you know you're
Hey, she's just regular month of shade. Yeah, no
Well, yeah guys, hopefully you don't you don't need one you trust your mom. Yeah, I bet yeah
That's exactly why I want you to have one because it's like I knew you were just a good month and
No
I think it's a good deal looking out because it's like sometimes I need people to look out for me
And I know you do okay, so say it was totally unprovoked. Oh, yeah
Yeah, guys, you know
The Almas Brigade yeah, I was like with my beard back. I thought they were Mormon. Oh my gosh guys, you know
I I'm like I'm I see the Senate of Joseph Smith. I'm like, I
Know oh my gosh, but I don't know I'm probably more Mormon than most Mormons, you know, right?
I don't think double recognize me as that
Yeah
Wait, I thought it was the Amish that were after you now you get the Amish and the Mormons
Well, no, no, because Alice was like I said it was the Mormons and then it's like someone said it was the Amish and then it's like
I mean, it was like at that point. I was just like ridiculous. I'm like, oh
Amish put up a barn
Yeah, I don't doubt it, but I think they were in Lancaster Pennsylvania. They don't
they're not fucking with me and you know a little like some like gay streamer in
California. I'm saying why why why is it almost yeah and that's what I mean some
of these people think like because some people really get scared just from words
you know so they think it works on everybody
Well, I'm not rid of the word Amish. I mean, we're afraid of the word
He's in Cal, you at the house in Amish, Pennsylvania, me and John
Right, right. It's horse buggy out there. Yeah. Yeah. KT. How's my sexy? How's my sexy wolf man?
How are you? How's my sexy wolf man? He is good. It's been a while. It feels like how many days has it been?
Hold on do you have no way with the dog pound I know it was in it. I'm sorry
Person I do I do they're actually under rules. I just buy I just buy the like the extra large under rules and
You know Superman that man and I get a little dog is done very nefarious. So watch out for him. They sell that in a
Yeah
Asked you see how much he loves cut off cancer nipples
I
Don't if you ask me how much I love them not at all. I've never seen one you've seen
I don't want to
Well, you know women who've had you know in breast cancer and had to lose they still need love too
They need love just not for me. It's okay
Like yeah, I feel like you've been live in like a couple. Maybe it's just me. I wouldn't know if you weren't live yesterday, right?
No, I did the same thing and then
Time said it to me in a chat today. I was like damn. He's right
It's crazy. I never get your notifications. I always have to check I
Always have to search if I never get your notification. I know it's weird. Did he say JT's nefarious? No, he said somebody else
He said a gay dog gay dog. Great dog, right? There's J dog and there's JT. I
Don't know
Shit it's fader, you know, Vader fucking psyche's always leaving us leaving his fucking pen. I used to do that too though
Mm-hmm midnight. Do you like like laser-cut nipples like cancer nipples like oh, I don't know why you're asking me that
What's your name KZ what's going on with you KZ? Oh
Fuck everybody's gone now much just you know just hanging out
Yeah, what's thank you don't he thought he had
Take a walk I think he gets people up here and he's like I can leave my panel now
I used to do it, too
Where the hell is everybody
Midnight, you're fucking weird, dude. You're the one over here talking about fucking cutting people's nipples off
Talking about
Are you going to bed sponky?
I'm probably one of the smartest people in the community and you know, half you guys have said that before
Cinnamon set it on his own stream
What did they say?
Yeah, I'm one of the probably one of the smartest people in the community. Oh
Is that right? I didn't know that I really don't know a lot of that was before years before they started hating
No, well
Once they hate you now you're an idiot again, you know
But what brought that up it was kind of out of the blue
I don't even know how to, it's just weird, I don't know, you know, it's all started just like posted in that Marty's Discord, you know, and
the same people I went there and that and that I'm about to talk to them and you know, and I don't know
I guess a couple of the waves thought I was cocky, the nerdy guys, you know
I'm not afraid to show myself I'm a tall handsome guy, you know
Okay, so you're not only the smartest guy. You're the tallest and handsomest guy too shit, man
You got a lot going for you
Thank you
That's what I mean. I'm like
You know, I've lived a good life and now I want to play on YouTube and these motherfuckers want to fuck around like they
They they want to think it there
Well, why do they hate you? Maybe you know what it is. Maybe maybe they're all jealous about you know
I don't know you'd have to ask them. I honestly could not tell you
I've been around for so long now, you know, in all the chats and uh, this this particular incident that was brought on tonight
is because I went back into
um, usually because Marty's dead server and you know it's controlled by
I don't know if you know about it but it's controlled by interesting folk, you know
So I just go in and hop in because I'll hop around from this good disco as he was going on
to the ones that'll let me in, you know, I'll talk my shit to the ops or whatever or
Say what's up to people and
Somebody who who somebody who I had run it who was around during the beginning time was still in that this board
He's like, oh, okay. Do you bet they can he could still like bully me, but meanwhile, it's like they're like 20 year old kids
Like am I supposed to take it serious like I'm I'm in my 40s now and like
The internet thought this doesn't work with me
And then the problem is I keep trying to tell them they keep using Marty's
Troll manoeuvres like that's not gonna work. It worked with a particular
Goblin that you gotta be unique Marty you gotta be yeah, like Marty's trolling style worked
With his trolls the people he the cows or whatever you want to call him hat, but now he he had all these
Little retards in his server, and it wasn't really his server. Like he knew it was just a you know, BF
I'm sorry, maybe I'm not getting a reference to a lot of what you're talking about
Does anybody in the chat understand what he's what he's talking about? I
Good question
Yeah, because I'd be honest with you. I don't know. I don't know who server you've been in. Yeah. Yeah, I know
I don't know like yeah, I just know it. No, it's you guys recently came in. I don't know where he is
Yeah, I
Really don't know
You know either way, I'm just not a follower on this thing
I come on here to have my own unique experience and I don't need to follow anybody and
So if I if my opinion goes against a certain group opinion
Boom, you'd be instantly become a target, you know, you know, you just you gotta put you got I can't I can't I cannot
Blind me fall. I'm too old
And stuck in my ways for that shit
And you go by KZ or do you have like a first name?
KG say you're playing on my last name
Oh, it's like a like a play on your last I got you got you. What's your last name?
corn
Corms K. A. R. M. Z
and
Carnes got you got you K. A. R. M. Z
God K. A. R. M. Z
You know, you know, that's not a that's not a very common last name. I've never heard that before
Not too often you hear that
With an answer
Yeah, you know, I never see a spell with a Z. It's crazy
Always in the news is that true are you in the news?
No, no, no, they're pulling up a police blog. You know what that is. It's like the weekly
Town newspaper and they you know all the weeks of rest from 2012 the last time I got arrested
Jio so when you say they them
Who are we talking about specifically?
Well, just like the underlings of the whole like
007 kind of spit, you know who 007 is now. I don't know who you know around here
I really don't is there anybody in here like in the chat that you could stay would be part of the most
Usually the ones talking shit, but they're kind of under all so I don't know how I could explain that
I don't know exactly which one is but it's a handful, but
it's most likely Tiki, when Tiki's one of them, it could be anybody, because once they see one person go, they'll jump on an alt, and just jump in, you know, once they see it gets attention, and then we'll see it all.
She's asking Memphis, can I understand him? Like I understand the words that he's saying, but...
like the context I really don't know what he's talking about very much. No. Yeah. Yeah, I get
I don't know how else to explain it exactly. You just I can't fill in that missing context
And that's what they'll try to do, you know, you go against the
If you have a phone line and you try to go against popular opinion
the
Like this try to ruin your name, you know the people or some carns KZ
People say a lot of shit about me too, and I'm like barely even known in these places
So it's like it's just it's part of the internet man. You know, what can you listen? I've noticed too
It's the same group that it's a weird group like in them. It's just a lot of groups men. It's a lot of shit
the question I mean
They're totally unsocial like unless you fall in line. It's it's just weird. I know it's weird
It's weird like you have to be a special type of reticers. They have to think they're better than you
Just fit in deal the phone line. Yeah, I mean like
Look man, it's not about being better. It's just about like
It's easier to troll in a group than it is like as a as an individual you got a whole fucking group
People back in here like it's fun. I can understand too because it's just a different generation
That's born with the internet. Luckily, like I was one of the last generations. We didn't have that shit
I know what I like Jinx. Are you Jinx?
My time was the 90s man in the 90s there was my decade growing up you like millennial or
Jinx. Well, you're born in the 80s
So I don't know what that is. Yeah. Yeah, you project X. I
Don't know why these people are older too, you know. Oh
Maybe you're a troll too who know you can see in your channels and stuff like like who's around and who's in the community
And it's basically all people we're all around same days all about people around like 30 to 50
majority people
Invader you ever been up here? You should come up here real fast. Oh
Shit, did you used to talk to Cyrax?
No, no, no, no, you never talked to that guy. I
Know he's like one of them. He's like one of the actual like kind of the famous ones as far as like the locales and shit
It's kind of famous
I kind of, I learned about him a little late though.
She says, no, you're lying.
Does truth even matter in a place like this?
Probably not.
Shay, you are an escort, Shay.
Yeah, you got it slow as you were an escort.
You ran and hid the tape to stop it, Shay.
I don't want to talk shit, but then they don't want to you know, I mean they like hypocrites
It's like look at your own life
You know fucking online escort. Are you gonna stick it in Chris?
Are you saying you're saying she's a hypocrite? Absolutely confirmed. Absolutely confirmed
Absolutely confirmed she had an online page and everything she's like 40 something
Oh, fuck it. She's got to make money too, I guess.
It's because I mean it like I don't care, but why front like she's sitting here playing like she's this house mom online
But you you're in a home
Own it. You're in a shit community. Like what do you care?
Why these people trying to moral fag in the worst they come from the Cyrus community
That's like the the taint of YouTube literally the asshole of YouTube of the people around the Cyrus community
And you're gonna take the moral fagging fuck out of here a mutant
Cards, there's no there's no morality on YouTube
Whoever told you that was full of shit
Sweepy I really don't know a lot about these locales honestly. I really don't follow that shit
I just I just saw like a picture Cyrax
I've never even seen his videos
Marty, I don't even know who the fuck that is
There's like a new one, too. I forget the guy's name
Who discovered like on cyrax, you know, and they all follow him and praise him like
You know, he even has thoughts you know, they like he gave a girl and she overdosed and died like people do shit
People live lives these people have lived years in their room behind the computer screen. That's the problem
You're saying they killed somebody
Hold on. What are you saying?
Oh page is in the back. I think okay. Okay. I think I saw here. Okay. Got my new charger guys. Let's see
Let's for that for the
brand new for the
This is the same kind of charger had on it
But we'll see if this one works if it doesn't this one's going back or the other one's gonna go back
Never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never mind, never
Wait, wait, wait, but Joker Joker's making fun of me. I see Joker Joker's type of shit wait for the grandmother
Come on. What do you think you for gruntle this gruntle Joker or the minute actually
She stands for degenerative principle, but it might also stand for gay and I might also stand for God
Might also stand for geometry and might also stand for gangster and might also stand for
Giovanni, which is anything with a G
For anything a kid, you know, and also it kind of looks like a toilet to and a toilet's called a John
Synchronous of these
Yeah, we're flushing away all the bad stuff. We're
Using the rest of polish the surface you're talking to me sex you were here. Yeah, I was in here
The it stands for I'm junk
What
This is where I'm jump. Yeah, but that starts with it. So I'm jump. So midnight. So midnight. Okay. You're talking about me now
So I'm jump. No, he means your junk like you're
No, no, like I'm jump like he's saying I am junk like I'm
Like your package like your junk like no, no, no
The G I don't want to be simple
I think he's the wrong way always
Paisie Paisie. That's a very large book page
We are all in trouble. We are all in trouble. What is this? Oh
It's a coloring book. Well, it's an Indian color. It's a coloring for us like discover Blackfoot Nat Nation art and wisdom
I'm gonna try to use this charge over back
Okay, my scooter working. It was working fine. I got it in the last leg. I got hearing back on it
So anything else I got back one last trip nothing. Oh, but otherwise it'll be serving a long time
I'm right back. You know, it's like you know, if you're gonna keep leaving it's like this. Just don't don't come back psyche
How about you never come back? How about how about I just kick you off the show of us never come back
Okay, how about that? Well, you have to wait now you have to wait for me
So here I'm just playing my phone. I'm just playing in the side of this charger
Darn scooter working. Oh, I mean bike
Guys, what if it works? What if that'd be so cool if it works something works once in my life something works
Okay, let's see. Yeah, plug it up. Okay, okay
Well, it plugs in guys sign one. What is the light off?
Okay, the lights on the green light is on guys. We have some green light now. Let's see if it fits in the hole
Okay, well
Guys time will tell
If not, I don't know this it doesn't seem like it's like it's the exact same as the other one
I'll try to move this forward a little bit
I only do one at a time though. Okay guys, I've tried my best. Let me see that's plugged in
It's like then that's what okay
Have my best guys
We shall see
You guys still hear me
Hello, yeah, yeah, I can still hear you okay everyone's so quiet like what JT left
Yeah, I mean, no, I can't come off. I can't come out because he's doing
You say why don't you say what he's like? Well, I just have to leave. Well, this why don't I just
We forever and this
All the all of that moment. He has to wait till you're back
He's still waiting, but he probably not we play has no patient. Come on. Hey, he was a joke. It's a joke by man
He's still there. Okay. I
see
Okay guys, we're back. We're back. He's back. Everything's fine. And we're back
Yeah, I was just being a dummy. I know why are you so reaching me?
Because you like it's like you like it when I'm rude I
Don't daddy
They did it fit
Who know I mean it's like it doesn't look like it has any different
I so I'll probably have to take it to the thing that it does have like a little why sit on a panel on mute for hours and hours
We're talking to me Memphis
Memphis, you're not talking to me. Are you I just modded. Oh, who's doing it? Who's saying that?
Oh, you're talking to
You're talking to KZ. Okay, I mean I just think he's very sure
You keep going
Yeah, thank you
Yeah, so guys if it doesn't work, I'll just I'll just return it in a Amazon's pretty cool with their policies
I did get finally some cigars. I got a lighter guys. You see my cool lighter. I got a cool lighter. Look
Look at I got
So Pete. Oh, it's a flamingo. Very nice. Yeah, isn't that cool? Is that a big order?
It's a big like your big I
Love them
Did you say you got cigars too?
Okay, well there so the cigarettes were too much
They were like because they're like $12 or whatever I already bought like five packs of them and say for five days
It's like ridiculous amount of money. So then I said, well, oh my gosh
I say I say well this has the backwards they have to back with them and then they let me feel it and they do but look
How disgusting look
It looks weird. It looks like you wrote a blunt. Do you didn't roll?
I was just
Did you
No, it's just disgusting. It's like disgusting tobacco. It's like just pure blood paper
I think the switcher was better quality. I'm just gonna like, you know, use it for like a little bit
I'll mix weed in there wherever or something. I have some weed to mix
So, I don't know. I'll just use a little bit. I'm trying to quit tobacco now
Tobacco is good spiritually though. Especially the Indians. That's what people in London do.
They'll take the weed and they'll mix it with tobacco and they smoke it like that.
Yeah, I don't like to mix it.
I like to mix it. I know I mean it's like I didn't notice when I first heard of smoking weed
like I was smoke weed and then I'd say we smoke a cigarette afterward.
We'd be like, oh my god, they're like, oh look the high is coming up and like the high would come up.
We just like feel like a little like a little boost. Yeah, like it makes you higher or something.
Yeah, this is a little bit. It was a little bit of a think think think is it kind of like a click here glasses
The post my picture in the finger go fuck your oh come on. Oh, I'm ever ever getting along
Yeah, Vicky or midnight where he means such a problem tonight midnight. You're gonna argue with the chat. Yeah, but isn't he always like that?
Well, I don't know. I don't think it's tonight. He's a little bit, you know rowdy, but I guess I do have I do have a
way to read
I'm just gonna read a little bit of it. I'm just gonna read like a little paragraph. It's called the way of the school
This is the beginning of this book. It's called like the call this zealot here
And it's a good initiation is the modern initiate explores the ancient mysteries
So this is my basically all the tarot and tying into all the occult. I'll just read the first couple pages. It says
It says, the way of the fool, it says, he will speak only of the things which are difficult
and not to be grasped by the senses, but indeed which are almost contrary to the evidence
of the senses.
So it's that's a formalius, archaeides, magica from the worlds of Parusha.
page 117. The way of the fool is the way of the independent traveler on the path of initiation.
Such a traveler may study under a variety of masters, yet will strive always to preserve
his or her identity and rarely undertakes vows of silence which will hinder his or her being in
the particular school or teaching. The fact of this traveling fool
is, on the path, is meant to reflect that he or she is following the way of the experience,
which is ancient Greek was formed, pathene, P-A-T-H-I-E-N, okay, pathene, says the path
of the fool is the way of the developing ego. In esotericism, the ego is the self.
Thus, self is a droplet of the universal mind, or Godhead.
The Sanskrit term Manus, which can be translated as the immortal individual, or the higher
mind, is the equivalent of the real ego.
It is the droplet of the Godhead, which is sought experience through involvement with
matter.
This minute particle of the Godhead is directed into matter in order to perceive itself or to gain experience in the realm of his own creation
There's a couple more paragraphs says because it holds this direct connection with the Godhead this fully developed ego is indestructible
However through the effects of incarnation and the and the consequent darkening through involvement in matter the human ego does
Not remain omniscient like the Godhead source
In this sense, in that as Cosmic Knowledge is limited by the hooding mask of selfhood,
the ego rarely works with its full spiritual potential.
From incarnation to incarnation, the ego dwells in what must be termed spiritual darkness
in comparison with the light of the spiritual planes.
Even so, it is possible for the ego
through its own efforts to regain its former full potential and to remove the darkening
self from its eyes. While in life, changing the physical body, the ego must work into
matter through the three organs or bodies called the esotericism, the astral, the ethereal,
the physical, of which we shall learn more shortly. These bodies are controlled by the
which the hermetic literature describes as a sweeping down from the spiritual world like a great bird,
a pelican, phoenix, or a swan,
huge well and flesh on the material realm.
The bird seems to be a curious one, for it has three wings rather than the usual pair.
Give us a couple more paragraphs. The ego is not entirely alone.
It is cast and dripped from the higher spiritual world.
It is accompanied by three higher spiritual bodies.
Paws invisible to the ordinary vision like the goddess Venus the ego is attended by three graces the trite of spiritual beings
Who we've a stately dance around her in these three beings?
We trace the three higher spiritual companions of the newborn ego in modern esoteric literature
These are titled the Arman the booty and the monos. That's enough for right now, but
Interesting
Because I've heard ideally what does that stuff mean to you what you just read?
But it means to me it's like well, it's like we begin a spiritual initiation
We come a journey and he's like you realize you're actually a
Spiritual being we're not this human body. We're the human body is a vehicle for this spiritual being which is
Almost identical to get connected to the higher higher God. Are you sure?
Oh, I'm certainly sure that's because that's why we hear God's voice. So we have this and that's why we're so powerful
We have this release the ego is attached to God people are being told to destroy the ego
When the ego is actually our spiritual power on this earth is having that being able to connect to the earth
Okay, so the way I understood it was the ego is like this in the sense of individuality and that basically like
God split himself into all these different people and they have to like transcend their
Yeah, we're we're talking about spirit. She is I'm here with your bullshit. What are you talking? Oh, she's in love with you, JT
No, the foot. No, she's not
Is this rain rain? Is this here rain? She's a girlfriend
Alabama here's a girl Obama Obama. Here's a girlfriend
Her name is rain
You'll put out your fire
Hold on hold on this is this is not woman out. This is destiny. I know you're right. You
This is destiny
That's not even
I'm so smart destiny
I'm so smart
Hey
Run over that cat. I'm a cat fanatic. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
What is going on here? Oh, what is this?
This beat it out is destiny
Beating your destiny be that your destiny. Oh, yeah plot twist
You are destiny. Yeah
Is this
Why are you carrying all these cameras?
Who is this?
This is barely even a fucking show.
This isn't Bita.
It's not Bita.
It's someone who has to beat a voice.
Who is this?
Who is it?
Wait, sorry you didn't kill a cat. I bet I was getting upset. I'm just kidding. Yeah, but I'm in love
Oh, you're like shit that explains everything. Is this Wendy? Is this Wendy the slow adult Wendy?
Is this you from the Howard Sturgeon Wendy the slow adult is and I'm in love with this Mexican guy with long hair
So
Can you fuck off
Yes, I mean, I'm gonna leave because if you can you like can you do it now though?
It's not destiny because destiny can really speak English, but
She's better at English, but you still need to work off
I'm just getting a horny on this show because
Get the fuck out of here
Sparrow things on me
Pita, Pita, I love you Pita
Do you like me? Like if you're into me, headset guy, like I'm into you, but I'm in love with you
Headset guy, headset guy, who is this guy?
Headset guy is gay, now get the fuck out of here
Where's Pita? What are you doing with her?
What are you doing with Pita?
Oh, now you have this whore?
Oh my, I thought that we were good to go and you're letting this fucking bitch
Don't call Pita
She
She shows to me those in her vagina. I've seen oh my god
No, she's not
Make this one way this one way to make ketchup guys. He's like, yeah, I do
I'm not trying to upset you
It sounds like beat a bit is like
Bitch you want to fucking go, you know
She went past all that
Yeah, who are you who are you?
I'm in love with someone who's married. Who is it?
I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him, I love him
Okay
Okay, no crying there's no crying in baseball
Apologize the page please. Hey, I'm sorry. I'm just you know, I'm upset and paid is a good girl. She's fine as fuck. She's fit
I wish I was Paige. I wish I had long blonde hair. I'm just a fat Hispanic lady who's in love with another guy.
No, you're not. Stop it. Stop it.
Who is this? Is this Kate? Kate?
I don't know.
Is this Diamond? Who are you?
What is Diamond?
I don't know. It's a funny name. I'm not a stripper. Destiny.
5,000 glows. Stig is one of you. It's one of you guys. Who is this?
My name's Hamburger. I'm a really good girl.
It says it says it says Alabama.
No, it says Obama.
You just can't fucking.
Oh, yeah.
You can get one card.
Yeah.
You are.
I think.
He says she wants to pull you apart.
I'm sorry.
Justice physically.
Hey, I think it's juice hall. Is it juice hall? It's juice hall on a he has a beta voice changer. That's crazy
I mean, I'm just like be there. I
Want to leave it would be useful
Guys plots with beta is juice hall. Oh shit plot twist. I was beat it all time. Oh my god
Plot twist this this is all a dream. This is all a virtual reality
Pull me a car so I can get up on the little G don't want to leave man
I mean we tell you something card page, please fuck you pull me a fucking car, please
Okay, you know I'll be back
Please I'm going I got it I got it covered
It's one fucking card.
Okay.
Is he in love with me back?
Oh no.
There was no one that will ever be like you.
But if something doesn't start moving forward,
you'll start to move on.
Wait, what was the first one?
You went too fast.
I can't read that fast.
No one will ever be you.
I thought I said no one will ever like me.
That's nice.
I'm getting out of here this
This show is very weird. Yep
He's so that was fucked up should have ever fucking encountered
Cool
You're muted
That's Bita playing a character, that's Bita was playing a character, that's her, yeah, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like,
Now I'm, I'm taking the Alexander route where I think it's all conspiracy.
Okay. Be this voice sounds different.
I know.
Is there some kind of voice changer involved?
I'm not sure.
It doesn't sound a little bit different.
Is that thing gone?
Yeah.
Right.
Wait, what thing?
That thing that was up here talking.
Oh, it'll be me. It'll be me. That was uh, it was beat his pick but not her boy
That was not beat his picture. That was a dozen. That was a black child
But buckwheat from a little rascal sure it was buckwheat. Yeah, it was buckwheat from little rascal good
Wasn't beta it was I think it was beta guys vote for who you think it was
It's like you on this one. I think that was beta
Yeah, is it a beta or that that that a destiny was like faking that she didn't know English
And that was a destiny and like destiny like really knows English really good
I don't know. I wish I wish you were right about that, but yeah
Now, Gotti's taking credit.
Oh, Gotti, come on.
Gotti's taking credit for it, Gotti.
I don't know, are you that good?
I want to hear you, I want to hear you
in the beat of voice next time you come up here to prove it.
Mystery guest, Galore, what's going on?
What does it say?
Time is, time is whole, I'll put it up, I'm just curious.
What is it?
It says time is-
Time is on your stage, bud.
Oh yeah, I got some, here, look, I got some too, guys.
I'm gonna bust off the stage.
Let's bust it out. I'm gonna bust it all over this panel. Hold on. It's so strange
Wasn't it? Hold on. Here we go. Look
What's that voice? That was I think it sounded like beat up, but I was like that and didn't like some of it's done
But it kind of did. Oh
That's what we do
There's one of your AI's yeah, he's laughing yeah, and I doesn't care
And that isn't care on but I mean it but oh come on guys
Should we tell yeah, tell me you guys tell me what tell me the story guys. What's gonna happen for next week
No, because if I tell if we tell you now it's gonna ruin the surprise
My god, let's burn my nail. Oh my god
Whoa, I got burns hey guys. That was a good sign though. I think when you burn yourself a little bit from the stage
It means like the the spiritual it's a good sign here is gonna work. It's a great sign
It's like purifying
Okay, you know, yeah, it's purifying you. I say yellow my color. I say yellow. What a color do you say guys?
I say yellow
But what are we picking a color for? Oh?
No, no, it was a feather on the big black one the big black to be be around the big black feather
This year BBS your big black feather a big brown feather
Whoo, hey, did you just only get my stage out and burn me? I'm never listening to you again
So are we doing some psychic stuff right now, or I don't know. I'm just staging cuz I was a really I'm just here. I know
No, I've
It was like a it was like a mixture of the two wasn't it? Yeah, I mean, it's like yeah
What kind of on a holy thing would that be
Parallel universe, I think the devil has to be involved somehow. Yeah, it was
She transcended her ego and she was like tapping into the god head, you know, like the book
Yeah
Well, that's how I feel like when I when I talk to myself sometimes I feel like
No, what's going on turn
What's that story like the seven faces of civil or something like you know civil like not civil shepherd
But there's some other civil and she had like all these personalities. Oh, yeah, she had like I forget how many yes
Why 21 or something thank you do you smoke even come?
Yeah, well, we do a lot of things. We're not supposed to. Yeah,
sir. Yeah, I mean, it's like supposed to. What's that? What
I mean? It's like, you know, it's like, what you're really not
supposed to do is hurt anybody or like to like, you know,
it's like, you know, it's like, you know, it's like, you know,
People wrong or like to be malicious and stuff like that. You're trying that you're supposed to help people
That's what you're supposed not you mean. I'm not any of that. Well, damn. I've been doing it wrong
Well
There's a song called post
Chris Brown
Okay, I got some I got some you know, that's fine now, but none of the miraculously healed
Amy's tab was in the chat. Yeah, smoke came out of it. It's on phonics. We're for me ABCDFC
Where is my feather? Yeah, my feathers my feathers are all put away
I'm making a making a set of angel wings. You want ice cream, too? Me, too
I mean, let's not page to cook. Let's page is cooking feather. Oh, let's let's all go
Anyways, it's almost out. So there you go. Okay. No one's cooking. Everyone deep breath. Everyone deep breath
Better bra, better boy
Relax
That nice everybody
You're I've been waiting for like the most invasive
Stage all right better boy. Yeah
Better boy constructor. You don't have psychic powers. Do you psyche?
I do I have very I have very strong psyche powers like very strong without the cars
Yes, but the cars are just the cars are there to like give a storyline to like give a focus because I
Will see like a lot of things at once and it's like where they go
I go because there's so much coming through so the cars give a focus of it, but they're not like the
They're not the whole thing. It's mostly intuition even what I read of the car is intuition
Hey, but that's like yeah, I think he's mad. I showed a giant turd did a night
Yeah, you did God you could have at least showed like you know a milky way or a milk does there's something in the toilet
You don't have to put a real piece of poop on my show. It's just disgusting. Okay. Everyone's disgusting everyone
Yeah, they're like reminds me Vita got mad when Gotti asked her she pooped her pants
Oh
Poop is not funny. Poop is not funny. It's not it's not it's no it's universally disliked. It just smells bad
It looks bad. It's horrible, you know
Got it. Got it. Do better
Do better. At least next time put it in a black toy so we don't have to see it.
Do worse. Do worse.
And I haven't. God, yes I haven't. I'm going to cry more.
I'm making operas. The tragedy, the comedy and tragedy of my show.
Just hope.
Oh, so la mia.
No, no, I don't know anymore. I'm sorry. Thank you. Come on. Can you on bad him dude? You promise nothing?
Who's in there? Who's a bam? There's not one person bam from the chat. Who? I'm gonna ban who?
You are?
No, I just wanted I just wanted to be included
Pages holding back. I don't pay pay the page that you want to say something to me for the past
He doesn't want you to tell me I mean
Hey, hey, you got that you got that I see you. I see your tongue. He's all over your tongue. You just keep it right there
It's gonna come out when these days we're gonna hear about I'm gonna hear about it
I want to hear though. They look like posters those little circular cards
They're tea leaves. They look like little pox like this. Well, like big
It's like a crime. God is not even banned. God is not banned. God is practically a mod.
I may make God a administrative mod. I'm basically an honorary mod at this point.
Yeah, but I might I might actually make gaudi's dinner mob
But he can watch over you. Yeah, I'm just gonna do that
If you have to watch your people and it's like gaudi if you disappoint me, you know
Last time I'm gonna give you a chance. Okay, you know as a mod you're not supposed to put some of my shows
Not supposed to be the no poop on my show gaudi. No, okay number poop
And you have to keep the JT in line and I'll make you I'll make you a month and then JT in line. What is this?
Yeah, you need a you need a handler GT. I mean, it's like gosh, I mean, it's like
Here it's got he's got he just you better go. You've got it. Don't disappoint me. Okay. Don't disappoint me, okay?
I guarantee you if you make me a mod you'll never regret it
Like for the third time. Why are you going out second?
God he says in defense of the kingdom he'll use it in the sense of you know
That said the psyche verse right is the psyche verse which includes you know the page verse
You know, like there's a lot of connected channels at the beta verse. There's like, you know
There's like the the bronze bird verse. There's
The bronze verse of the God you verse guys
There's there's this they say man
It's pointed by I
Would have had a black guy it would have been even better, but yeah, you're watching me. I'm watching you too states her
I'm watching you too. Okay. I have a
My your Alexa is feeding into my ear right now, and I don't like what you've been saying to Alexa
No, you're don't talk to her like that. You're being appropriate. Trust is earned. Yes, exactly. How do I?
Do you force skin backstage to get muck?
No, he's not so forced to get he got he got he circumcised
My fault everyone was bitching about me in the beginning. Is that my
You give up psyche I'm so carry about my channel as a what I think that is what are you talking about?
No, see that is he's called
What's happening thing?
Here's what I'm saying is it gotty. Oh, I think that is if you want to be a monster, but I'm saying is gotty
Mod party got you can like keep
The crew in line, you know, it's a crew. There's no crew. What is this? Yeah, there's there's a discord. Omish. Omish
It's called like that. I've been there the Amish adventures
at for the for the
Latter-day Saints Church
and
The morning it's called it's called it's called what is it called a cabal or it's what it's a word. It's called a cabal
Yeah, the discord
What's it called guys? Basically a word for it. It's a cold. Yeah. It's a cold. There's obsessed with
harassing me harassing me. So a Goddy. That's why it got it
I'm watching. I'm watching you guys. Watch me too. Well, I'll watch you
Okay
Watching me
well
Nobody's watching you because you're not doing anything that interesting
So why shouldn't I what the why do I need a handler if I'm not doing anything wrong?
Because because you're so misbehaving in the audience, and I know I can't have like the audience
Yeah, I can't I can't yeah the all thing I thought he and I thought he knows that he knows
Wow, I gave a shit. I'd be insulted right now
Oh, okay. Well, so stay with me. It's a ditto ditto. Do you want me to kick you off? No, no sit here be very nice
Okay, I'm not gonna kick you off the big thing. No. Oh, you want to be
Okay, then you have like the you know, like a weird bird and a werewolf
Looking like they're gonna make a snack out of us
Well, at least out of me
They're gonna leave you alone
They're like, you know the bird like my flesh
Why is Vader alive? Hey, it does come back
We all see a brown eye. Well, my eyes are green. You know green my eyes
That's right, dude. They look very green. Don't they? They're kind of magical tonight. Hey, we have Chris K back guys
Let's get spicy
No, what's up?
Hi
Hey page what up?
Nothing what's up with you I
Was trying to get hold of you
Have that work out what happened pages page has a private mind you have to just talk to on the show in the chat
And then you know, so you should get back to you
You don't have an Instagram well you should get one get one real quick
Why why do I need one? I don't know. I don't want to give you my phone number
But like I want to like you know, I want to be able to like talk to you
Put it put in the bag check. Yeah, Chris. Okay, but in the bike shop. I won't share and she seems really interested
Is it like about a reading?
No, yeah, it's about a reading. Yeah, if you ever come to Vegas, I said like, you know, hit me up
Oh
You want to see that you want to see that recount the cards because you can as you're good at cars
You can count the cards in Vegas have some blackjack
Well, no, I almost I almost like on Fremont
Dude, there was this dude
I knew that we were gonna get a rent a circle because you have to rent circles and we were gonna reach our cards for like donations
Well, you should yeah, that's really I guess you can do that you can get business licenses
Use it better than me reading them and I was gonna like try to bring people in type shit
Yeah, yeah, he's a barker and stuff like that. He got it. That's my thoughts exactly
Yeah
Bader wants page. Well, Bader, I don't know if page goes that way because I heard Bader is a beautiful woman also page
Do you see Bader's picture? She's very hairy. I just I see this here because Harry is a
No, no, no the baby
Yeah, Vader is a she-wolf and then it's like you're like a Teen Wolf well you're kind of like Vader is a man
No, no Vader's a woman a beautiful woman. She told us today
Is that what he told you?
Yeah
Yeah, I think earlier you've heard to that as my girlfriend that that's definitely not
Well, I just asked if that was rain because she was like totally into you
You're just very you're just very you're very attractive to anybody
I want to bite out of you too, JT
I
Get the full moon today guys the full moon tonight guys
I gotta stay in the house
But like I don't want to hang out with anybody and I live in Canada. I'm just going through a divorce
So I don't really want to hang out dudes
You can hang out with me Chris. You know, but you like you you know, they want to creep in while you're vulnerable and you don't want that
It was for you psyche he was talking to you
You know what I'm not even gonna ask, you know, I've got it in here. I need a handler. Yeah. Hey, what's up, Pat?
Hey, what's up? Oh, yeah, my name. I love the name Pat. You know, is it a guy or a girl?
Everybody knows this, but instead of life, it's Julie. Hey, well, you know, I think, I think like, uh,
Canadians like hate Americans now or whatever. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, they do not. They do.
They're all really butter and sensitive lately over with the Trump stuff.
They love Trump.
They seem to love Trump.
They love you.
They yeah, yeah, but some you know, some don't I mean they like they like it. I mean nothing. They love it
Hey, there's America. Can we have a moment of silence for Chris? He looks down about that. Okay, Chris. What's wrong?
Okay, I
Will never do you like a woman with you, you know women break guys. I'm really sorry
I'm just like not ready to like for anything like I just don't want to hang
I mean if I you know if I come to Vegas Monday, maybe we can chill, but like I'm not
I'm just like, I'm just going through emotions and I'm like, not really wanting to, I'm not interested in anything.
I don't know, yeah. I don't know your situation and I respect like your, uh, whatever you got to do with the type of shit, you know, just, I, I can't imagine like somebody, you know,
Instagram, Instagram, you have no social media.
Well, yeah, because I don't, I don't know. I don't, I only have like Snapchat and Facebook and YouTube.
Yeah
Text you off just trying to like just trying to get in your pants, you know
She's gonna start doing the stream yards and then you're gonna be able to talk to her backstage or her stream yard
Okay and establish a emotional connection with you maybe one day getting your pants is that okay?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, that's guys. That's not what you do to women. That's all you want to do
They know they know that game for a mile away unless you're really really really cute
They're not here to give you them a day, but I am not really really cute and it does work. I like her style
Do you know she's kind of like cool?
Yeah, read the room guys in the room Wow
Because here Chris are you an asexual Chris K a sexual what he is now
I
Okay, Chris. It's okay. It's okay. Chris. No matter what you say you're not gonna be you're embarrassed of yourself as much as Mr.. Big Pikes embarrassing
Well, he doesn't have any sense of shame, so he doesn't even know he's doing it. It's great
Okay, I'm sitting up is that an indestructible mod you got there
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Let's page. Uh, hey, read my
page. Please, please, ma'am.
Page gave me a pretty good
reading. Can you read mine?
You know, I still haven't, you
know, Chris K is asking. Sure.
Read, read mine. I want to see
You give me vibes
Off on you even though you're not interested would that be okay could I what?
He wants you he wants a reading
Yeah, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he
Well, I'll give her I'll give her the name right now. I want to see if she can see what it is. No, she's not in her head
No, well, it's not it guys. It's not really it's not a guess in games. If you guys have to fuck up. Oh
Wow
People I don't know who you're dealing with but there's two people I want to say like I'm just seeing
I don't see their, I don't see fate.
I know it's a male and a female energy.
There's two people, I don't know what's going on,
but like it's something to do with your heart chakra or.
Sleepless nights. I'm not sure what's going on. Like are you going through something yourself? Are you are you kind of?
seeking
Freedom or new something within your like are you in a relationship or did you have a relationship just recently that went south because or like were you interested?
Or did you get like was it third-party energy because I'm really feeling like
I'm just seeing I'm seeing two people and they're just like they're the way that they're moving around you is like
It's a deceitful. Yeah, they're not they're not my they're our relationships, but yeah
Okay, um, I don't know what you were working with them on or what the you know the dynamic of this
Friendship partnership whatever you want to call it was but I do feel like
Everything that your intuition was telling you this entire time you were absolutely right about but I know that they lied to your face
quite a few times
I mean, I mean they uh, yeah, I mean because they didn't know type shit. Yeah, you're getting a kind of little bit
Like fucking I proved them wrong, you know, don't let me fucking don't let me fucking, you know fucking be everybody
Tell me I couldn't do it. I fucking did it like what look look now. So that's it
What'd you say what I couldn't do I couldn't do something what oh, yeah, what happened? Yeah, I did it
a little baby with a rhino. Yeah.
Let me tell you real quick. Like
my my stepdad dude he passed away
right my stepdad used to read this
is his cards. Here we read a
terror cards for the like the
one eight hundred number for like
you know like you know.
You watch your forecast let me know if you're a pre-reading right he worked for that company and these were his cards
He taught me how to do it and fucking I have other brand new cards like you those ones you have I
Can't do it unless I use the ones that my stepdad
these ones these are old school and
It only works with these so and like I said
He's like he's like I haven't had dreams. He's like telling me to do this
Like you know what I mean? He's like, you know be and after he passed away, so he's like telling me like I
And I have like little like words that I put on this shit that the fucking it's not me
It's like he's helping me from another fucking
Dimension like after he passed away type shit and like fucking
Your source of channel first through him
Yeah, and I'm not gonna fight it or whatever everybody says. It's like evil or whatever like I'm not gonna like fight it
It's not evil at all. It's not evil. That's what I'm saying. I'm just gonna let it flow
You know me so that's it and like a fucking I say it's a way that's the same way I read cards
I let it go and I'm not gonna like fight
Like because people are like so scared everybody's scared. I'm not I'm ready to like do whatever
You know me so that's it
Like I'm not I'm ready to like just like whatever. Let's go like I'm fucking I'm I thought I say what I say everything
So yeah, I mean that's it
But these cards are shot dude like these card look how the fuck it's all fucked up
But I can't read the other ones, but these ones work
So yeah
Yeah
the interesting
forgiveness
abundance
Faith
Acceptance and mysticism. So what we have here is
You going through exactly what you just you just said except for a little bit differently, you know, there's
You having these channeling gifts now that come through you through him it's very much
What happened here like this is not this is totally it's not a topic because it means something
But there's something to do with this here like I'm not sure what your childhood was like, but it's like
trying to find like be a different person than
Then you were like
Being something that you're either you're breaking chains or you're
Or you've fallen into patterns that were inevitable, but also like made
Changes and created abundance from from the loss like you've found forgiveness in your heart for most situations
So and like look at this man here
It's just a matter of having the right, you know guides and spirit guides, you know
One thing I would say is like your temper work on your temper. So like having that forgiveness and having that like
acceptance of others, you know, and and what
Whether there's a good or bad outcome like I feel like, you know, don't let it
Wait, go that go put that one. That was what's his name psych that was psych right there. Look see
I'm just a joke
No, it's funny, but just have faith in yourself like and and just believe in yourself like you're doing and I feel
Like everything that you are doing to move forward from here on out because I think you've had a you know
A little bit of a rough life like most of us
You've learned a lot so it's been easy for you to start accepting things seeing them differently
Forgiveness and acceptance and having faith makes room for abundance to come in and grow all constantly, right?
Whereas if it's the opposite, then we're just shut down and darken out of the soul, so
That's my only choice. You see to that or like death like death
You know we have creation so the creation of this mysticism comes from acceptance and faith and
Forgiveness and abundance comes with all of that
Okay, just let me I'll just do like one or two of these. I like your nails. What what kind of nails you got?
They are like holographic black and red
So we have birds so news is on the way
So if you've been waiting for some news, which I think you have some good news, hopefully
It's on the way. It'll be there soon. Oh, yeah
Yeah, it's a it's a long story for my shit, but yeah, it's fucking you know, everything's everybody's got their own their own situation, you know
All right, what those are like couple this there like posters
They're really they're really hard to use they're actually okay, so the ear what did I say good news? Hopefully so it is good news coming
That's a gross card. It's a dirty old ear. Yeah. Yeah, right
Okay, well, we're gonna pick those up, but we have romance celebration and party so whatever this good news pertains to is maybe something releasing of
I'm not sure. Maybe you're gonna you're growing from the situation that you felt love and that is kind of didn't work out
Or if you love for something, it doesn't have to be a person.
Oh my God, I'm always under the fucking table.
Okay, it doesn't have to be a person.
You know, it could just be like the love for something,
like creativity, passion for something.
Well, hopefully it's like, you know,
I could talk to you like, you know, off stream,
like something like that.
That's not what it's about.
So like, you know, celebrating maybe this good news
that you're gonna get, it doesn't have to be romance based.
It's just this is romance, celebration and party.
feel like you're gonna celebrate this good news that you have coming. I feel
like you're very much going to celebrate it. It'll give you a reason to maybe go
out. I don't know if you haven't in a long time. So look it. Okay, so compliments
from an admirer. Oh, trouble accusations. Interesting. So be careful with this
situation. I suppose increase your efforts if you want to achieve your goals
with the boot.
the box, you will receive a gift. So you definitely have good news on the way, you're
gonna have a deep friendship with someone of the same sex, you're going to
receive a gift and you're gonna receive it rather quickly, but there's going to
be some trouble that comes with it so just be just be mindful of it, it's
nothing scary, it's just gonna be there a thing that you can't avoid. And I will
So, you know, if someone's coming at you in a situation that makes you feel good and with your good news or whatever your gift that you're going to get or the celebration, like, don't be tempted to lower your standards if someone else is trying to ruin your vibe, right?
Yes.
And we'll finish up with one more and then I will move on to the next one.
It's moving everywhere.
Okay, so January.
We have a month to come out.
So I don't know if that's significant to you as of the past or in general or if it is going to be a prediction
So what do you think my birthday is?
January
Is it September is coming out as well? So
We've got Capricorn and Virgo energy
And we have the
What sign do I think you are did you start tell me your birthday's in January?
No, I
Think that you're a fire sign. I think you're a Leo or an Aries
No, we're interesting Sagittarius. No, I'm not gonna keep playing the guessing game
Weirdness I don't know them
Got me stumped water sign you're a water sign
Water Pokemon water Pokemon. That's my guess
Are you a fucking are you Scorpio? Nope. Okay, that's a fire sign isn't it? No, that's not a fire sign
What is it water? Yeah
Okay, so we have the diamonds, so you'll be receiving this gift soon, you have a new creative idea and new adventures and a fresh start with like a job or a career, problems that will be resolved, so it looks pretty good for you in the next coming months.
I mean, I would keep January and September in mind too, for sure, because they definitely have some significance.
Great
Because I don't think you have any specific questions, I didn't feel any in your energy I think that
You're pretty open to just hearing what anything that was what do you think my my stepdad's name is
I'm gonna try to give it to you right quick. Let me go ahead. I don't know
I just heard Ron or something in my head like with an hour, but I don't know if that's correct either
often
Does it start with an R?
Okay.
Does it start with a C?
No.
I don't know then, honestly, I got Clark and I got Ron, so.
Well, Clark, I live in Clark County.
Nevada?
Yep.
What's that a say it right buster? Nah
It's a Hispanic name it's Navarra
Thanks, Paige
I could give you a channel like medium reading I'm not gonna do that on here though. It's not really like my favorite place to do it
I'll just have to like watch for you on here. Whatever like I know you're going through like a situation or whatever
But yeah, I want to like talk to you more
She's just I mean what else am I supposed to you know, I think she said in like 50 million ways. No already
So you don't do the you don't do the in-depth ones here
No, no, because it's just like
It's a different kind of reading it's
Personal it's super like it can be a super emotional one when you're doing this stuff like oh
I like the one you gave me. Yeah
Thought you were spot-on. I'll have to do it next time when you
When you're doing it on your channel
Yeah, it's a little bit different on my channel. It's cuz it's
You seem to be more open and less frustrated on that day though
Pardon?
You seem to be in a better mood that day like
more receptive
Yeah, Hannah that was Tiffany that said you got your nips cut off by the way. That wasn't me
Chris, why do you I'm getting a little feeling you seem so agitated. What's going on, brother?
Who's upset? What's going on? You seem a little agitated. I'm getting a vibe from here. You they're not like you talk or what?
You talking about Chris?
Yeah, Chris
You know
You know, maybe she doesn't want you to see her now. So, I mean, I don't know why you're agitated about it
She could go ahead and say
Fuck you. I don't want you to see I mean tactically she's she'd never say that but I just they're not nice
I have to go get them done. They're all growing out. But so they're they've had them for like five weeks
Ghost how the fuck are you?
Good
Good, where's Jamie age? How are you doing good? How are you?
gray. I'm feeling pretty good. I'm over my little illness I had.
What's good?
Stuffed up for like, dude, like past like week, I don't even know what it was.
I ran a fever a couple of days, but I don't know.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
I was on the panel trying to talk and I was like,
I think that's not horrible. That's not what I was like, oh gosh.
It's definitely in a better mood do when I'm sick I get cranky dude. I get I'm short tempered when I get sick
I don't know why I am too
Maybe I feel like it's like when a woman's like like when they're on I why can't even say that
But you know when they like you ask them a simple and they snap on you because they're going through a certain thing
That's how I am when I'm sick and like why do you just why do you just like say like why do you just like yeah?
I was like I wasn't yelling first of all, but why did I raise my wife? I don't know
Then I'm back to bed, Hannah. You're really creepy. Oh, that's a handsome man
Who which one this this
A drunk bait or hello
Yeah, we're all shit-faced
Sure, we just ask that question
If anything, I have this little pink dick out top of my head.
I wouldn't, I wouldn't even trust a, I wouldn't trust a way that says,
don't worry, I'm not gonna port bomb you.
Hey, what the fuck are you even bringing it up for?
Ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, that's, that's...
Don't worry, I'm not gonna debate you.
I don't think I've ever seen you debate anyone about anything.
Actually.
Well, we never, I mean...
You have to join other you'd have to I'd have to like
By the way, well, why does he sound so loud right here? You're hurting my ears right now. All right, just throw your volume
I'm pretty sure you can turn that motherfucker down to you
Would you like me to explain it?
No, I don't I don't know all right. I just have all the fucking cars
In order to get the right ones I came here for a reading from page. That's this is exactly what I came here for
30 bucks
30 bucks. That's too much. Hey. Yeah much. Well, she said 60. I'm saying 30. So you give me a little bit talking by the way
I'm sorry. Who's talking?
That goes when I do you see do you see my do you say it move in do you see it move in when people talk you see out moves
I've done it plenty of times what would be the point of doing that
Because I don't know if you're a female do you even have a plate do you have a camera?
I have my picture on right now. I have my picture. This is what I look like. All right. Okay, cool
I'm not trying to ask a question about what you yeah
This wondering is Lord Vader
Are you like a disingenuous asshole, or are you a fucking retard like which one is it? Why couldn't even go?
That's actually a really good point
He's probably both
Oh, you see you see now you piss Chris off. He doesn't you see what you guys are
well
It's when you join
Anyways, I was here for Paige and you guys were just ruining Chris you do readings too. Yeah
You could you do you got powers?
Yeah, yeah, you're psychic. Oh, okay. This guy's good. I'll do it for free
I don't know if you have I don't know if you have powers though coast your powers listen
I am shuffling. Let me mute up real quick. I am shuffling my deck Lord. I will give you one free reading
Alright, no, no, let's get it. Let's get it from K first Chris K. Chris K. Let me let me get a reading
Ghost I like you but you're an attention
Chris can I can I get a reading man? Yeah, I mean let's I do
Ghost no, he doesn't actually read he's not a reader. He's just fucking her up
I would know I did pull one card. Do you want to know what it says?
Lord what's the what's it? It's not your reading. It's not your it's his reading the fuck
Just hurry up and say it so we can get past this
No, you want to Chris go ahead. He's got the card. Oh, I mean Chris is actually holding a deck in his hand, so
You're eating meat. It's werewolf. Yeah
Yeah, like instantly change werewolf, you know, yeah, it's a full moon full moon. Yeah
Are you sucking all down?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I'm letting him do his thing two or three supples. How many?
However, however many you need man, whatever you think is right. You gotta make the choice
What type of tar cars are you? How about three? Let's do three three shoppers
Can you be quiet and let the wolf may get his reading?
Shut up, bro. How about you shut the fuck up and let him know?
Yeah, you can do three actually the card. I pull it. It's like you want to shut the fuck up
What type of what type of cards are those by the way, Cheryl cards
I'm they are tail cards. It's different. It's different kinds. Alright, I pulled two of them the first one said you wouldn't shut the fuck up and the second one said you were a dumb dumb so I'm pretty sure I'm correct and I'm pretty sure my car's talking. Who's talking about it? I don't even know who that was talking about it. Stop asking me. Alright.
So we're gonna, before we start this reading, I'm gonna ask everybody, what is everybody sipping on tonight? We'll start with Ghost. First of all, I'm sipping on some scissor. Yeah, okay, Ghost. Champagne of beers, brother.
Okay, I got more too, but okay, and I get the impression Denison's not sipping on anything
Correct. Okay. Of course. Now. He's just about that reading. Yeah sober individual
He's doing a really high
Champagne of bears you would know that if you weren't a degenerate he's doing reading now
Do you like your job or whatever it's like something with your hands?
No
Like what was it with the grease like you guys like you get greasy
No, we need page. I'm sorry. We need page King page. Can you come up one more second? We need a better radio
Well, it's his reading
Here's the thing you fucking you just the something like what happened in your life right now. It's like crazy change something like recent, right?
I don't know you tell me and then but here's a year fucking I don't know where you live
But is it by the by the coast or you're trying to go there and I don't know if you're gay. Are you gay?
No, he's definitely gay.
That's for sure.
No, you got that right.
That's accurate.
You know some gay people and you fucking...
No, I'm gonna go.
You talk a lot and you have something but you're...
Is it your dad?
Your dad is fucking with you right now for some reason.
And I had a game with the water.
Oh my god. He's actually accurate. Can you show the cards to the camera when you're in those? Yeah, your dad fucked you in the ass. That's right, JT, you're hurt, yeah.
Vader, could you be any gay right now, please?
Yeah, I don't know what I'm saying. I knew it. The Wuffman is gay. I knew it.
It's like you want me to be gay Jesus, which one says he's gay all those
Honest with you, but so far everything you've said is super super accurate. I'm not shitting on your abilities. I'm just saying
I don't know. It's like when you get a it's like when you get a therapist and they suck
Company went down in your life right now. They went down. Can you pull the closet card, huh?
I think you could let him go let him continue sounds like somebody's in the key shut up, bro, please
No, I think you like you know a listen dude like, uh, you know, I'm not a homophobe, bro
If it you know if you if you like to cause it because like cock-blocked you from what you were doing page. Is that why I'm gay?
No, I'm bad
You think about it you think about it you have something that you fucking something you might have like did like a couple times
With somebody you feel like it's like a happy about it. Sounds like you want me to be gay
Wait, wait, wait
He says you're gay he says that he says hey, you also said
I didn't say maybe you fucking you feel like you almost like you got like some connection with somebody that's like
You know, maybe you like that like like, you know
But you know
Maybe you could maybe you could shut up while he's talking maybe I agree
It's
Go ahead
I want to shit on this powers right now, but so far I'm not not really resonating as they would say
You know what it is, you know what it is like fucking you are like thinking about you know like
like
Coming out of closet, but your dad is gonna fucking trip if he knows about it
Is that what it is? And that's that's a town that's you have to climb that
Is this you projecting under the guise of a terror reading right now relax bro. Just let him finish the fuck
You've got the fuck. I'm not talking to you
I mean, I wouldn't really shit on hand there
They're biggest like fucking their greatest warrior to already left what should be paid just like the destiny of this world
As soon as we joined she took off which I was I was actually not even trying to talk about any of this
I was just having a fun time hanging out on the panel
Like you there's there's somebody that
Well shit, it just keeps intensifying right the gayness just keeps fucking humping us
I mean, here's the thing like I you know, I you know, it's I don't want to like
If it's if I'm wrong, then I'm wrong or whatever but I'm not trying to like
Imagine you're actually
Like you're shooting blank man. We're all gay here dude. You know, I'm not fucking. I don't care dude, you know
Are you gay? Is that what it is? Did you just say we're all gay here? I'm fucking, you know, I'll you know, I'll just
Nobody you're fucking all
Wait, wait, are you just did you just say you're everybody's gay here including yourself? What kind of a gay reading is this?
Look man, are
What it are you try to tell us you're fucking gay. What is this?
I'm not a homophobe
Well, you couldn't be if you're fucking dudes, right?
Right, I mean that would be a weird position to be and I mean, I guess it's logically possible, but Jesus Christ
I mean, you know, you can be a self-hating gay basic, you know prison print people go to prison for life
You know, they do weird stuff
What is your I mean, I guess it's possible. What is your dad do? What's your dad do?
Fuck you guys do
Just gay porno
You're always you're always up you're always a concern about your dad like what he's gonna think
So Chris, how's your relationship with your father
My my real dad died in prison and my stepdad died
Well that explains it
For that it really doesn't
So your real dad died in prison your stepdad what?
You died like they were like six years ago of cancer cancer. And were you close to your real dad?
I was the closest one. I
wrote him like at least once a month and
I have a brother
That fucking I was over here like trying to like fucking
You know do all this shit. I'm like you didn't fucking write him
I was the one that wrote him.
Are you gonna cry about it now?
Like, fuck you, come on.
Emotional.
Did he know about your proclivities?
My cliff, was it?
Did he know about your tendencies?
What tendencies?
Your tendencies?
I'm not gay, dude, that's what you mean.
I mean, did he know though?
My dad?
Yeah.
I wrote I do I wrote them and here's the thing bro. It's a whole it's a whole conspiracy, dude
Yeah, I don't know we wrote him
It is a great idea midnight
Can you continue on with your game ready?
Well, I don't know the day he I don't know if it's like that's not fair. Let's not bully the guy he didn't
He's literally telling you he's not gay
Like I don't agree with the tarot reading but like
Arguments and I will definitely fucking argue with him all the time
But don't call him gay because there's nothing he said that was gay. Did he call you gay?
No, he asked if I don't know what the fuck he asked something about gay, but don't call him gay cuz
You're trying to you're trying to gang up on the boy, and I don't even like the guy, but I'll fucking you send him
Okay, I don't think either of you I don't think any of you here are smart enough to have the argument
So you're not gonna boy this dude for no reason let him let him read his thing. Let him finish his
No, he already read it. It's over. He read it. Yeah, you fucking you said like that when you were younger when it's three against one
That's what that's when it's kind of
When you were younger you had it really asked them like are you gay? Are you gay? Why are you good? Why are you good?
Motherfucker said he wasn't gay
like how many times he's answering the question
don't ask it 50 or more times
I didn't even say he was gay
okay boy if you're gonna make proof
you're gonna make the claim to burden the people on you
and I'll burden that ass up because you don't have to fucking ghost
stop bullying him
he gave you a little reading which was bullshit
I don't believe in terror reading you guys know that
but don't sit there and keep saying the same shit
it's not even your fucking reading
because Vader you're a fucking retard
you don't have to fuck your time
He's doing it. He's doing a gay reading fucking JT or a relax. Yeah
Let him finish his thing reviewer when you used to have a really good relationship with your dad and back when you were younger, right?
Yeah, I've always had a good relationship my father
Okay, so that's the one you're always like you you're afraid to like do you know, I don't know if it's being like a
I don't even know if it's gay. Maybe it's something else.
What are you trying to hide from your dad?
That's what it is. You're hiding something. I don't know what it is.
It's fucking maybe...
Something that you yeah, I'm hiding the bodies in my fucking freezer. Well, you've got something you got me
But if you tell him he's gonna be like that what how you know something like that or whatever
He's gonna trip like fucking you try to like you're trying not to I don't know what it is
And I don't care, but yeah, you're trying to protect it and
But you fucking something happened like hardcore
How hardcore was it?
Was it really hardcore?
Yeah, I mean he was like
I got hurt. I don't know what would you do with some guy that he's so full of that hurt
We'll go hard
Some how does your father die in prison by the way?
curious
That I mean they say it was uh, he got COVID in there, but uh
He was all he was like fucking like 80 years. He was 80. Wow. He had you late
Yeah, me like yes
Yeah, but that's what I'm saying like I uh
At least he got the you know, it's a long story, bro. I'll tell you let me finish the curvy sure sure
Well, yeah, yeah, um, so the what I'm getting so far is my holy shit here we go
Chris was a psyche up here earlier when you were up here
He left when you got a young panel
Yeah, I think Chris on here, but I think Chris tried to hook up with Paige and not psyche
So you calling him gay is kind of weird. It's not
He wasn't calling him gay he was just doing a reading you fucking retard
Look, can we let the man finish his reading? I mean I'm done
You know your dad you look to your dad like you're scared to do something with your dad
Scared to do so.
Is that your, is that your reading, Chris, for real?
I gave you an outing.
Come on, we need Paige.
Jesus, Chris.
Come on, I'm trying to help you, brother.
Well, I know I'm trying to stop and defend you.
That's not what I meant.
Hey, listen, listen.
Hey, you know, I was, I was, so...
No, I mean, you're, you're, something you're...
No, I did, I did ask him for a reading, so...
I guess he gave me one, but...
He did give you one.
There you go.
Chris, I'm trying to have your back.
Come on now.
You didn't even take my fucking...
Yeah, dude.
You know what Chris uh
Like you have some shit going on where I don't know what you're trying to hide from your your dad because it's something that you done
I'm going to beat the gay away.
All right, Chris, you gave it the old college try, man.
I'm not going to.
Tell your dad this shit.
He's not going to want to be as friendly.
I did give you an escape plan, though, Chris.
You didn't take it.
No, go and try to help you out.
Now you just, now you do.
Oh, shit.
That was that was something. All right, that was
Something beautiful reading round of a box
No, it was definitely a reading
Well for what it yeah, thank you for the reading
Great for shit. So basically I'm doing it in my dad wants to beat my ass
What what no, please just talk over me. That's great
Yeah, but I mean you're gonna call a court or what? I think he was looking at cards
Listen, I'm not shitting on your tarot abilities, but I think
Anybody but you would probably be better at it. I'm shitting on you. I mean you can't I don't care who you are
You can't try to predict something that's in the future
Maybe you can try to say what's in the past, but obviously you're shit at it
And it's gonna happen like if I ask somebody questions, obviously something's happened to you in the past
You're not gonna predict shit like well, I think in next month. You're gonna be
Again, I'm not shitting on it
Regardless of what I say they're gonna say they're gonna be like nope that's wrong and they're gonna make fun of it
I feel like they're regardless so I'm right or wrong. I'm not making fun of it. I'm not making fun of it
I'm not shitting on it
Listen, I'll put it. I'll say it a nice way. I don't resonate with it. Right. Isn't that what people say?
I don't it doesn't resonate with me. So
I appreciate the reading you did you did what I asked. I asked you for a reading you gave me a reading
That you're fucking by like by like you like you like kind of gay you have a gay vibe
Do you want me to be gay? Like what's going on with you? It ain't me. No, it ain't me. It's fucking your card said that
That's all i'm saying if it ain't I don't think the card said it. I think it was you
You're you're like fucking tripping because you don't want people to know about it. So that this is happening before
I'm not tripping. I said thank you for the reading. I mean, I'm trying to be I'm being polite, right?
I was being nice people like they say I'm wrong, but it's like I just I just what do you want me to say man
I said, I don't resonate with it. What do you want me? You want me to lie to you? Oh, yeah
Thank you, Chris. I resonate with everything you said you want me to lie to you or you want me to tell you the truth
Well, you don't want you know, you don't want to admit, you know, cuz you're like still in the closet Chris
You know what this is a really about you didn't like me cock-locking you with Paige
That's what you didn't like so of course you're gonna give me some bullshit reading about me being gay
We didn't like you being there was definitely cock-locking the fuck out of you because she wasn't interested
Well, yeah, yeah, that's being a weirdo. They're not interested. You keep doing I mean stop
So just say that you know
I don't hate you I don't even know you man
I don't think you're a bad guy you just coming off a little desperate and the woman clearly wasn't interested in your bits
That's all simple. I mean if you want to fucking
say a mother fuckers gay because
Because I told you the fucking sir in the closet of being a creep Chris
Dude, I mean the shit was coming off desperate man. You won't listen you need a you need somebody to tell you the truth
You don't want me to lie to you. Do you want me to lie to you Chris?
Or do you want me to be honest with you well, like the last time I last time I talked to her
I wanted to like get her Instagram or whatever and I remember she doesn't want to fuck you
Doesn't want anything. She does. She's not interested. Yeah fucking. She's not interested. I'm not gonna be rude
She's not okay. You know, at least I got to like I would say better luck next time
But if there was a next time look man, I did your favor think about it
I did your favor. I saved you a lot of time a lot of a lot of embarrassment. Good logic. You're welcome
Yeah, you know, I tried to let her know if you see her once come to Vegas
I got with like you're still it's over. It's not talking about it. You're making yourself a little weirder
Entertainment
So again, I enjoyed it. I I don't think you guys
Yeah
Simple, you know we everybody gets rejected, but you got to realize when you get rejected because men approach women correct
You get rejected time to you don't keep going especially when you're doing bad
Right
Yeah, it's all good you're right well your tarot reading is a little shit you need to work on that, but you're all right
I mean, if you're going to learn how to con, I mean, to become a con man, there's a lot of work that needs to be done. It's like becoming a magician.
Yeah, honestly, I've been a little sloppy with my shit, but I haven't been focusing on it.
If you're flirting or with your tarot reading?
My tarot reading. I haven't really been focusing, you know.
I mean, you're a battle-good tarot. You're with women, huh?
I didn't say that. We're trying to be nice over here. I'm so I'm being about as nice as I could be
Well, god damn
Yeah, thank you, why don't you abandon your panel like this? Yeah, what happened psych?
No, I'm not I'm supervised in front of the next stage
Summoning you I was about to show my dick and get you bad right now. Oh, you were I was gonna
What do you think like this you be years became like immediately weirder dude. I was like
Yeah
So
Locked up in County jail with Chris K. I would take a shower with him
And we might, we might, we might, we might sit together at dinner once in a while and you know, we might occasionally, I mean occasionally call him daddy and that's all, that's all I'll say.
Okay, I'm just kidding.
Okay, God.
It's a joke.
Okay, okay guys.
I know I like take it was because I dated a peckerwood. So I already I've already been through that data
I did it one of you one of you guys like you got that you got the the radar, right?
Yeah, you think about Chris here. Yeah, the peckerwood radar peckerwood. Oh
Chris would not my
I think you'd I think you'd experiment just just one
He would fuck around with me a lot of people a lot of people with a lot of people, you know, like most people would
Most people you guys you had never had a little experience in the locker room or and you know, it's your your best friend when you're
You know, because he's not even denying the general
Chris that's you say that's you're cuter to deny or defend yourself
Well
I was I'll defend you here because I will defend you. I don't know what you say
I'll defend you. You're a straight man. It guys here. But if I was a straight we can identify as whatever we want to and
And I believe it's a real man. I think yeah, yeah, you have one pregnant, didn't you? Can I say this? Can I say this?
I mean, I don't know if it's a lie. You know, I'm just gonna say, you know, I'll be down to like
You know because you could probably like pull chicks like better than me like pull chicks, right better than me, right?
Are we down like, you know, like do like that threesome type shit is a nice game. It's confirmed
Okay. Well, let me too. So let's let's let's hang out soon
Let's go to have a threesome with you psych basically. That's the devil's threesome brother when he got two men dumb dumb
Okay, guys guys. Nobody's in there. You're another word about it
It's like, you know, you know, I'll hit it from behind or whatever vice versa
and like the same time, like fucking hit that bitch,
like that shit.
Okay, it's getting way too gay up here.
Okay, no, no, no, this is what the devil's doing.
No, I like this conversation.
I like where this conversation is.
You know what?
When Chris is gayer than Psyche, there's a fucking problem.
No, guys, guys, you know that there's like the most,
the most hood, like the most like masculine,
like, you know, hood people I've ever seen in my life.
They they're doing like double penetration. They're they're all in there
Half the guys are gay. The guys are gay in the straightforward. I even noticed they can't they can't be guys do both
Fucking hell
Yeah, we guys were
You're so talkative Dennis in what?
That's that's 50% I mean
Dennis and shut the fuck up
I mean, if we if we some bitch we get we come across and it wants to suck like our dicks at the same time
I'll sit there right next to you as she sucks our dicks together. Well, no wonder we know that
That makes sense. We know that
But yeah, I want to hit that I want to hit that shit like from behind like wow
She's such a dick at the same time. Okay. I would do that. You know me
So yeah, we got with that, you know, what's wrong with that? I fuck it. That's gay that I'm gay
Have you but have you done anything on that before like have you done like a threesome before with your homie? Yeah, yeah, but it wasn't
It was sloppy. It was sloppy, bro. I was like fucking like like 19 with my with my accent shit like that
You didn't have like a little
You didn't brush up against each other at any point.
I don't know.
Maybe.
You brushed up against each other.
Yeah, I don't know. I was wondering if like the guys
What the fuck
Guys guys guys. Okay. I'm ready to kick you guys together guys off because we're having a night. No, we're not gay enough for you right now
Yes, they are gay enough for the panel guys. I want to talk to this
You guys do your gay stuff. I'll be all okay. Yeah
Yeah
I don't know. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. I'll
defend you. Oh, so, uh, Denison is still here. Okay.
Denison wants to hang out. Denison. You okay? No, my
fucking, uh, my real dad, bro, used to do like fucking like
mushrooms and like fucking LSD and shit and do like it get in
through it get in orgies. I have pictures of my my dad
My real dad. So he used to like get all fucking baked out and fucking like get crazy sex like sex with whoever
Yeah, I've been like, you know, I've been doing DMT with my friends and it's like it has gone kind of sexual
Like with that and it's like it never has before like in all the years
I've known that it's like never never has now
It's like he's like, you know taking off his shirt and like, you know
It comes in right next to me flexing and she's like bending over cleaning and like I don't know it's getting like kind of interesting
Uh, I don't know if it's uh, yeah, there's loosens youngs. They're pretty fucking cool. I
You know, I I want to get one of those
I'm just being serious, you know, my dad my dad was a freak. You know, I mean he fucking uh
So
You know, I take out for my dad's
I like to fucking I listen I like porn I watch porn
I want to go to the fucking, uh, uh, adult video.
Here it is.
Oh, here it is.
I have a few seconds.
Okay.
Thanks.
Yeah, you know what I mean? I like I go to strip clubs. I get fucking I get lap dances and shit like that
Yeah, I went since I went I've been to Vegas once when the AVS were in town
I would be there there for different reasons the AVS just happened to be in town
There's a lot of porn stars walking around. It's also the moonlight bunny ranch. It's in Nevada some place that
That's not in that's not in a big person city. It's a Carson City. Maybe I'm not sure but you know
Yeah, I know where it is. It's not it's a prostitution isn't legal in Clark County, which is Nevada, like a Vegas. Yeah. I mean, yeah, it's you can get it, you know, yeah. Well, I just remember seeing the casinos like, you know, like back in the day was like, yeah, even back in the he was like a hippie.
Yeah, like get going Ortiz, dude. Like, you know, I would I'm not trying to like fucking like fuck other guys
But like if you want to fucking like, you know fuck her in the ass while she sucks my dick, let's do it
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like that's why you know, we can all be everyone can everyone can
Departure gay it's so gay
Denizen so that isn't so hold up Denizen
so
Lucky Pierre is the guy that's like he's being fucked and he's also fucked me at the same time
And so it's like he's leaving the middle. He was lucky Pierre
Monkey in the middle. That's that'll be me. That'll be me. It all goes right. Okay
Yeah
I do like how I like, you know, I do see like a lot of fluidity like especially like, you know, and
Yeah, there's a big ghetto presence in like the adult videos and even like the gay thing
You know, it's like they did to people at 10th man and women. I mean, it's like, you know, there's people all kinds of you know
There's the 40 diamonds in the neighborhood. There's that
Not too many sexy awakens, but you know, there's only one sexy awakens
But you know, I wouldn't be surprised if a lot of gay dudes do porn
Right. Oh, yeah, they definitely do. Yeah, and because they're not really into it, right? So they can just act
And they're basically they can get hard. I mean usually they are like but there's so like I mean
There's like so many of the things I watched have been like, you know
We've used gangbangs with like a multiple black guys, right?
And it's like that is very comfortable like, you know doing the gangbangs and the double penetration and there's
You know white people are a little bit more squeamish. I don't know. It's like
Yeah, or it was just like it's very popular. I don't know why I said the group's a black guy
The money was right dude, I would fucking I would get on chatter bait and fucking, you know
You do some gay shit on chatter bait for like, you know, give me some money. Let's go
Well, yeah, well you could I mean it's like chatter bait. I've noticed it's like, you know, if you do it, right? Yeah, I would say
You know you get in there. You would like you set up a menu of like, you know things you're willing to do
I have one. I was just never able to
When I first made it you know what you have you have a chatter bait
Yeah, when I first made it when I went live dude, I had like all these fucking viewers
They're like, oh, this would be interesting like what look at it. Yeah
And I was like, I couldn't do it.
I couldn't show my dick.
But they were a bit of, yeah.
But yeah, that's why you have to put a menu with a certain number
of tokens.
And then it's like, and then you just kind of like,
you know, we take off your shirt or something like that
and just hang out and talk.
And then someone's going to, like,
people are going to start donating for the tokens
for the goal.
And then you just complete the goal.
And that's also, if you don't want to do it on the screen,
there's also people that just do it all private shows.
And so it will just take you off into a private show
with the person.
I'm a, how do I say I'm not, I'm a.
Sexually free or whatever like I'm not okay anything type shit. Yeah, I don't care
Well, I think that's good. It's like I'm not so good. And I'd be yeah
And I definitely you're wanted to collaborate on chatter, but I do have a counter and I would be well. I'd be happy to
But yeah, yeah, I know we can make some money
We can make some money, you know if you want to make some money like I think I think we do a lot better
You know, I think it's the other you know, but uh
You know, there's people that do groups. There's a group to like five people. There are people in Mexico. They're all over. They're all over the country.
Let's make bank on that shit. Yeah. Yeah. I'm ready. Let's go. Let's make money.
I know guy. I know guy. His name is Sean Gatz and he bought a food truck. He made over a million dollars on only fans.
They just do it only fans and he does. He's a tattoo artist. All he did was he tattooed his chode and he tattooed his like his dick or something like that on.
And then he did a couple like scenes with his girlfriend and stuff like that, but he made a million dollars in like about a year or only then.
You can see him, he's a Sean Gats, he's a Gats Deli, he tests the value too.
Yeah, I mean, it's a bit, yeah, and so it's like, you know, it's like, it's a little bit, I just like, me just being alone, it's like, on a camera, it's like, you know, I can do that here where I'm just talking and stuff like that, but it's kind of like different on test.
And I think people do like me on Chatterbait because, you know, I'm like well endowed and it's like, and then...
people you'll always like oh I want you to come like um in like have sex with my wife I want to watch
or like and then people that would know when everything's I'm gay on it um
listen hey we listen if we if we if I got on chatter rate with you bro we'd have to have another
chick we have to have a check okay yeah we can we have to find it yeah we get a check yeah okay yeah
I think they do a lot of that. Yeah, they do a lot of that. I think they do a lot of like the I don't know what section you have to put it
But it's like yeah, I have seen them
But there's a bunch of like Russian guys and then they have like one one chick and then they're all like getting naked and stuff
And she's like they're too and like but even the gay guys seem to like like you need to be sucking our dicks like fucking
You suck at mine. It's yours suck suck mine go back and forth type shit and fucking it and after that
I don't be hit that shit fucking in her ass. I'll hide her ass
And fuck you, you know why she sucks your dick and then fucking they know if she wants to sit there and fucking like ride
My dick with her pussy and then fucking you could like hit the ass. It seems like he's giving this some thought
Yeah, I mean, yeah
Guys who is anybody in the chat what about you want to go to Vegas for
We're gonna Vegas
We're gonna do some filming in Vegas guys
I like this guy. I like this guy.
I'll party with you. I'm down.
But I'm not trying to fucking fuck guys.
I'm afraid for that kitty.
The kitty will be fine. The kitty will be fine.
You'll be afraid. You'll be afraid.
I'm going to take your word for it.
I will take good...
I'll make sure...
I'll be down for a gangbang on a bitch though.
I'm not trying to fucking fuck guys in the ass though, dude.
Okay, okay.
Well, we'll take these one step at a time.
What's the kitty's name?
The kitty. Yeah, what's your kitty's name Chris? The fuck is going on in here?
You should know. His love is in the air. Don't you see? Don't you feel it? Should know. Why would I know?
It seems like someone had a baby oil spill. Hey, you're still, you're still, I have a lot of it, I have an extra supply.
It's Albert. Oh, I love it, Albert. Does it look like Albert?
Hey Al, hey Al, Albert, you sure, is the editor Albert Einstein or what's the name after?
I like the name Albert. I had a kind of Alec actually, so that's pretty similar.
Who's a virgin? Who's a virgin? Is Chris K. is not a virgin. I think Chris K. is the
head sex.
I don't know. I just wondering if Chris K. I just wondering what I just want to know what happened in some of those house parties
I don't know. It's been you got a little
I've been raped by chicks before dude. Oh, okay. That's not drunk and these bitches I wake up. They're sucking my dick
I'm like what like fucking eat on me. Yeah, it's all bad. No all women all women though
It's like you're not you're never vocal with a guy doing that did you?
No, okay. No, you do a second
You ain't got over on a lot of band of trap houses. Uh, where the junkie horse be, uh, I
used to rise around the best trap house in
Glendale, California, you know, I had pretty much the number one the best one within a few cities
And it was, that was the place to be for a while.
I know a couple of years, a couple of years.
It was crazy.
All my windows were broken out of my house, by the way.
I didn't get stabbed in the ear.
I was very heavily, I had a lot of problems,
but here, I'm doing much better here.
You swear to God, I hope the room get,
oh, I don't know what's gonna happen.
I mean, I have, I've done, not on here, but on Discord.
I had the Cam on like so I had I called up
Like a frosty come over and see I see I can't jack me off right here
Come on everything and fucking she got the lotion out. Just kept going
Asian bitch Asian chick and
She was how I felt her to you know, I want it, you know everything I want to do
She requires she's like wait, you got it, you know more money. I had to cash out for every time
Yeah
Donate like fucking 400 bucks. I will fucking call it a fucking bitch over here right now
I don't fucking like don't put the camera on
Guys, you're yourself committing a crime
Dollars he didn't like he didn't send me it said it over there and I will take care of him
And I would be I'll do it for you for that person. That's the thing if I'm not gonna charge you for cash
I mean, it'll be like my pleasure. It's just like, you know, I listen to whatever you want. If I hang out with you, bro
We're gonna fucking we're gonna you're gonna. Holy shit. You're gonna help me get a chip, bro
Like on the right on the beach
You know cuz you live by the beach real
Yeah, yeah
You're gonna use your attractive gay friend to lure in some unsuspecting woman is that what you're saying?
I'll go yep, I'll go I'll go I'll go in the pure my speed. Oh
Fucking you we can kind of get it like, you know, maybe get some drinks
Bring back your pad and we can do it with double teeth
that
I'll be experienced experience for me too. It'll be experience for me too
you know and I know
If in the midst, you know, we never know what might happen, you know, if you're over here with your gay shit, you know
The pin, you know, let's see the salary. How did it go? It gets going touch it. I mean, that's what I'm not
Let me say I'm not I'm not like, uh, you know, homophobe bro like fucking whatever you like fucking, you know
I mean, so that's it. So yeah, I mean, what's a little bit of anal sex between friends, you know what I'm saying?
I don't know. I don't know. I'm starting at a brick drive for this
You know, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
I don't, you know, I feel like
my friend, you know, yes, you
are. I want to like, you know, I
have to like, I have to say, you
know, because I got to drive down
there, it's just good to take.
I don't want to like
Be like oh, I'm gonna come like stay your house like I want to make sure I have money. Let me stay hotel
Yeah, well, my house is like you know, it's like a lot like
Cleaner because did my friends have been helping me out and so so you want to share your dick with him, but not a bit
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
ༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀༀ
I mean like you'd be down for that shit like that, you know, like tag like tag team like, you know
I'll be hitting that shit. We can switch off tag team back again. I'll be like WWE. It'll be like, you know
You know, and I fucking if you know if fucking that, you know, I'll stream
You know streaming on a chatterbait or whatever. Yeah, we can we can stream some of it. Well, yeah
Some of them will probably be too hot for you to I
Need money, bro. I need money. That's why
Yeah, but we maybe do a stream off of chatter chatter, but we can send people to the chatter bait and they know maybe
We'll see guys guys. We have so there's so many possibilities with this show like who knows where
Put it on chatter bait it might
And then you guys have a whole gang bang Pat play the Alice clip for the Alice clip
Guys, yeah
You have to realize like there could be like, you know kind of like maybe like
Some foreign important, you know, basically people people will see it
You know, I don't know if I'll ever get out, but you know, you gotta be very confident yourself
There's a lady that lives underneath me that just banging on my floor that'd be too loud
Uh, we're not even being loud. You know, we are we are getting kind of excited. Uh, are you guys going to go?
Sure
Sure, go check. No, you guys should go check
I don't know. Oh, hold on. No, no, no, no, no guys. You don't be don't be impolite people are saying whole thing
I am very I'm very safe. You know, I'm very safe, you know
so
I can't believe she's back that fucking bitch. This this is the same bitch that calls the cops on me all the time for being loud
She's made on my floor
Like underneath me like fucking
Look at that me loud. So I'm gonna try to chill. Oh, you know me?
Yeah
Yeah, I had another like there's another terror reader. I would watch and she had like a
Some lady from upstairs with like bang on her day and she was just start screaming at her and she's oh my god
They're she's like this bitch is there was an old times of night. She was just like bang on that
Don't use the answer. Yes, there's so let's see
Your beat a mods you okay, so
Yeah, so how are we doing tonight? Are you exiled in it and then didn't see and how how are we doing tonight?
Are you are you doing good here? Are you gonna come to the party? You're down. You're down to be in the gang bang
I'm single as shit, and I'm still not going to
you're not coming, we're single, come on, we're going to get some hose
you can be like Jenny Fox and hold the camera, Denison
You can't get the angles, you know, maybe some nice, nice, uh, nice butt shots and you know, dinner since working on becoming a monk
So he's very
Yeah, he's trying not to like fuck up his enlightenment
Yeah, well, you know, I just study like I studied to bend Buddhism under the Dalai Lama's Lama
Dabi Rinpoche
Well, he's only doing these things for study purposes. He don't believe in any of it. Oh, he does. Oh, it's okay
Okay. Oh, there really no women in their gang bang
Yes, there will
If we come down to it, I'll have to get out my
my party's to the blonde wig and you know, we can turn off the lights, whatever happens
to happen, whatever happens to happen to us.
Nah, come on, nah, you're not fooling me, I know you could, you could, you could easily
attract some women.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, do you have 40 diamonds?
How many women have you slept with, Pat?
We hire 40 diamonds
Yeah, play the Alex clip bro play the Alex clip
He's being a tease tonight
Have you heard the trans ever or no or is that like or anybody?
No, I got married to my wife and then all that trans stuff started happening like before then I didn't know about no trans people
To each his own. I don't care what people do, but it's still a dude. Oh, you're flashy Chris
Yeah, all I know is my man not hoard myself out the women
Yeah, well, you know, I think like be quiet because the lady or anything just banged on my floor
And I don't want her to call the cops. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I think it's it's a camera just like sort of like
Okay, so she calls the cops stop beating on the floor. You're louder than us beating on that damn floor
Maybe get maybe a headphones because they get headphones. So you're like sometimes
I do
To be honest, I'm not being loud. She's just a fucking Karen's bitch. It's fucking. Yeah true. I've already. Yeah, you're not being
Barbecue Becky stop. Oh, why why are you being super quiet now though? Like who cares what she does?
You're gonna fucking lose your deposit when you fuck that
I'm about to just go to sleep anyway type shit and fucking
I look I didn't know she was like actually back already. She's our dad. Don't let their lady
Come over right now come over right now and we can like yeah, well, uh, you can see people you can spend it over here
You don't do it. Yeah, you stay
Yeah, you stay in apartment don't you you don't let your neighbors for
I'm just saying, you don't let your neighbor force you into a car for you, do you?
Soon, Chris. Soon, Chris. Soon, Chris.
Well, I mean, not if he's not being loud, right? Like...
My neighbors could kiss my ass.
It's just a normal voice love. Yeah. I mean, come on.
I'll be on my deck at three in the morning loudest.
Please send the cops to my house.
I will tell the cops through the door that I'm going to file a complaint if she doesn't stop making false police reports.
Yeah.
I've talked to them and they they're gonna they started to say like where they're gonna give her
Citations if you keep right
exactly exactly
Fuck that beach
Well stop beating on the floor before you get to pull these cod on yourself
That's what I was wondering are you stomping your feet or hitting the table?
No
Just your voice
That is a woman from upstairs
Are you she downstairs in like the same house and you rent a room or is it an apartment complex?
It's an apartment complex what Jesus Christ she needs the minor old business get a white noise machine is some shit
So she's not even just disturbing you. She's disturbing other neighbors as well. For real for real
I don't know sometimes people can hear walls are kind of more thin than other times, but it's like, you know
It's like just
Melatonin tell her take a moment
Chill pill and
Before
and I went down there and I have a fucking video of me walking down there and like live
it's live streaming it saying hey stop fucking banging on my shit bitch like I'm not even
fucking loud it's fucking 12 fucking noon right and I fucking I recorded the whole thing
and fucking uh after that she started calling the cops instead of banging on the floor so
is weed legal in your state?
Yeah, hell yeah
You should like tape a joint tour motherfucking
Door would have led it says here's your chill pill chill the fuck out
Oh, I would be a little more passive aggressive when it comes when there's legal consequences
Like I've had that situation before and literally I would just start playing my guitar louder than I normally do
So like if I like if I'm on the phone having a conversation, right?
And she bangs on this the floor my floor her ceiling because I'm being too loud
That's what I'm gonna break out the guitar amp and open the window and show you what loud means
Basically do all the shit. She's been accusing you. Oh, it's exactly
Fucking excited for not doing yeah, I become like a shitty girlfriend real fast if you're a shitty neighbor
That's the thing listen like she I do all that passive aggressive shit
She has no idea like I have a fucking a 500 watt receiver in my group my closet
With the fucking sub with its own amp like you want to hear. Yeah, see fucking windows. Are you saying?
Yeah
I know the average response time too, right? So by the time the cops come it's gonna be quiet
I'm gonna be in the living room listening to my TV super low by the time they show up
To 15s do
Or hey, hey, I'll come over there. I'll come over there. We can make some noise. We can make we can make the
apartment shake
Don't she was she's been gone for like a month. I guess she's back now
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
And I have fucking homies that will fucking that are female. They might fucking like this like fuck you up
And it's homie fucking this bitch will be fucked up dog type shit
the
where you got a bunch of
Then you order a carrier service and have them order uh deliver some of the food to all your neighbors, but that bitch
Yeah, we can we can't bite we can bite them to the gang thing
too, we can we can we can like how you know we can give them at least you know at least uh
You know a lay and a gift a gift bag baby, so they could you know that's okay, man
He's like don't get this back. I can they can they can take it they can take one slide on the slip and slide
It's gonna be a big baby. I'll slip and slide. It's gonna be amazing. I'm like anything
It's amazing. Yay. Okay.
Everyone's here. There's 33 people in chat. 33 is a nice number.
It might be a year from now.
Somebody might come up on that. It's from a year from now. She won't even know.
Why does that happen?
I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy. I'm a little bit busy
Bandit, okay, you have the you have the mystery and so the mystery is something okay
So the mystery is like the high priestess card, which is like a very you know
Intuitive and you already know you you're part of the mystery you understand the mystery, but then we have like the
What's the mystery about has nothing to do with the truth it has something to do with you finding out the truth
Are you knowing the truth you having the truth and the truth can be like a sword, you know
If you can cut down at him, you know Kim's
You know raise up it can do different things, you know, but you know you have something about you finding the truth
Or you're knowing the truth and you being able to speak the truth and this and moving forward on something
So I hope you like that reading. Okay. There you go
Yeah, that's good. Okay, so how do I feel about it tonight? How are you feeling pretty good? Stay turn. I feel pretty good
Uh, I feel pretty pretty good because you know
I like, I like this guy. I like, I like for a few weeks, uh,
kind of interesting tonight.
Um, yeah, band is here. I hope you like that. That sounds right.
Okay. Um, hey, states are, hey, uh, hey everybody.
Uh, yeah, good. Okay, yeah.
First, then, midnight.
Daryl says could have stopped playing and dancing to Yoraka in your high heels
Yeah, yeah, Yoraka
Kaka's yeah, I don't know what it is. Oh, okay. He's back here
Hey, what's going on? You guys done with your having your little orgy thing?
Yeah, well, yeah, it's free schedule. You know, we just had it like a little we know a little like a little
The cat many freak off this they still need a camera man JT
Yeah
GT you want to get back up I mean we have gift bags with the little files of baby oil and
Cocaine isn't gonna be in there. You know, I value my eyesight and
Beer a beer one beer a couple beers. You're back thinking. Hey Vicky. Hey midnight. Yeah
Yeah, something is that sounds I think I
You know yeah, you know like everyone everyone's coming to freak out. Yeah, but it's like real guys
That's where it's worth it's with these animal masks. It's not like a furry. There's just these
Like the like a masquerade ball. Yeah, like I like eyes wide shut so we don't nobody can be bright in those
Yeah, yeah, because it'll be you know, the reason we think it's happening in the photos like you know
Everyone knows just be like oh, who was that no no one will be able to tell me you might be able to like see my
Tattoo and you know, I am very noticeable
Frank, but you made it big
He'll be up. He'll be uh, probably will
Reasonable down
CB
Moonlings that yeah, so anyone coming to the freak out. I gotta need your arse if he's right now right now
Okay, we're gonna do this
Chris is really excited. I think Chris was breaking up
You know Chris would love that. Yeah
I
Can't believe that fucking bitch is back. I got to deal with this
Who is it? Oh, she's a lady that was upstairs. I don't want to worry about her just ignore her
Just like you know, that's why I'm saying headphones because then you won't even hear her like banging on that thing
I'll just ignore her. It's like it's like if she's not there. Don't worry about you
We're just have one ladies knocking, you know, it's like just like means you're like, you know
alive
Room gang left me. Oh, I'm sorry. Good night
Listen, this is this thing. This is my thing right here. Like I'm not gonna go to jail over this bitch. That's all yeah, don't
If you
Go down there and fucking I could go down there and fucking like bang on her fucking door break your fucking door
Don't do that. Don't do that. Don't don't don't make it
You go is knocking
Please stop please stop being or whatever she's doing. What kind of shit is she doing?
Yeah, reverse psychology go down her touch. She keep beating on the ceiling evil
Midnighters at 1 a.m. There's a
Ludicrous
It's actually squabble 1 a.m. So it is
You know, I'm talking this normal talking and she's banging out that this loudness
It's like, fuck it, it's crazy.
You should be here to the police.
Peter to the police called the police on her.
She's knocking on the ceiling.
Wait, so your girlfriend is knocking on your door?
Like, what's going on?
I
Live and down stairs the woman that lives upstairs or downstairs, and they're knocking on the they're knocking on
Just stay in the same place don't walk around too much and like you know and then you know just talking that's not gonna know a voice
Who call first you should call them on her
I'm better over for a beer. No, I don't you know, I don't call the cops
Yeah, I try to make friends with her
I'm sure for that entertainment
Because like I think you know, I have the most conversation I had with her was
I was like, I'm sorry for the noise or whatever.
She's like, I can hear you rolling around on a computer chair.
And I hear you yelling.
I don't know who you're talking to up there.
I'm like, that's why I have this chair right here
that doesn't roll.
But I have like a fucking gaming chair that does roll.
And I switched it, dude, just for that reason.
Tell her you're like a telemarketer,
or you're like, worth some home on the phone.
And so you're going to be talking to people all the time.
I work from home.
Like, what do you want me to do?
I told the cops this shit, too.
Decimometer that you know shows like I could legally fucking be the specific decimals like legally to fucking you know loudness like fucking
You know me they're they're like, yeah, well, she should have known this we're moving into a complex like this or whatever
I'm like, yeah, no shit
Like you know me I hear fucking all kinds of loud noises. I don't trip like fuck. That's what I moved here
That's what I moved. That's what I came into
Yeah
Thank you. Did you know did you know he's an aerometer? How it is here? No, he's not
Kristen then doing readings on my show for several months now. Like, you know, he's he's out. He's been here for a long time
Obviously almost since I started just a few months ago, you know, and
He's always you know, he's like a different he's a different style of reading and I say I enjoy a different style for sure
Yeah, I like having a straight guy like there's not many straight guys that do tarot cards
And it's like at least like you know, it's like, you know, at least I've noticed that like many straight guys that do tarot cards are very
detail-oriented about it like they're very specific and then like with it and
it's like I think it's like half about like knowing that the actual meanings
and like the like the technical stuff and then half of it is like intuition and
but I think he has that I think he has the intuition so I think he's just like
kind of like developing is the female issue.
You have like the gay intuition things, yeah.
Something gay intuition, it's just like having,
like we have the masculine and feminine side,
it's just like, and so we have both sides of our brain,
we have the feminine and the like, it's like on over.
We all have it, we all have it, people are like saying,
people just put too much attention to like the sex,
these genders of sexes, and this is how the sex is act.
We're actually, we're very complex,
our brains are the most complex,
organisms on the entire planet, you know, and so it's like, you know, we're very complicated people
and beings were amazing beings, and so
you know
you gotta
Gotta enjoy our life, you know, so it's a big key. Oh, it's a great. Okay. Okay. We're fighting in chat
No, I have you had a straight guy on panel tonight. Yeah, of course in the straight guy. This is a guy I think
JT's I think he said it's straight
Exile said he's straight and
Everyone's straight here except for me. I'm just I'm the only thing straight about me or my teeth
And they're not even that straight anymore. So I mean, I don't know guys
How old are you, Chris? How old are you, Chris?
How old are you, Chris? You're 38? You're 38, I think you're 37.
You're 39. You're 39, okay.
So, okay, somewhere this word for yours is the same name. I'm just 44.
I mean, how old are you? 44.
Over here, Abraham Lincoln.
Every I'm like, hey, I'm yeah
Okay
Listen, I'm just tripping out because I didn't realize she was already she's back
Okay, okay, are you using her to like you know
Get away from okay. We'll talk about things later. We can talk about this we can talk about discord in private
We'll talk about this one. We'll do it. Are you on my discord? I'm gonna talk to you in private
Can we do we do a discord video chat sometimes?
Yeah, you want a video chat with him, okay?
Okay, well, sometimes no, no, no, no rush. No, no, no, it's okay. Yeah, I'm not I'm on the discord
But I'm not in here. Okay. Okay. I think I am
The guy that said he saw his dad having orgies and that he would do gay shit for money
This is the same crazy. Yeah, he said he won't know he's a perm I mean from well, yeah
I mean, I'm not not like he was charging me. He said he would like, you know, for you he'd do it for free. I'm sure but you know in general
Will be involved for sure like fucking he's got to be like her
What's going on? What's going on gentlemen? How you doing psyche? What's up on Chris K exile wolf man was good
The audio is good
Oh, we have another guest one didn't and it's in his back. Why don't we do a chatter? But yeah, I want to do a chatter
We can collab and we can make so much what they wouldn't have got a thing yet. He said he had chatter bait
Yeah, yeah, so it's like if you're there if you're verified you have to send your ID in there and get verified that we both have verified that we
Can do it like a joint?
Yeah, or we can just do our shows and like you I'm sure you get so much donation and you know
We just like you know basically just hang out and we just do your quest or whatever you want to hang out with psyche on chatter bait
Yeah, yeah, of course why wouldn't he want to of course?
What's wrong with that? You won't want to talk to psyche on the chat. It says chatter base. Whatever that is. It sounds like a check
That's your homeboy, right? That's your means, right? That's your means like he's your means, right?
I don't know
Guys, you know, some people are gonna like, you know, maybe give you a little shit, but you know what? No, I
you know, I like
I
I get to kind of like I think I know you're straight
You know, you're not really down to like, you know, you like the bus stuff or whatever, but like right now, but
Uh, you know, you know, who knows what can happen as like, you know, with the bright circumstances, you know, what exactly hold up that chatter based thing that you're talking about. Is that a gay app? Is that a gay app? No, no, it's, it's day straight. I mean, they have they have they have women on there. They have men on there and they have like men that sit there, you know, straight men, they have men that are.
I don't think so either. I don't think so either, Wolfman. Yeah, you know what I'm saying?
He seems pretty open minded, I think I'm good. I'm good. I'm not trying to piss him. Yeah. Yeah. No, you're not
Like I'm dead serious. I'm dead serious. I
So why wouldn't he you know want to kick it with you on that particular ad?
I agree Vicky said Vicky watches gay porn and she says it doesn't mean anything. Yeah, I mean, I don't know if he was
I mean, it's like I mean, I was straight for I was straight for I didn't watch
I'm straight in real life
Yeah
Who ain't hold on who watches gay porn?
A gay person
or it's like really into some weird shit
Chris, did you say you liked gate porn earlier or no?
Chris, did you like gate porn earlier or no?
But he never know he never answered about the trans he's been with the trans he went with the trans person
You never answer a psyche sake. Let me let me ask you a question brother. I never heard about this particular app
Right, you said it's gay straight and trans correct. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, so so let me ask you
Let me just ask you one question one question brother. Hey, you got the floor. Um
If it's gay straight and trans, why would why would the straight people join this app?
Like if it's mostly like, you know, gay people or trans people, it's not it's not
There's a women's area
There's like where it's all women or couples or like straight couples and then there's like a gay area where there's like
It's not a dating app. It's like a it's like a it's like a there's a bunch of chat rooms on it
Website for a live stream that's like this, but it just doesn't get posted to YouTube, right
I'm just trying to understand that I'm very new to technology
Cam girls
Are we like this is probably
But you know what it's free also it's free and then it's like even it's even free go in the chats
You can either like, you know, sometimes people donate you donate tokens to perform or if you give requests and stuff like that
They're usually doing stuff anyway
And sometimes they're doing some for other people but then they sometimes the people will take them into a private show and that's like
Oh, and then you have your little one-on-one with that person. Yeah. Yeah
All right, I like that shit if it's straight men, you know for straight men talk them talk women like
Make sure you're at work when you do it, too
I
If I'm going as far as like some internet shit like it'll be hoes on Instagram that
You know, I mean I hit up slot and they did they might fuck around to be married and still pop out for the night
You know, yeah
Like I've never knew what a fucking stream yard was until last year. I'm only like I'm one year fresh into this shit
Like I really I'm a baby at this shit. I didn't even know
like existed all you'll definitely like that chatter bait shit you should check it out
nah it's too many it's too you got i'm sorry i don't know
no that's the only one you need you can let go of the other one
no that's a different that's all you need
like that's gonna be a different show
there's too many categories that's off the wall for me you get what i'm saying
yeah i know i know but if you wanted to you wanted to do like a you know
but if you wanted to do like you don't have to wait till you find out about all the trends on instagram
Yeah
Bitches I know in real life though like on Instagram
Yeah, then let's you hit them from the back, you know
Don't even ask for a reach around, you know
This is a dude who's talking to me
Me this is psyche. Are you guys?
Do talking shit it was a door exile
Who was I talking to just who is Papa shit just now if you were talking to Denison right now
Denison oh the
Yeah, oh, I thought it was a I'm looking at. Oh, I thought it was a
Yo, Dennis, yo, what you want to say to me, bro? So talk your shit
Get it off your chest family. What do you want to say to me?
You throw a set you you say here throwing jabs here and there say what you got to say family get it off your chest
And we'll go about our conversation get it off your chest
Chatterbait.com
It'll replace all the other sites you're using. Yeah, who the fuck is it?
It replaced some side chicks like
What makes you think I'm looking for bitches though like like seriously, what's up with you, bro?
No, I think he said it replaced. Are you having a stroke right now?
You want to end it at looking for bitches like the way you sitting here implying that shit on me like bro
Are you projecting bitches?
Who sent the word bitches?
I said bitches
Are you having a stroke right now?
Who sent the word bitches?
I'm telling you
I said bitches
Yeah, you said bitches, correct
So
You need to check out that chatter bait calm
You send it to the HR lady to shoot like oh, yeah, yeah, you're all that and all that you listen you right
We're gonna listen to the rest of psyche stream. You're fucking boring
You're a clown, bro fall back
Keep talking back in the psyche show you're
So who's there?
This is a weird ghost here.
Oh, no, it's not a ghost.
How am I supposed to talk to him?
Hey, psyche, don't say nothing, because, like,
when I start tripping, don't kick me off, you are...
You're already fucking hearing things so I think you're tripping already.
I think you're whilin' on already.
I will, I will, but if we hit the back...
You think I'm havin' on everything?
You know
Why are you diverting don't stop diverting
Yeah, I took your shit let's get into the next conversation you steady throwing
Like every time I really spaz for real like stop playing
I'm not the one you want to be with him.
This is you're not special.
Chris, I'm competition.
Chris, Queen Hippo has a crush on you,
and she says she is in Vegas too.
There you go.
Doesn't that sound nice
Chris thumbs up or thumbs down
I mean, what queen? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
You want to come? Are you? Oh, ghost you want to join the orgy too? I would I would love to join this
Yes, yes, I am you'll I am gay
Oh
That's goes goes what you running goes
I think
There's only ones that say he said he's busty. What is it? Oh my pussy. Oh, okay. Yo, right? Hey, come up top crack
Hey, stop saying my name in the check come up top crack it
Anybody
I think you know, I think this is a really good guy like I you know, I I don't have like the best like self-esteem sometimes like about my
I think I think it's very attractive. I just remind you of the the guys I was in like jail with for a few days
I was in jail for a few days for like some
L.A. County, yeah, L.A. County, yeah, L.A. County, okay
Yeah
Like a man, you almost fuck you almost fuck the bitch that's that that that third day, right?
There's one guy that really likes me I should be shy with him and he like gave me his phone
phone card number
Ayo psyche is that when you is that when you first turned on gay as a gay man? No, no, no
No, I was already gay before I was gay. I mean I did
How well you was when you became when you became on a gay man or when you like knew it
Like when you're doing your head put it like that
We're doing it. I knew I knew probably by 11 or 12 and it's like then I came out probably 13 14 and then
you know and then it was like I was very out I was the only one in my school that was even out
in the closet yo psyche did you ever fuck a bitch in your life
Yeah, I had some of that one woman that when I dated this one woman
I was like 32 or 33 and she was like
Yeah, you ain't get no pussy until you was 32 33. Yeah. Yeah
How did you not fall in love with that shit after that though like I don't understand
Well, she was a 50 year old woman. Yeah, she was not a heavy set heavy set. Yeah
I'm gonna say like 50%
I believe you wouldn't be gay if your first experience with abroad was terrible, but your
best experience with a man was like, well, it might have been like super.
Educated and you get what I'm saying like you had the worst sex with a woman
And that's why you went to them
I get bored actually having sex I like it's more like fun to think about
That's what turns you
With a beat up broad you had a beat up broad which you couldn't get jiggy. You was already kind of feeling men
And then you probably ended up with some type of pro that turned your ass out like
I
Don't have sex with a lot of people like I like you know
I was I had my wild days kind of late in my 20s like my teens of my
I'm not really like in this. I'm like more into finding love now
I
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's a but I've talked about memory. She was kind of she was a kind of a witch. She's like a, you know, witch, a shapeshifter.
He's a fucking alien reptilian, bitches.
She put she put she had menstrual fluid and like forgetting thousands of stuff. Yeah. So I was wondering about something else. I was wondering why I haven't charged.
uh changed the channel yet can't find okay what did she what did she say shift
into oh yeah oh she said she didn't say like uh like a younger like attractive
like indian woman you know it's like kind of a goddess because with blue skin
and like with like ornamental i mean it was just very like it was like very
crazy illusion uh it is like an illusion i suppose but it is yeah
You know, she put lsd in your coffee. Yeah. Yeah, there was like some people there's some weird. I don't know if there is yet
But yeah, that's like he always does better comments
Second me five my comments, and you always read the words what the worst one every time I know there's five hundred comments
I read the worst comment. I'm sorry chat stays stay turn gay. That's why you didn't go. Hey
He laughs what was that what did you show guys? He just showed me when he was naked was he?
Was that psyche psyche? That was my psyche. That was my camera. Oh, okay
I was in the top that was me
I'm not listen no pulling ball me. I'm I'm not doing all that
Okay, hi
Hello, sir. I you're all you're black. I'm shocked
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
I don't know anybody else that you know. No, I'm crazy. It's interesting too. Yeah. Yeah. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like
Thank you
Okay, please don't change your photo, okay, I love how the frizzy. Oh my gosh will Vader come on
Don't call me a fringy loser all males. You should go. Yeah, come on Anna. What Anna?
Why isn't she full of men? I don't know because you know the case the way
Page, I don't know who did is like I think we ghost. Did you do that you change this page?
Chris, I don't think Chris did. I think the page is like she's had her phone died or something like that early
She was like this is gonna be in chat when a gangster and you've been on YouTube for eight years. Yeah, okay
Sweet he's curious
Let's see
JT okay guys come on is the link up? Yeah my link is up come on ladies come on join the panel
Where did all these new people come from these people are from everywhere? They're from everywhere guys?
I have 2,500 subscribers. I have been
My number 10, but I don't know sometimes people put my my shoulder just what I do appreciate
I do ask you to share my like share subscribe, but you know as I see me friendly
Um, you know in a good for my show in a good light and not have people come here and
People have been very nice lately. So I really am happy about that. How's everyone doing? It's like a Jimmy Dean's factory in here
Why why?
Why do you need you because it has like
What not not because there's not spam
People spam the chat. It's like, you know, I don't know for products
Easy. Oh who just left?
Chris, Chris, oh my God, where'd he go?
Okay, that's okay, it's okay.
Well, Chris, Chris is about,
I think Chris is like, you know,
I think he got a little overwhelmed.
I know, I'm a little bit too much.
I got a little bit, you know, expect, hopefully he'll come back.
We'll see
He's right there. I'm sorry. I thought you were, I thought you were gone. Who left? Someone else left.
Wait, listen, I'm tripping out because the chick underneath me has been gone for like two months
And now she's like suddenly back begging on my floor
And I'm just trying to like figure that out because I now I have to like adapt
Chris what if what if Chris what if I have a surprise for you?
What if I written the apartment downstairs and moved in argument me knock that's me knocking on them on the ceiling
Come on and come on over
Get in the bed
I just say we can't even want to hear a fuck-up page well no listen I was I was like playing music earlier
And I was like Nelly to like the lyrics and like fuck it. She must hurt it
Well, were they with a terrible lyric and an awful song
No, I mean
Why are you why are your eyeballs like fucking when you call the cops on me dude fucking I trip
I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't fucking, I don't
No, it's not. No, it's not.
Chris, you're getting mad at me.
Chris, it's not me. It's not me.
It's not me downstairs. I was just
kidding. It was a joke. It was a
joke. It was a joke. What happened?
No, listen, I know you bro. I just fuck. I'm talking about that bitch on an evening. I don't give
Fuck that bitch. We don't care. Fuck that bitch. Wait. Why are you why do you care? Like, you know, who cares if they don't just ignore her
We're putting her in a head post. She's not gonna bother you because you know what? Maybe I fucking maybe I fucking I don't need cops in my house
You know what? Maybe you should chill the fuck out. You ever thought about that? Yeah, maybe you should chill the fuck out
You don't have to
They're not they're not gonna have a search warrant. Maybe you should know noise complaint. Yeah, just chill out
Just chill out
Don't crash on his podcast
You want you yes, okay. Yeah, he wants okay
So, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
because I fucking, uh, there's a lot of shit I want to do, but I don't want to go to prison, you know, I know what I could do right now, and fucking, it will fucking face the problem.
Gotcha, didn't I?
You can't even fucking act around here unless you're on the prison.
If you were to act straight and not act around here, not go to prison, you were to act straight.
It's simple.
I go back. I listen. I'm not going to fucking jail or prison over this bitch. I'm done with you
I'm done with you. What what?
Yeah, anybody else want to
Time bro. I would handle it. Are you retarded for me?
You're dumb dumb
You better knock that shit against it you smoke weed. Are you a dumb dumb?
Anybody else want to talk?
Yes, up in range anybody wants to talk we can talk let's open go ahead
Don't breathe into the mic you want to say anything
Damn this shit's easy never mind fucking bunch of retards on the mic man. I'm not leaving
I'm not fucking leaving. You're you're also a retard but anybody else make a noise well for you to talk go ahead
She's gonna the fuck are you talking about?
The fuck are you talking about?
I don't care dude to be honest like fucking, but you know, I'm not doing nothing illegal. Yeah, but if she comes down there, what's gonna happen?
Yeah, but if she comes down there, what's gonna happen?
I'm gonna she does it. She's scared. She's scared of me
She's scared. She's scared. She's scared of you. I mean, that's a good point, brother. Like yeah, like yeah
You beat the fuck out of her. Yeah, you know, I'm saying like suck the fuck out of her
You know I'm saying she shouldn't come around there. You should beat the fuck out of her, right?
I feel like she's the type of chick that probably has like some fucking like
one of those like, you know
By the way, I just fucking got you and that's a clip by the way and she should actually message me
because I actually clipped you.
That's illegal.
Yeah, she should leave, you fucking retard.
You're the one hitting her, you dumb fuck.
She shouldn't message me.
You're too stupid to have the conversation.
No, you're beating on that girl.
She's a woman.
You fucking legally stole my shit.
This is my house.
Yeah, legally they stole it.
You're beating on a woman.
Yeah
You gotta be able to get her get her up to your house and for an orgy with us
This is
Yeah, I mean you just submit it to it
Well, no, he didn't say anything.
Not you psyche.
No.
No, he didn't.
No, he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he's he
All right, go and play.
You got to be in your mind.
Don't defend him.
Where I live is in the country club, very like fucking people.
There's a bunch of fucking black people out here
that fucking bulk the radios.
Sike, he just said a bunch of black people.
Don't defend them.
You need to learn how to run your panel.
No, you can say you're allowed to say a bunch of black me it was like maybe like there are African-Americans who are in the area
I don't know. It's like you know, it's not racist me. I mean can beat women and men can beat women
I'm about to take off anyway, John.
He's reporting me, okay, bye.
He's reporting me.
Thanks.